<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
                   <mteval>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref0">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A class doing a walking exercise. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman picks up a watering can, shows it, then puts it down. </seg>
<seg id="3"> One wrestler throws another wrestler, who slides across the floor on his face. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting, and one man hits the other man on his head with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A cook spreads butter on a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="7"> a woman practicing a volleyball </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is doing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A boy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a keyboard piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man rides his horse in the dessert. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing up a knotted rope suspended from the ceiling, when the scene flashes to the same man splashing water on his face from an outdoor container. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her nails. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is checking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is putting on lipstick with a brush and talking. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is firing a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> a man shooting a gun </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring chili in a kettle. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a large tree limb in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse falls down. </seg>
<seg id="23"> a man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man rides a street bike through the town. </seg>
<seg id="25"> a man and woman riding in a car </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is coating a pork chop with flour. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A black colored pet dog is biting a stuffed toy fish. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A lemur is holding up it's arms and someone is scratching him. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is riding a motor-cycle on the one wheel. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone stirs chopped vegetables in a kettle with a wooden spatula. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A young man is seated in a chair playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing on drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> a man shooting a gun </seg>
<seg id="35"> Lionel Richie dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman dips a shrimp in batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing the key board. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is window cleaning. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is adding spices on a bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around in an enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman picks up a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse by some water and a woman's head comes out of the water. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper in half lengthwise using scissors. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are rolling huge tires sideways down a street while spectators watch. </seg>
<seg id="48"> a man riding a bike on a half pipe </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man inserts the tip of a large knife into a vise and pulls the knife towards him, then removes the knife and appears to be checking the blade for straightness. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is stir frying pieces of meat using chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A raccoon-like animal is hanging off two ropes suspended from the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman carrying a baby puts him in a garbage can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby plays around in his diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is slicing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is seasoning sausage in a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting cooked chicken wings in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is smiling as he reads an email message. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone is stir-frying a ground substance in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is grazing in the grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man a playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man puts together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A tortoise chases fish in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman and a man, with their arms around each other, are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is scrambling eggs and spices in a glass bowl with a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="68"> The group Slayer plays a song onstage. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A couple ride on a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A person riding a mechanical bull </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man has his arm around a woman and they are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man plays a violin on the roof of a house. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A gerbil is getting washed. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is lying on a lounge chair on the beach partially covered by a beach umbrella. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is being treated for an emergency in a hospital. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy cutting grass at the edge of a sidewalk turns and yells something. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cuts throw a rope, suspended from the ceiling, with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is karate kicking at someone's gloved hand. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is placing oil in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef cooking food </seg>
<seg id="85"> Meat is being cooked in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog laying on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Lionel Richie dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man rides a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man playing a guitar on a bench. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A chef boils noodles. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A couple of policewomen are singing karaoke. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A young boy, standing on a couch, is singing into a microphone and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> An older woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A young man is seated in a chair playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping a tree in the Forrest. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A group of girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man boxing a bigger man. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing blades into a close target outside. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy does flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A man has a conversation with a younger man. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A woman and a man are holding hands and running towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man puts together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman dances in the rain out side. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Jimmy Hendrix performing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="117"> a person cutting a potatoes </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman demonstrating abdominal exercises. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A person is slicing bread with a bread knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man rides his horse in the dessert. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing the grass with a lawn mower. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man draws a four sided shape on a screen and then puts an X inside of it. </seg>
<seg id="123"> a guy typing on a computer </seg>
<seg id="124"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is skateboarding on a half pipe and he tries to do a flip and fails. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is lying on a blanket on a rock and reading a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> a woman cutting chicken and vegetables </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down a street and the scene flashes to a man and woman bowing. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman cuts up some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is placing eggs into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="132"> a person cutting up a fruit </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping and dicing onions with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man emerges out of a puddle of muddy water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is cutting partially peeled zucchini into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A guy levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is grazing in the grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A man playing soccer on the beach </seg>
<seg id="142"> A chef is preparing a snake for dinning. </seg>
<seg id="143"> An onion is being cut. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading his gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting cooked chicken wings in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A..man..plays...a..guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man breaks a slab of concrete that is lying on a prone man with a sledge hammer. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A guy levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man cuts the toe off a brown boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A person adds strawberries to a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man takes a shot at a target outside. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby biting on a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is giving a lecture on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man slicing a bun in half with a knife appears to cut himself. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man dangles a mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is in an office and juggling a small ball off his feet and head. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is cruising through the waters. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Someone is cutting an onion with a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A chef pours shredded mozzarella into a sauce pan. </seg>
<seg id="161"> a man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around in an enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting each other on stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deer are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman puts four okra in a pan of boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A little car sits on toy railroad tracks, as a train approaches. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The group Slayer plays a song onstage. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An airplane takes off and the wheels are drawn up inside the plane. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting, and one man hits the other man on his head with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy cutting grass at the edge of a sidewalk turns and yells something. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is voicing over his troops. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is spinning in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A boy does a back flip into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is smiling as he reads an email message. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A boy made a skull ""talk"" by moving the mouth with his hands. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> a person cutting up a fruit </seg>
<seg id="184"> A piece of garlic is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man cuts the toe off a brown boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on stage with fire in the background. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat rubs up against an infant </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman cuts up some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A young man is seated in a chair playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A group of teenagers are dancing outdoors. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person chops garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> a man and woman riding in a car </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is stuffing all kinds of food into his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezes. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is slicing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman stirs beef in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman boils eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is felling a tree. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is lying down on a blue mat exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bicycle with training wheels in circles. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Toys are floating in a bathtub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman picks up a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A demonstration of how to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is slicing a row of mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is slicing a row of mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="212"> a woman cutting a tomato </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is sliding under a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is thinly slicing a white translucent with pinkish rind looking vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is smiling while talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man wearing glasses and a suit is standing and talking in front of a huge bookshelf. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping off the edge of a bowl filled with food with a paper towel. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger club is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> a woman cutting chicken and vegetables </seg>
<seg id="223"> a man is slicing meat </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman drops down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A demonstration of how to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A person is peeling the skin off a potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="228"> hamster eating cheese </seg>
<seg id="229"> A girl applied eye makeup with a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl is doing make-up on her cheeks and forehead with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> a person walking through the woods </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man, wearing a billed hat, is playing the harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman rides her horse at walking speed. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is bouncing his front paws on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> The woman is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Two women are sitting on a couch knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is slicing raw meat into strips. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around in an enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref1">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A group of people are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman lifts up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A midget wrestler receives a face plant. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A cook spreads Crisco on a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman hits volleyballs at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A child is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a keyboard piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A cowboy rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman with purple fingernails is drumming her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is checking a calender. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is painting her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is spraying the field with a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man aims a handgun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is mixing a pot. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling in a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is picking up a tree. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse and its rider fall down. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man cuts a potato into sections. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man gets on a motorcycle and rides it out of an area of chairs and onto the street. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A man and a woman are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman brushes flour on a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up behind four people. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A doberman pincher is chewing on a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person is tickling a slow loris. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is riding on one wheel on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man mixes vegetables in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man aims a handgun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man danced on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman dips shrimp into a batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A guy is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man cleans a building glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is making garlic bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="42"> Two men are standing in a kitchen and one is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A girl is hugging a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> One man is erasing a chalkboard while a second man is talking to someone that is not in viewing range. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man cuts a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A bicycle rider is doing tricks on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man puts a knife in a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting a potato in half. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A person is cooking beef. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A slow loris hanging on a cord. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trashcan. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby bounces around a room. </seg>
<seg id="55"> a woman is slicing a vegetable </seg>
<seg id="56"> A person seasons meatballs. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts chicken wings in a container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man checks his e-mail. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is cooking beef on a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating on a field. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumped into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is adding a silencer to a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman walking hold each other. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A person whisks eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> The rock star performed with his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and a woman are riding on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A boy is playing bull riding game. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is standing on a roof top playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person washes a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A doctor is giving chest compressions to a man in a stretcher. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man with a sword slices a rope. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimp is kicking a target. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A person is cooking onions. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A big cat opens a plastic drawer with his paws and then hops inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef is cooking breadcrumbs in a large pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman adds marinated beef meat into a large pan containing smoking hot oil and stir fries the meat using a pair of tongs. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A person cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A chihuahua lying on top of a bed is snarling while wagging its tail simultaneously. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man danced on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle around a parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cook puts some noodles in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A boy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girls jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man chops down a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are acting silly. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A boy is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Men are boxing in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing a knives. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy is doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> One man is erasing a chalkboard while a second man is talking to someone that is not in viewing range. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A man in a red shirt is talking to a man in a white shirt. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is adding a silencer to a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A girl dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A band is singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A cook cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A girl is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is using a knife to slice a loaf of bread into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A cowboy rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing grass. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man draws shapes on a board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is describing the game he is playing on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man doing freestyle on a skate ramp. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman reads a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A boy is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A chef is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping a onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman cooks scrambled eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A papaya is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A person holds a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man emerges from mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A baby panda relaxes on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman chops an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A young man standing on the ground appears to levitate, and another young man runs his hand along the space created below the first man's shoes </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating on a field. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of boys are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A fish is being cleaned and cut into pieces for Chinese cooking. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A chef is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man cleans his gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts chicken wings in a container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is passionately playing a guitar in front of an audience. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man </seg>
<seg id="148"> A young man standing on the ground appears to levitate, and another young man runs his hand along the space created below the first man's shoes </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> a person is making a pie. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man fires a shotgun at a target. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby hugs a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man gave a speech from a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man slices bread. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man grabs a live rat out of a snake's cage. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing is kicking a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is cruising through water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person slices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man adds a plate full of grated cheese to a pan is which tomato puree is being cooked. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man cuts a potato into sections. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The cats are playing with each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deer are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is whisking two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is boiling peppers. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model car is hit by a model train. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The rock star performed with his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane lifts off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A commander is inspecting his men. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Two boys are talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A boy does a flip into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man checks his e-mail. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man holding a skull in his hands is moving its jaws while he does the talking. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A papaya is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A food is chopped up. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A view of a band playing through what appears to be a hole in a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band plays onstage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A black and white colored cat is snuggling itself against a baby's face. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping a onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A baby panda relaxes on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl and discards the shell. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person is slicing a garlic into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man and a woman are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is hogging noodles and ice cream. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezes and startles another baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> a woman is slicing a vegetable </seg>
<seg id="200"> A lady mixed meat and spices together. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman boils two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is whisking two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a trunk with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> An orangutan is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Toys are floating in blood red water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A girl is hugging a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> The woman is dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is shown chopping several potatoes into small pieces using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is shown chopping several potatoes into small pieces using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A tomato is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling on its back under a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A person slices ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A person is cleaning a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A chef is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing the meat for the dish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman climbs down a vine and kneels by a cage. </seg>
<seg id="226"> The woman is dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A potato is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A baby guinea pig is nibbling on a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A girl is making eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is applying makeup to her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man crosses a fallen tree trunk, as he is treading on dried leaves in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman slices some kind of seafood in chunks. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A woman slices a fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A man creases a yellow colored square sheet of paper by folding it diagonally at all sides and then opens it out. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref2">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> People exercise togther. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A midget wrestler is thrown in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting near cows. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is applying butter to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting a volleyball on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A kid is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A guy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is counting days by looking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is painting her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is shooting a gun multiple times. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man fires an empty revolver. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is mixing a pot of chili. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a tree. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse and rider are falling to the ground. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a bike on the road. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman and man are driving in a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is seasoning a steak. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up behind some men. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A doberman pinscher is chewing on a stuffed animal toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A slow loris is being tickled. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man popped a wheelie on his motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person mixes a bowl of vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a drum set. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man fires an empty revolver. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing on some kind of machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is dipping fish into batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a key-board by one hand. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is preparing garlic bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is pacing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman holds a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is cleaning a green-board and other man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are flipping large tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A bicyclist is performing tricks in a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man puts a knife into a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A male is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A person is cooking beef on a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="52"> An animal is suspended in air by holding onto two cords with it's hands and feet. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby climbs down from a sofa to the floor. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A women is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is sprinkling spices onto sausages in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting foods in a box. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is checking his email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone is putting raw ground meat into a wok. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing a guitar on a stage outside. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman whisks two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and a woman ride a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a bull machine. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing a violin on the roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A lady is washing a little hedgehog in the sink. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is dieing in an operating room. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A teenage boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man slices rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimp is doing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman pours some oil in a skillet, then some seasoning, and then some diced vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat climbs into a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef is preparing some food. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is cooking meat in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cracking an egg into a small dish. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog is wagging its tail on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle on the road. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A person is boiling noodles. </seg>
<seg id="94"> People sing and play instruments. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is coming up on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man cut a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing in a room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A guy is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The boxers fought in the ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knifes at tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is cleaning a green-board and other man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The boy confronted his dad. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking  with style. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing a guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man cuts a potato at both ends and thereafter slices it into thick strips. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A girl is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A guy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man cutting grass by the machine. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing a diagram on a white board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is looking at a picture on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A boy is showing skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A boy is playing flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person cuts a tomato into many pieces. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is scrambling eggs in a skillet using chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A person is carving the skin off a papaya fruit. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking  with style. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man's head rises out of a pile of mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing an eggplant into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man appears to float off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men are playing football by the beachside. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man chops the head of a snake, dips the body immediately in a bucket of water, cuts and peels the skin off. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A chef sliced up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man dressed in fatigues is loading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting foods in a box. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is paying guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man hammers a concrete slab on top of a man. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man appears to float off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> very look like beautiful </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is firing a shot gun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is hugging a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man gave a speech from the lectern. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a hamburger bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man holds a white rat close to his face after touching it to a snake's body in a glass enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with a ball in a office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is going through water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is adding something to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is pacing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The cats fought each other from two stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deer cross the road in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is stirring two eggs in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A person is boiling chile peppers. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model train crashes into a model car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An airplane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting near cows. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A teenage boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A Drill Sargent addresses his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is sitting in a swivel chair talking on a cordless telephone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A guy is doing a double back flip off the diving board into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is checking his email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man holding a skull is talking while manipulating the skull to look like it is talking. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A person is carving the skin off a papaya fruit. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cook cuts up some cauliflower. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A silhouette of a band playing is shown. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is playing on stage under blue lights when slowly the lights change to bright white. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A black-and-white-cat is snuggling heads with a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A chef slices a garlic clove. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman and man are driving in a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is stuffing food in his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two babies are sitting side by side in infant seats. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A women is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A lady mixed up a meat mixture in bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman boils two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is stirring two eggs in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping wood. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is stretching. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A woman is dead in a bathtub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman holds a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A girl is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is cutting up mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is cutting up mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman cuts a tomato into slices. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling under a piece of furniture on it's back. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is speaking into a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping the edge of a bowl off. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person cuts a tomato into many pieces. </seg>
<seg id="223"> chopping something </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A girl is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A potato is peeled. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig chews on food. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A makeup pencil is being applied to a female's eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is crossing a tree in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A jockey rides a horse around an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A woman is slicing fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is pacing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person folds a piece of paper several times. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref3">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> The people exercised to a video. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman bends over and picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A wrestler throws a man across the floor. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is in a cattle pen with some other men and he's hitting the other men with a wooden club. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is buttering a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting volleyballs over a net. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A kid playing a synthesizer. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man gallops on a horse across the desert. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope that is suspended from what looks like the ceiling of a warehouse. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingernails on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is applying lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man holding a revolver in front of him, turns it four times and then puts it down. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring a pot of chili with a spoon. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a fallen branch out of a pathway in a wooded area. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse and the person riding it fall down on the ground and then stand up after a while. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motor-cycle in the street. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman and man are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is coating a piece of pork with a flour mixture. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog chews his toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is petting a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man pops wheelies on his motor scooter. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone is stirring a pan full of chopped vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man holding a revolver in front of him, turns it four times and then puts it down. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing hanging upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is tying in the machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is dipping a piece of fish into some batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is putting garlic on some bread slices. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is carrying a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man with a bow and a quiver of arrows is riding a horse near a small body of water. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man erases a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a paper by scissor. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are moving tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A biker is performing stunts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is clamping the blade of a knife in a vise. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman sautes some beef. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A loris is swinging. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A young girl puts a small child into a metal trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is crawling off a bed. </seg>
<seg id="55"> chopping vegetables </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man seasons meat in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts chicken wings into tupperware. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is staring straight ahead and rubbing his hand over his chin and then the scene switches to a personal ad in some kind of paper or magazine. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is cooking beef. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is firing a shotgun and you can see the blast from the end of the barrel. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing a violin like a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is assembling a Silencerco 22 Sparrow gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is swimming underwater near the floor of a body of water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking arm in arm through a wooded area. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is beating two eggs in a bowl using a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding a motorbike. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and a woman are walking in the garden. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is on a roof dancing. </seg>
<seg id="74"> Someone is washing a small rodent looking animal in an aluminum pan. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is slipping at the sea-shore in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is injured and bleeding on a stretcher. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimpanzee and a man are practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is adding oil and paste into the pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat has opened a drawer and entered inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef prepared a meal. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is putting beef into a hot wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracked a egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog is wagging its tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing hanging upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A person is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="94"> The two officers danced and sang in front of the band. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> An old lady is adding an egg into the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping a tree down. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing with music. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing a drum set. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The men are in a boxing match with barehands. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a target. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A guy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man erases a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The man talked to the young man. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running through an open gate that leads to the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down the road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is assembling a Silencerco 22 Sparrow gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is chopping a potato. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A lady did exercises on a mat. </seg>
<seg id="119"> Bread is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man gallops on a horse across the desert. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing his lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing a diagram on the board and explaining it. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing a computer game. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is firing a shotgun and you can see the blast from the end of the barrel. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man does tricks on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A girl is reading a book in the wood. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person cuts up tomatos. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down a road and then the scene switches and he's doing push-ups in front of a woman. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is frying some eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A person peels an orange object. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is mincing a clove of garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is catching a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down the road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is coming out into the water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is sleeping on woods. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A chef is chopping a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is finding something on the road. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men play soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is cleaning a snake. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man cuts an onion into thin slivers with a cleaver. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts chicken wings into tupperware. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man breaks cinder blocks on another man. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man is finding something on the road. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man severs the toe of an empty leather boot using a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A cake is being decorated with strawberries. </seg>
<seg id="151"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is firing a shotgun at targets. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is hugging a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is delivering a lecture at an event celebrating the game of cricket. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is splitting a bread roll in half with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is dangling a live mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with a hackey sack in a work office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is moving across water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A chef is slicing into an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is putting cheese into a pan with sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The two cats fought with each other from their stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deers are crossing road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is mixing eggs in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Someone is cooking okra in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model train hits a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An animated passenger jet is taking off from the runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is in a cattle pen with some other men and he's hitting the other men with a wooden club. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is inspecting a barracks. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A boy is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man does a back flip from a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is staring straight ahead and rubbing his hand over his chin and then the scene switches to a personal ad in some kind of paper or magazine. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is mimicking with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracked a egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A person peels an orange object. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cook is chopping a mushroom. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man severs the toe of an empty leather boot using a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> There are several views of a silhouette of group playing music. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is nuzzling a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is sleeping on woods. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl and puts it in the stand mixer. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is slicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman and man are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating noodles and ice creams. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby is sneezing and other baby is afraid. </seg>
<seg id="199"> chopping vegetables </seg>
<seg id="200"> A person is mixing a batch of beef in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling egg. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is mixing eggs in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting wood with axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing exercise. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A primate rides a little pink bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A girl with black lipstick on is laying in a tub filled with red liquid and a toy shark. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is carrying a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="210"> Mushrooms are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="211"> Mushrooms are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman cuts a tomato into two and thereafter slices one half of it. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling under a sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="215"> Someone is slicing a ginger root into very thin pieces. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is cleaning a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing with an orange ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person cuts up tomatos. </seg>
<seg id="223"> Fish is being sliced for a fancy dish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is hanging on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A Guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying a dark brown shade on the outer edge of her eyelid, using a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is powdering her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is stepping over a log in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man in a legionnaire uniform is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is jumping on a jumper. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is slicing octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> One girl is knitting while another girl is talking to her. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is cutting a red piece of meat into thin strips. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person folds a yellow piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref4">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> The women are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is picking a water-pot. </seg>
<seg id="3"> Men are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is greasing a sheet pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting volleyballs provided by another woman. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl plays with her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding her horse in training in a riding ring. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a musical keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man in cowboy gear rides a horse in a circle. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing by a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A teenage girl is putting on lip gloss. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is firing with an assault rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is aiming a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is stirring a food with spoon. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man pushes a large tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse drops its rider. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle through a town. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman drives ""The Arnold"" down the street in a convertible. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is putting flour on a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car exploded. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog chews on a stuffed whale toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person is petting a baby sloth. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A moped driver pops a wheely in the street. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person is stirring salad. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is aiming a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is typing keys. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is putting fish into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is seasoning bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a mobile. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is cradling a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing something from a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are rolling big tyre. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A guy is riding a bike on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a hunting knife in a vise. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Meat is being cooked. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A sloth is hanging from some string. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman is putting a small baby in a water pip. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is playing while wearing a diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> SOMEONE SLICING VEGETABLE </seg>
<seg id="56"> A person is adding cumin seeds in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting chicken wings into a plastic storage container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading a message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone dumps a bowl of meat into a skillet and starts cooking it. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is fitting silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle and fishes are swimming under the water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is whisking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding a motorcycle down the street. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A couple are walking through a forest. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing the violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> Someone is cleaning a animal. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is relaxing on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A patient is lying in the operating room. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A BOY IS CUTTING A GRASS BY SCISSOR. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man sliced a robe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is fighting with a man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A chef is sauteing garlic and onions in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is climbing into a storage box. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef sautes food in a large pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman pours meat into a hot wok and mixes it around. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone cracked to eggs into a bowl </seg>
<seg id="88"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog is wagging its tail. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A woman is boiling noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> The women are singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A small child is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is jumping to a car top. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing drums </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The men boxed in the ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man is doing back flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing something from a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The men are having a conversation. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman are running toward the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is fitting silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing and signing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing the electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman does exercises on a floor mat. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A chef is slicing a bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man in cowboy gear rides a horse in a circle. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing a polygon with an X inside it. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing a video game on a laptop computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is doing some skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman reads a book on a rock. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is cutting a tomato into chunks. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping garlic with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding an amphibian. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man rises from a swamp. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is lounging around. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing a eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> Two kids are doing a magic trick. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group plays soccer at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is cutting a snack. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man cuts an onion with a butcher's knife. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a rifle with bullets. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting chicken wings into a plastic storage container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A brick is being broken on a mans body. </seg>
<seg id="148"> Two kids are doing a magic trick. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a shoe. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A cake is decorated with slices of strawberry. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is firing a shotgun down a range. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is hugging a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is delivering a speech on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is dangling a mouse near a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is tossing a ball with his feet. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is moving in the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is scooping pasta from a plate into a pan of sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of caribou are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman beats two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is boiling finger in the water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model train is riding on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A BOY IS CUTTING A GRASS BY SCISSOR. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is speaking to soldiers standing in attention. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Two men are speaking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man does a backflip off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading a message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a human skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person dices a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a shoe. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is singing on a foggy stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing against a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A group of people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is lounging around. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is chopping up garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman drives ""The Arnold"" down the street in a convertible. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating various foods. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two babies are sitting in high chairs. </seg>
<seg id="199"> SOMEONE SLICING VEGETABLE </seg>
<seg id="200"> A person is mixing a meaty mixture in a glass bowl with a wooden spoon. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs in a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman beats two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping a tree trunk with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy fish is swimming in the water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is cradling a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman cuts a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling under sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A person is slicing a garlic into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> a man is talking on the telephone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man in a library is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man in a chef's hat is cleaning off the edge of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is cutting a tomato into chunks. </seg>
<seg id="223"> Man chops meat and puts it in a plate. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is climbing down a rope. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying cosmetics to her eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl is applying make-up with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is stepping over a log in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A person is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is riding a horse along a perimeter. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A couple of girls are sitting on a couch crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A person is slicing a meat into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref5">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three individuals do aerobic exercises. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is picking a can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is sliding on his forehead across the floor. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A couple of men are fighting in a corral full of cattle. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person is buttering a tray. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting volleyballs. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl fusses with and brushes her wet hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse along the perimeter of a fenced area. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing the piano with a bass base. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse in the desert. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is applying lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is firing with a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is stirring a pot of chili on a stove. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a branch from a walking path. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse is falling in the sand. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman drives a man in her car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is adding flour to meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind 4 people. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog chews on a tennis shoe. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is petting a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person does wheelies on a motor scooter. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person is stirring together ingredients in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is sitting in a chair playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is firing with a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling of a room. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is putting shrimp into a batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a piano keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is seasoning buttered bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking in phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is holding a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a white horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is wiping off a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man is doing bicycle tricks. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a knife to a machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting a skinny potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is frying something in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A animal is hanging from a string. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is playing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> Woman cuts cucomber very thinly. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A cook seasons some sausage. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting chicken to a box. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading a romantic email message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is frying a meat in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> Someone is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A sea turtle is hunting for fish. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A couple is walking in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is mixing eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding a motorized bicycle through a town. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman is walking together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing a fiddle on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person is washing his pet rat. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying in a chair by a lake. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A wounded man lying on the operation table is moving his legs and hands as doctors are treating him. </seg>
<seg id="79"> Someone is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is practicing martial arts moves with a man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> Someone is putting ingredients into a wok. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a box. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A cook stirs ingredients in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman pours the contents of a bowl into a hot wok and stirs it with a pair of tongs. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A person is adding eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> chopping vegitables </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog on the bed growls as the camera approaches, </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling of a room. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A woman is putting noodles into boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two officers danced on the floor with the band. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A little kid is standing on a couch playing an acoustic guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl appears to be jumping from the ground to the top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is sitting in a chair playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping at a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two boxers fight each other in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Different children jump on different trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is wiping off a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two Indian men have a conversation. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="113"> Actor Surya is walking. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing and singing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A person is slicing potatoes into fries. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman exercise her ab muscles on a floor mat. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a french bread loaf. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse in the desert. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is cutting grass with machine. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing on a digital dry erase board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> Someone is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is doing stunts on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down the road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is making scrambled egg. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is slicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding frog in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="135"> Actor Surya is walking. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is climbing up from mud water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is lying on logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing egg plant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Boys are playing football at the sea-shore. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is cutting a snake to cook. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting an onion into slices. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting chicken to a box. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man is breaking a concrete slab placed over a man's chest. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting through a cowboy boot with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef carefully places straberries on his cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> chopping vegitables </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at a target with a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a doll. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is giving a lecture. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is feeding a mice to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with ball in office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is on water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man pours a plate of shredded cheese into a pot of sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting on stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of deer are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is adding cut green beans to boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy car is hit by a toy train. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An air plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting a potato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A couple of men are fighting in a corral full of cattle. </seg>
<seg id="172"> Someone is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is cutting sweet potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is speaking to some soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A an is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Two guys are talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding away on a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is diving in the swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading a romantic email message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is cutting sweet potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person is chopping garlic cloves. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting through a cowboy boot with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is playing in silhouette. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing onstage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing against a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is sitting in a chair playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Peoples are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is lying on logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is breaking an egg on the side of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person is slicing food with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman drives a man in her car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating food while his stomach grows bigger. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezed and scared another baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> Woman cuts cucomber very thinly. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A raw meat mixture is being stirred in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping a log with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is laying on a mat on the floor doing abdominal exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy fish is moving in water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing on a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is holding a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A person is slicing an onion into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> chopping vegitables </seg>
<seg id="215"> A person is slicing ginger with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting sweet potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is taking on his mobile. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting a potato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A chef is preparing some food. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger plays with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="223"> some one preparing nonveg </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding away on a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman swings down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A person is slicing an onion into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye liner to her eyelid using an eye pencil. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is applying cosmetics to her face with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is stepping over a tree in woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man in a hat is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is bouncing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is cutting something. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Women are stitching. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A person is cutting meat into strips with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a potato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref6">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three kids are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is picking up a water can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man slides across a wrestling ring on his head. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person is greasing a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is practicing volley ball. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is brushing her wet hair in the mirror. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse in an open enclosed ground. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse on an open ground. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is making sound with finger. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A young woman is applying lip gloss to her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is firing an assault rifle into a hill. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is pulling the hammer on a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A ]person is stirring something in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a large tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse stumbles and falls after a jump and the rider is knocked off. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman driving a car is having a conversation with her male passenger. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is flouring a piece of pork. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind a group of guys. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is chewing on a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A woman is stroking a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is doing a wheeling on his bike. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is stirring cooked vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is pulling the hammer on a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling, while a group of spectators are dancing on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is typing. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is placing shrimp in a bowl of sauce. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling seasoning on several split and buttered loaves of bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on the telephone as another man listens. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is wiping a board and speaking to other man. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are tumbling tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man is doing stunts on a bicycle ramp. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a knife into a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is frying some meat. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A slow loris is hanging on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman put a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is rolling around in its diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A chef was slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A person is adding seasonings to a pot that is simmering on a stove. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A person is placing meat in a container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is smiling. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is putting meat in a skillet to cook. </seg>
<seg id="60"> Rhinos are grassing. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is swimming in water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and a woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> Someone is beating some eggs with a whisk. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing en electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding on a motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and a woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing guitar standing on roof top. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person is washing a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is singing along as he strums the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is taking sun bath on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man dances on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors are trying to revive a man. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is demonstrating a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is showing fight stunts. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A person is frying onion. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a draw and climbing into it. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is cooking food in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> Meat is being cooked. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is pouring an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A chef cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A cook is slicing up an onion and green beans. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A puppy is sitting on a bed with a dog. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling, while a group of spectators are dancing on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A woman puts noodles in a pot of hot water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two police women are singing and  dancing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is singing and playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> An old woman is breaking egg. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is jumping on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man dances on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Some teenage girls are dancing for the camera. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man dances on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two fighters are punching each other. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at the tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Kids are doing tricks on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is wiping a board and speaking to other man. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two Indian men have a discussion. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and and woman are running together, holding hands. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a path. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain in a garden. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is singing and playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A person is using a knife to cut a potato into wedges. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is doing exercise in the room. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse on an open ground. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing his backyard. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing on an eraser board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is working on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is riding a skateboard on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> a woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is preparing an egg in a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman dices a small onion. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man holds a small, slimey frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a path. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man rises up from a mud hole. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda rolls around on a stack of logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person with a knife is slicing an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is showing magic. </seg>
<seg id="140"> Rhinos are grassing. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are kicking a ball on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is preparing a snake for cooking. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A person is placing meat in a container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man is breaking a stone slab. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man is showing magic. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a shoe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef covers a cake with strawberries. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A cook is slicing up an onion and green beans. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at some targets. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is giving a speech. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing something. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is feeding a mouse to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> In man is doing tricks with a hacky sack in his office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is swimming on the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person dumps a plate of shredded cheese into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of deer are crossing the street. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is boiling some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train comes round the corner, dashes and throws off a red car parked on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing en electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A animated plane is lifting off a runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is walking. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding his bike on the road. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is diving into a swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is smiling. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is pouring an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person is cutting garlic into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a shoe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is playing instruments. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing against baby's face. </seg>
<seg id="190"> a woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing together near a house. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda rolls around on a stack of logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is breaking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person carefully cuts and dices a small onion. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman driving a car is having a conversation with her male passenger. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man eats several different types of food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two baby are sitting. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A chef was slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is mixing meat. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man cuts a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> An orangutan is riding a tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Two electric toys are swimming in red water in a bathtub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman cuts an onion into two and thereafter chops one half of it into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A cook is slicing up an onion and green beans. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing a piece of ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is cleaning the edge of a container of food. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="223"> the man making fish food </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding his bike on the road. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is descending from a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman cuts an onion into two and thereafter chops one half of it into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye liner. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman applies cosmetics to her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man steps over a fallen tree in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing some musical instrument. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is riding their horse in an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is jumping over trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is cutting an octopus tentacle into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A young woman is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A woman is cutting fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a square paper piece. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref7">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A girl is picking up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> Two men are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is attacking another man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person is wiping a pan with butter. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is practicing volleyball serves on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is playing with her hair in the bathroom. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is playing an electric keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at numbers. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman applies lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman fires an assault rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is rolling the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man is stirring the contents of a pan. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a small boat in a river. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a huge tree branch into a clearing. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A man gets knocked off of a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman driving a car is talking to the man seated beside her. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is seasoning a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind four men standing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is eating a doll. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A loris is raising both its arms to be scratched underneath. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is doing some bike stunts. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is stirring some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is rolling the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person is typing on a stenographer. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman batters a piece of seafood. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing an electric keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass of door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling seasonings on bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a mobile phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting some paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men push monstrous tires along the ground. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man jumps his bike on a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a knife in a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting up a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Someone is cooking meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A loris is hanging on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman is putting her baby in a waste bin. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is walking. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A cook prepares a vegetable for a meal by slicing and dicing it. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is adding some spice to a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts chicken pieces in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is rubbing his face, and reading. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A woman is adding something to a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A shotgun is being shot off in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is plucking a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting a silencer onto a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle follows some fish around at the bottom of the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and a woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman is riding on a mo-pad. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man, and a woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing the violin on the top of a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person washes a small porcupine in a pan of water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is resting on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors are trying to save an injured man. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is doing martial arts moves. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is pouring ingredients into a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a drawer and climbing inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is cooking food on a large frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The lady poured a meat mixture into the wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone is cracking a egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A person is slicing up an onion into little pieces. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog is laying on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding an electric bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Noodles are being boiled. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two uniformed female police officers are dancing and singing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A child is playing guitar, and singing. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A small girl jumps from the ground to the roof of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> The girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing the drums under spotlight. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are boxing each other in a boxing bout. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives on a distant wooden board fixed on a tree trunk ahead of him. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Kids doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are having a discussion. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman run down a path. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking along a path through wilderness. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting a silencer onto a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is singing on stage as he strums a guitar too. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A potato is being cut. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is doing exercises on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man slices bread with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing some figures. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man plays a game on his laptop computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A shotgun is being shot off in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is riding on a skateboard ramp. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running on a road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping and slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is mixing yellow and red ingredients in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking along a path through wilderness. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is rising from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A baby panda is laying around. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman cuts up a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man demonstrates his ability to levitate. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are playing soccer on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A person is chopping the head off a snake and taking out its intestines. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting and onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is reloading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts chicken pieces in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man is breaking a concrete slab on a mans belly with a hammer. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man demonstrates his ability to levitate. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man cuts of the toe end of a boot with a machete. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef is decorating a cake with cherry slices. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is slicing up an onion into little pieces. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at targets with a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is shown standing behind a lectern speaking </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is feeding a rat to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with a hackey sack in an office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is traversing some waves. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person with a knife is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is adding rice in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of deer cross a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is mixing ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> okra is cooking in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train crashes into a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An air plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is attacking another man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant talks to his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is chopping a white vegetable with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is making a telephone call. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding his motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is diving off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is rubbing his face, and reading. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person is dicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man cuts of the toe end of a boot with a machete. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is performing. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing out stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing its face on a small child. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping and slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Some people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A baby panda is laying around. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking a egg. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman driving a car is talking to the man seated beside her. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezing scares another baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A cook prepares a vegetable for a meal by slicing and dicing it. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is preparing chicken. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A person is mixing ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping wood. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing some exercise. </seg>
<seg id="205"> An orangutan is riding a tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Toys are swimming in a bath of red liquid. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man sings while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman cuts up a green onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man dices several mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man dices several mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling upside down under the couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A person is slicing up an onion into little pieces. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking in a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man wearing a suit is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A chef wipes off the edge of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="223"> a man is preparing a dish </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding his motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman cuts up a green onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating food. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye makeup. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A young woman is applying makeup. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man walks through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman is riding a horse in an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is pouncing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is slicing octopus with a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A person is cutting a piece of fish into slices. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref8">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A girl picks up a water can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A wrestler throws another wrestler. </seg>
<seg id="4"> People are fighting in a cow pen. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is sitting in a room playing a piano by lamp light. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person spreads lard on a tray. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is smashing a ball in a practice. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is striking a table with her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is pointing at a calender on the wall. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is putting on lip color. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is firing an automatic rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring a pot of stew. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man paddles a canoe across a pond. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A man is falling down when he is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man sliced a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is driving a car while speaking with a man. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman puts flour on a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind four people. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is playing with a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person rubs a small furry animal. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is doing wheelies on a motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone is stirring a pot of stew. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar, and humming. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing some drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person types on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is breading shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning glass doors. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling spices on four sliced half loaves of buttered bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is pacing in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man talks on a cellphone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man riding a horse is looking around a forest. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalkboard with an eraser. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man on a bicycle jumps high in the air while riding on a metallic sheet curved at both ends. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man trys to break a knife blade. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is frying meet. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A furry animal hangs on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman is putting a baby into a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby plays on furniture. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A cucumber being cut into fine strips. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is seasoning some meat. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting chicken in a dish. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading his email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is sauteing meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A person is firring a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is standing in front of a microphone holding a violin in one hand and a violin bow in the other. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle walks on the bottom of the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking together through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> Someone is beating eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is rocking and playing the guitar on stage. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is dancing . </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A couple are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A young man is standing on a roof, playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A hedgehog is getting a bath. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man sings and plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man lounges on a chair at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors resuscitate a man. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A young man is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cuts a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimpanzee is doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman puts oil and food in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is cooking. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The lady poured the meat mixture into a wok and stirred. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman chops an onion into fine pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog lays on a bed and wags his tail. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding an electric bike on a concrete ground. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing the guitar on a park bench. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Noodles are being mixed. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are dancing and singing in front of a crowd. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is pouring eggs into a dish. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is jumping onto a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar, and humming. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> The girls danced around the room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are boxing in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man throws blades at a target on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> People are jumping on trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalkboard with an eraser. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are speaking each other. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man, and a woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man walks along a trail. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man playing an electric guitar is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A potato is being sliced into many pieces. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man mows a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is writing on a  school board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man plays a video game on a laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A person is firring a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is skateboarding on a ramp. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A girl is reading a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A tomato is sliced into smaller pieces. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down a road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman cooks eggs in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling the skin of a ripe papaya using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping onion. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A woman is handling a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man walks along a trail. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man rises up out of a swamp. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is cutting vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is levitating. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A snake is killed and skinned. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man loads a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting chicken in a dish. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="147"> One man is breaking cement on another man's chest. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man is levitating. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef is decorating a cake with strawberries. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman chops an onion into fine pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at targets. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a stuffed toy. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is speaking at a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is splitting a piece of bread. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is holding a white rat by it's tale over an aquarium containing a large snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man plays hackysack in an office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat sails along the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is adding shredded cheese to a pot. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man sliced a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is pacing in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are pawing at each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Animals are crossing the road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman stirs eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Someone is boiling some peppers. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train hit a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is rocking and playing the guitar on stage. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A computerized plane is taking off a runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting potatoes into small cubes. </seg>
<seg id="171"> People are fighting in a cow pen. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A young man is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A man is talking to a group of soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is having a conversation on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding off in a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is doing a back flip into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading his email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with man's skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling the skin of a ripe papaya using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A woman finely chops a few garlic pods using a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> People are playing instruments. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is playing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing it's head against a young child. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar, and humming. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Teenagers are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> Someone is slicing something </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman is driving a car while speaking with a man. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is stuffing various food items into his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby is surprising another baby with a sneeze. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A cucumber being cut into fine strips. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is stirring a marinade mixture into some beef. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling to eggs in a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman stirs eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a tree trunk using an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing crunches. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy shark swims in a bathtub full of red water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is cutting mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is cutting mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is playing underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman chops an onion into fine pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting potatoes into small cubes. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man speaks while standing in front of a bookcase. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A tomato is sliced into smaller pieces. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A chef was slicing raw fish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding off in a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is descending on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye makeup. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is applying some bronzing powder to the outer areas of her cheek and temple using a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A person is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman is riding a horse in an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman with a knife is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Two girls are knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is cutting some meat. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is pacing in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting potatoes into small cubes. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref9">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is holding a water can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> Men are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy plays a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person wipes butter on a tray. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is tossing and hitting volleyballs on the beach, while another woman standing nearby is passing the balls. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A small girl standing in front of the bathroom mirror is straightening her hair using her fingers and then combs it with a hair brush. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> An individual's right hand plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing on his keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A girl taps her fingernails on the counter. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is pointing at days on a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A girl is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman standing on grassland is holding a rifle and shooting a series of bullets in the air. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is shooting a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring soup. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A man is falling from horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man slices a peeled potato into thick slices and thereafter cuts each of them into half. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is putting flour onto some meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car is blasting. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is playing with its stuffed toy whale. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is petting a monkey. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is performing tricks on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone is stirring a pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is shooting a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is using a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is battering food to deep fry. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning the windows of two glass doors, using a couple of squegees. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling spices over buttered bread slices. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man rides a horse through a river bed. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A guy cuts paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are moving tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man on a bike performs jumps on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is clamping a knife into a vise. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is cooking meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A monkey is hanging from some string. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A girl is putting a baby in a garbage can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby wearing only a diaper is walking and playing around actively in the house. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A lady is taking the top and bottom off a cucumber, then chops it length-wise into long thin pieces. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is putting seasonings in a pot of sausage. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts wings into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Someone is reading an email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is frying meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A guy is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man played an instrument and sang into a microphone on stage. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man modifies the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and a woman walk through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A person is whisking eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man jams on his electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is riding a motorcycle with a woman passenger. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> Two people are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing a fiddle on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> An animal is being bathed. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying on a lounge. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors tend to an injured man lying on a gurney. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A teenager cuts a clump of grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cuts a thick rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is frying onions. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is toasting nuts in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The woman is cooking meat in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> a woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A person breaks an egg into a small bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog lies on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding on a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing the guitar seated on a bench in an outdoor location. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Noodles are cooking in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are dancing and singing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A kid is singing. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding on a bike with his luggage. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a very large tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three girls are dancing in the room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are boxing on the rope-stage. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man throws knives at a target hanging on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> People do flips on trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are speaking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running outside. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man modifies the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Jimi Hendrix is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A potato is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is exercising her abs. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a whole bread loaf using a bread knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A guy is mowing the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A person is drawing on a large touchscreen. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man using a laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A guy is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is skateboarding. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A girl is reading a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is cutting a tomato into small chunks. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is dicing an onion using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is slicing a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is mincing some garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is emerging from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man appears to levitate off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A snake is prepared to be eaten. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man loads a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts wings into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man breaks a stone. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man appears to levitate off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a boot in half with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef is placing strawberries on top of a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting shotgun slugs across a hill. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a toy beaver. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is speaking at a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is showing a rat to snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is kicking around a foot bag. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man stands on the deck of a ship. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Someone dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is pouring cheese into a pot of red sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man slices a peeled potato into thick slices and thereafter cuts each of them into half. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are playing while sitting on stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> dears are passing the road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is scrambling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is adding vegetables to a pot. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train is hitting a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man jams on his electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane takes off of a runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A teenager cuts a clump of grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is talking on a cell phone while sitting in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is doing a backwards double-flip off a diving board and into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> Someone is reading an email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is providing voice to a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> a woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is slicing a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A woman is chopping up garlic. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a boot in half with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band performs in silhouette. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is snuggling a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is dicing an onion using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is chopping garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man stuffing his face with food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezes. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A lady is taking the top and bottom off a cucumber, then chops it length-wise into long thin pieces. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is stirring meat in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling two eggs in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is scrambling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man chopping a tree. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy fish is swimming. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing a song while simultaneously strumming his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is rapidly chopping some mushrooms using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is rapidly chopping some mushrooms using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is pulling itself under a sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping food from a bowls rim. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is cutting a tomato into small chunks. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A cook is slicing fish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is climbing down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman pealing a potato </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guineapig eats a piece of carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye make-up. </seg>
<seg id="230"> a indian girl puffing power on here </seg>
<seg id="231"> The man is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing the harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman cuts up a piece of octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Two women are crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is cutting raw fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref10">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> The lady picked up the watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man throws another man across the ring. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> An individual greases a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman serving volleyballs over a net. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A young girl is playing with her wet hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A young woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> Someone is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A girl is drumming her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is pointing at numbers on a chart, then turns around and says something. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is applying makeup. </seg>
<seg id="17"> a woman taking pices on the farm </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is trying to shoot a bullet. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is stirring some chili. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat on water using an oar. </seg>
<seg id="21"> Someone is moving a tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A person falls off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding his motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is driving with a man. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is breading meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car is blowing up behind four men. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is playing with some kind of dog chew toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is scratching an animals belly. </seg>
<seg id="30"> An individual does a wheely, while riding down a road, on a motorized bike. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person is stirring vegetables in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> Someone is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is trying to shoot a bullet. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing upside-down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing. </seg>
<seg id="37"> Someone is breading meat to fry. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning the windows. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling toppings on four half loaves of bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman picks up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man erases writing on a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are flipping over oversized tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A person on a bike rides a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> The man put the knife in the clamp. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is slicing a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="51"> The lady cooked the meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A animal is hanging on a string. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trashcan. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A commercial in Spanish for pampers. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A large knife cuts up cucumbers. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is seasoning food. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man places chicken into a container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading an email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person browns meat in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="60"> Animals are grazing. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a really tall box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> Someone is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man plays a string instrument. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man put a gun barrel together. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle swims. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man, and woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="67"> The lady whisked the eggs and spices in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A person is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is riding a motorcycle with a woman. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A guy plays a fiddle while standing on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person is bathing a hedgehog in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is lying on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing in the street. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors try to revive a patient. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> The man slced through a thick rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is karate kicking a person. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is tossing breadcrumbs in a pan and roasting it using a wooden spatula. </seg>
<seg id="85"> Two woman add ingredients to a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is breaking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman cutting onions. </seg>
<seg id="89"> Dogs are lying on a bed, one is wagging its tail. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing upside-down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is rinding an electric bike. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Pasta is added to a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are dancing together. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A young boy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps up on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding on a motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing in the street. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping the base of a large tree trunk with his axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three girls are dancing in their room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing in the street. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are fighting each other. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man throws knives at a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> People jump on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man erases writing on a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are talking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running down the street. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a pathway lined with greenery. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man put a gun barrel together. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Jimi Hendrix is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> Someone is cutting a raw potato into strips. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is exercising on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="119"> Someone slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A guy is cutting grass. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A teacher drawing a line </seg>
<seg id="123"> Someone is playing a computer game on a laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> Someone is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man moving rapidly on a skateboard goes up a slope, does a couple of summersaults and falls down while landing. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is laying on a blanket. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a wind instrument. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is dicing half an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> Someone is pouring eggs into a pan and scrammbling them. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is using a large knife to peel a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> The lady cup up the vegetable into fine pieces. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a pathway lined with greenery. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man raises up out of muddy water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> The panda rested on the logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> someone is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is levitating. </seg>
<seg id="140"> Animals are grazing. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men play soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> Men are skinning snakes. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man standing on snow is loading bullets into a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man places chicken into a container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man is breaking a concrete block on a person. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man is levitating. </seg>
<seg id="149"> Someone cuts a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef places strawberries atop a dessert. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman cutting onions. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting with a gun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby plays with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is speaking on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a hamburger bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is teasing a snake with a mouse. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man passing a ball back and forth with his feet. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A powerboat is cruising across the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Someone is slicing something. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is putting shredded cheese in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are rough housing. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Deer are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> Someone is beating an egg. </seg>
<seg id="166"> The lady added the pea pods to the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train is striking a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A person is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A jet is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is slicing a potato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> The lady cut the vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A military officer is instructing subordinates. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man chops one half of an onion into small pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man talks on the telephone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is sitting on a stopped motorcycle then he rides off on the motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is jumping off a low diving board and doing a back flip dive. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading an email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> The lady cut the vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is talking through a skull head. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is using a large knife to peel a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A woman is cutting garlic. </seg>
<seg id="185"> Someone cuts a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> Men are playing music. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band performs on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is snuggling with a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is dicing half an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Several people are dancing on the patio. </seg>
<seg id="193"> The panda rested on the logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking an egg open into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is chopping a garlic pod into fine pieces. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman is driving with a man. </seg>
<seg id="197"> The man stuffed his face with food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby scares another baby with a sneeze. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A large knife cuts up cucumbers. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman stirs meat in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> Someone is beating an egg. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man chopped a fallen log. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bicycle around a stage. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Bath toys are swimming. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman picks up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> a person chopping potatoes very fast </seg>
<seg id="211"> a person chopping potatoes very fast </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is sliding underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman cutting onions. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is cutting some ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> The lady cut the vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is slicing a potato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Someone is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A chef is cleaning up a bowl of soup. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A cook slices some fish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is sitting on a stopped motorcycle then he rides off on the motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman climbs down off of a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A Guinna pig is eating. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eyeshadow. </seg>
<seg id="230"> The girl applied powder to her face with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> The man stepped over a fallen tree in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman is seated on a horse as it prances along the periphery of a stadium. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is cutting octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman seated on a sofa is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is slicing meat. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is slicing a potato with a knife. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref11">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are marching. </seg>
<seg id="2"> The woman picked up the watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A wrestler on the floor topples his opponent, who slides on his head and bangs the other end of the ring. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting in a cow pasture. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> Someone is greasing a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> One woman hands volleyballs to another woman who serves them. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A young girl is standing in front of a mirror working on her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> Ladies horseback riding competition . </seg>
<seg id="10"> Someone played the keyboard with his right hand. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man plays a piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A girl is tapping her finger nails on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy points out dates on a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> The woman is applying lip gloss. </seg>
<seg id="17"> The girl shot the semi-automatic rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> The man is aiming a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> The man stirred the chili in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is dragging a tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A rider on a horse goes down with the horse and both get back up apparently unharmed. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A person cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding on motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="25"> Arnold Schwarzenegger and Rae Dawn Chong drive down the street. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A girl is putting flour on meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car is burning. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is playing with toys. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A lemur with outstretched arms is being scratched by a person. </seg>
<seg id="30"> Someone is doing stunts on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> The man stirred the cooked vegetables in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> The man is aiming a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is singing and dancing on a ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is dipping prawns into a batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> a man is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning two glass doors using wet and dry sponge mops along with a piece of cloth. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man seasons some bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around his cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman picks up and holds a baby kangaroo in her arms. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a blackboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> The man cut a piece of paper in half. </seg>
<seg id="47"> In a race held, each of the two men is moving a huge tire by tumbling them repeatedly on a road lined with people. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A rider is doing bicycle stunts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> The man clamped the knife. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man slices a raw potato into two halves using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="51"> The woman is cooking meat in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A loris is swinging from a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A baby is placed into a garbage can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A toddler is walking around with a cartoon worm attached to its diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A person is slicing a zucchini. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A pot of sausage is being seasoned. </seg>
<seg id="57"> The man put the cooked chicken into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="58"> The man read a personals ad. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone is stir frying some meat. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is grazing on some grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a very large cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man fires a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man puts a silencer on a handgun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking under water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A couple are walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> The woman is whisking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A person is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man plays a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man rides with a woman on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding on something. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and a woman are walking together in a garden as a song plays in the background. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is fiddling on a rooftop. </seg>
<seg id="74"> The hedgehog tried to get out of its bath. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is doing some footwork moves on a road in a scenic location as music plays in the background. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Medical personnel are trying to revive a patient. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is trimming grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> The man used a sword to cut the thick rope. </seg>
<seg id="81"> The monkey is doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman adds oil and sautes garlic and onions in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs into it. </seg>
<seg id="84"> The man is cooking on a tv show. </seg>
<seg id="85"> Two women are cooking in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg on a wooden top in the kitchen and puts it into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="89"> The dog is on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is singing and dancing on a ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is shown riding a bicycle with some type of power assist attached to the rear wheel. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is sitting on a bench in front of a microphone playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Someone is cooking noodles. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> The baby played the guitar on the couch. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps from the ground of a lawn on the roof top of a car parked nearby. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man rides a motorcycle across a field. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is doing some footwork moves on a road in a scenic location as music plays in the background. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is cutting a trunk of a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three girls dance and plays. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is sitting at a set of drums playing them. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is doing some footwork moves on a road in a scenic location as music plays in the background. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are fighting in a boxing ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> The man is throwing knives at a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Peoples are jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a blackboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are talking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> The man and woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man walking down a trail. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man puts a silencer on a handgun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Jimi Hendrix plays an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> Someone is slicing a raw potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is exercising on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="119"> The lady sliced a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A teacher is drawing a diagram on the board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> The man is playing a game on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man fires a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man rides his skateboard on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman reclining on a rock amidst greenery is reading a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running on a road lined with trees. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is finely chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman pours raw eggs into a pan and cooks them. </seg>
<seg id="132"> The woman is peeling an orange vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="133"> The woman is dicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A purple frog held by a man in his hands is making noise. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man walking down a trail. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is coming up out of a mud pit. </seg>
<seg id="137"> The panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A guy raises his feet off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is grazing on some grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> People are playing soccer at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> The chef cut off a snake's head and prepared it for cooking. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is slicing one half of a peeled white onion using a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A soldier is putting rounds in a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> The man put the cooked chicken into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> The man chopped the cement block on the man's body. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A guy raises his feet off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a cowboy boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A cook decorating pastry with strawberries. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is target shooting. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby plays with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="155"> The man sliced the bun in half. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is trying to fed a snake a mouse. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A guy is playing hackysack </seg>
<seg id="158"> A ship is moving on a sea. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person puts pasta in some water. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A person cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around his cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are sitting on stools and batting at one another with their front paws. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Different species of dear are roaming in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is scrambling two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> The woman is boiling okra. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train runs into a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A person is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A play takes off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting in a cow pasture. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is trimming grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> The woman is slicing sweet potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A soldier walks through a barracks and talks. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man cuts an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A guy is speaking on the telephone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man rides off on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man jumps off a diving board, does summersaults and dives into the water of a swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> The man read a personals ad. </seg>
<seg id="180"> The woman is slicing sweet potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is talking to a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg on a wooden top in the kitchen and puts it into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> The woman is peeling an orange vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A woman is slicing some tapioca. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a cowboy boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A guy is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is playing onstage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is seated and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat plays with a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is finely chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> The kids danced on the patio. </seg>
<seg id="193"> The panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="194"> An egg is cracked and added to the mix. </seg>
<seg id="195"> The lady chopped up a garlic clove. </seg>
<seg id="196"> Arnold Schwarzenegger and Rae Dawn Chong drive down the street. </seg>
<seg id="197"> The man is eating. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby is sneezing. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A person is slicing a zucchini. </seg>
<seg id="200"> An individual mixes beef, with other ingredients, in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is scrambling two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> The man is using an axe to cut through the tree. </seg>
<seg id="204"> The man demonstrated exercises on the floor mat. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey riding a small bi-cycle is waving his hand round the corner while riding in circles. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Mechanical toys are moving in a bathtub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> The man sang and played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman picks up and holds a baby kangaroo in her arms. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is finely dicing an onion using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man chopped up potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man chopped up potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is sliding underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="215"> The woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> The woman is slicing sweet potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man with glasses is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> The chef is wiping the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with an orange ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is cutting meat. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man rides off on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is finely dicing an onion using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman peels a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guniea pig is eating a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="230"> The woman is applying makeup. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A guy is standing inside the forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> The man played the harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman rides a show horse in a stadium. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dogs is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is slicing octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> The girls sat on a couch and crocheted. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A person is cutting up some meat. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around his cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref12">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are walking in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> The wrestler flipped the other one on his head. </seg>
<seg id="4"> The men are fighting each other. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy seated in a room is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> Someone is greasing a square cookie sheet with shortening. </seg>
<seg id="7"> The girl hit volleyballs over the net. </seg>
<seg id="8"> The little girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> The girl trotted the horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> Someone played the keyboard with his right hand. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man plays the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A girl is tapping her finger nails. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy studies a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> An hispanic girl is applying lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> The woman is shooting a machine gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> The man is stirring the chili in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="20"> The man rowed his boat in the river. </seg>
<seg id="21"> The man moved a large tree branch away. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A woman falls off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A person is chopping a vegetable into thick slices. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man rides a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> The girl drove the convertible on the highway. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is coating a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="27"> Four boys are standing in front of the burning car. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is trying to eat duplicate fish. </seg>
<seg id="29"> The lady scratched the little monkey's armpits! </seg>
<seg id="30"> Someone is riding a motor-scooter on the road and they do a wheelie. </seg>
<seg id="31"> The man is stirring the vegetables in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man seated is playing a set of drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is singing and dancing on the ceiling as other people are dancing on the floor of the room. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is tying on a stenographers machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman dips a shrimp into a bowl containing flour batter and coats it on both sides. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man played the organ. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning windows. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man sprinkles minced garlic from a small bottle on top of four generously buttered elongated slices of bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking within a cage in a zoo. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman picks up and holds a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> Someone is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> The man is using scissors to cut paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two people flipped tractor tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A stunt bike rider. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man shappens a knife. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A person is cutting up a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Thin slices of meat are cooked in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> The animal dangled from the ceiling on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A small child cries bitterly as a woman lifts and dumps him in a dustbin by the roadside and walks away. </seg>
<seg id="54"> The baby climbed off the bed. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A person is slicing squash into thin slices. </seg>
<seg id="56"> The man is seasoning the sausages. </seg>
<seg id="57"> The man is putting chicken into the container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> The man is reading his email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A woman is frying ground meat. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The rhino grazed on the grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into an empty box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The man shot his gun in the air. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man standing at a microphone is holding a violin like a guitar and plucking it. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A person is placing a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> The turtle followed the fish. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A couple is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman beats some eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> Someone is playing an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> The couple are riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is sitting on the back of a toy bull which is swiveling wildly in different directions. </seg>
<seg id="72"> The couple strolled together down the path. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is fiddling on a rooftop. </seg>
<seg id="74"> The hedgehog is getting a bath. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying out at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> The man did a funny dance! </seg>
<seg id="78"> The doctor was helping the patient. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with a pair of scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man uses a huge knife to cut some rope. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimpanzee is performing karate kicks. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman adds chopped garlic to a skillet containing oil and thereafter adds some chopped onions and stir fries it. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat opens the drawer of a storage box and squeezes into it. </seg>
<seg id="84"> The man is frying bread crumbs in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> Two women are cooking some meat. </seg>
<seg id="86"> The lady cracked the egg in to the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone is cracking an egg open. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="89"> The dog is wagging his tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is singing and dancing on the ceiling as other people are dancing on the floor of the room. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man rides a bicycle in a parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is sitting on a bench playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Someone is sitring noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> The little boy is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking open eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> The girl jumped on top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man rode his motorcycle on the dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> The man did a funny dance! </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is cutting down a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three girls dance around. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man played his drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> The man did a funny dance! </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="107"> The man threw knives at a target. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Several groups of children are shown doing flips on trampolines </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are talking. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A couple are running towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> The man walked down the dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A person is placing a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Jimi Hendrix plays the guitar and sings into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="117"> The cook is slicing a potato into french fries. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> The cook is slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> The man is drawing on the board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A guy named Mike on holiday playing a video game. </seg>
<seg id="124"> The man shot his gun in the air. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man skateboards on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="126"> The lady lay down on the ground and read a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="129"> The man ran down the road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> The lady scrambled eggs in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="132"> The woman is peeling the skin off a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is dicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> The man picked up the frog in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="135"> The man walked down the dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> The man emerged from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda lounges on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> The lady cut the eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man elevates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> The rhino grazed on the grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> People are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> The chef killed the snake and shed it's skin. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A onion is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="144"> Someone in a camouflage outfit is loading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> The man is putting chicken into the container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> The man is using a sledghammer to break the concrete block that is on the other man. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man elevates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> The man cut through the boot with a large sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lady chef is decorating a sponge cake with whipped cream and strawberries </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby plays with its toy. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man makes a speech. </seg>
<seg id="155"> The man is slicing thin bread. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man picks up a mouse from a case holding a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing hacky sack in the office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A yacht is moving across the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> The lady sliced the onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A woman is putting cheese into some sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A person is chopping a vegetable into thick slices. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking within a cage in a zoo. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats bat at each other from opposite stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Many deer cross a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> The lady stirred two raw eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is boiling okra. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train runs over a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> Someone is playing an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> The men are fighting each other. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with a pair of scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman cuts up vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="174"> An army drill sergeant inspects his nervous troop. </seg>
<seg id="175"> Someone sliced an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A guy is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man starts a viper bike and rides off on the road ahead. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man jumps off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> The man is reading his email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman cuts up vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man manipulates a mask to make funny faces. </seg>
<seg id="182"> The lady cracked the egg in to the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> The woman is peeling the skin off a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Garlic is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="185"> The man cut through the boot with a large sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is playing. </seg>
<seg id="187"> Musicians are performing music. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat rubs its head against a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> The people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda lounges on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> Egg is cracked into a mixture and blended. </seg>
<seg id="195"> The woman is dicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> The girl drove the convertible on the highway. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is stuffing himself full with food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Kids are sitting in a bumba. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A person is slicing squash into thin slices. </seg>
<seg id="200"> Food is stired in bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> The lady stirred two raw eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping a tree. </seg>
<seg id="204"> The man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> The chimpanzee rode a tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Toys are in a tub of water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A guy plays guitar and sings. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman picks up and holds a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> The person is slicing mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="211"> The person is slicing mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is sliding upside down under a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is thinly slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman cuts up vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="217"> The man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> The man spoke in front of the bookshelves. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is cleaning the edges of a full bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with an orange colored ball on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is cutting meet to make some pieces. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man starts a viper bike and rides off on the road ahead. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman with a weird hairdo comes down a creeper and lands on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> An elderly woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A hamster is eating a piece of carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is using an eyebrow pencil to color her eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl is applying makeup on her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> very nice and green trees in the forest </seg>
<seg id="232"> The man is playing the harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> The horse and rider performed in a competition. </seg>
<seg id="234"> The dog played on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is slicing up some octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> The woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> The lady cut sliced the meat. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking within a cage in a zoo. </seg>
<seg id="239"> Someone folded a square yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref13">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people exercise. </seg>
<seg id="2"> The lady picked up the watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> The men are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting in a corral. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A kid is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> Someone is putting butter on a baking pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> The women are playing beach volleyball. </seg>
<seg id="8"> The little girl is putting her hair into a pony tail. </seg>
<seg id="9"> The horse and rider trotted by the fence. </seg>
<seg id="10"> The keyboards are being played. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man plays the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingernails on the counter. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A kid is pointing out days on a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman puts on lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl shots a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person stirs some vegetables and sauce. </seg>
<seg id="20"> The man is paddling in a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> The man is carrying a branch of leaves. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A woman falls off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A person is chopping up potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man rides his motorcycle through the city streets. </seg>
<seg id="25"> The lady drove the convertible on the street. </seg>
<seg id="26"> The lady floured the meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> Four men are standing in the woods as an explosion sound is heard and the white car behind them is burning. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog playing with a toy </seg>
<seg id="29"> The animal is being scratched under the arms. </seg>
<seg id="30"> Someone is riding a wheelie on a motor scooter. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man stirs some stir fry. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> The drummer played his drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A singer dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> The lady typed on the stenograph. </seg>
<seg id="37"> The lady battered the shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is washing the door glass of a business. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man sprinkles seasoning on a piece of bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> The tiger roamed around its cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking over the phone standing in a restaurant kitchen. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman picks up her pet baby kangaroo and cuddles it. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse by a creek. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting paper into two equal strips. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men each flip a huge tire down the pavement. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A stunt biker does jumps on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> The man put a steel rod in a clench. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A potato is being cut into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman puts some meat into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="52"> The animal is hanging on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> The girl put the baby into the trashcan. </seg>
<seg id="54"> The baby rolled around the room in his diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is choppping the cucumber with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A cook seasons some meat. </seg>
<seg id="57"> Food is put into a container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading an email message. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A woman adds some meat to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The rhinocerous is grazing. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps up into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man strums a violin on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="64"> Someone is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> The turtle is walking under water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> Two people are walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> The lady whisked the eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> someone is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> The couple are riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man rides a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> The man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing a violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> An animal is washed. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man seated is singing a song and strumming a guitar too. </seg>
<seg id="76"> The tide came in where the man was lounging in the sand. </seg>
<seg id="77"> The man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> The emergency personnel tried to save the man on the gurney. </seg>
<seg id="79"> Someone is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> The man chopped through the hanging rope with a large sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey pratices martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman fries chopped garlic in a skillet and then adds chopped onions. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat pulls a plastic drawer out. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is sitting on the bench </seg>
<seg id="85"> Two women are preparing a meaty meal. </seg>
<seg id="86"> The woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cracking open eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is chopping an onion and frozen green beans. </seg>
<seg id="89"> The dog wagged his tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A singer dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> The man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Someone stirred the noodles into the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A little kid plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> The lady cracked the eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> The little girl jumped on the car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man speeding on a bike on a muddy road suddenly comes to a halt. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> The man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is cutting woods. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three teenage girls dance in a room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man plays the drum. </seg>
<seg id="105"> The man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="107"> The person three knives a target on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Several kids are doing tricks on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are talking. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman run toward the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man walks down a dirt path. </seg>
<seg id="114"> Someone is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="116"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> cutting potatoes </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> Bread is sliced. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> The man mowed his grass with a mower. </seg>
<seg id="122"> The man is drawing on the board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing a game on his computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> The man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A skateboarder does tricks on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="126"> The woman is relaxing in the woods reading a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is cutting a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="129"> The man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> The cook is scrambling eggs in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="132"> person preparing something </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman cuts potatos into tiny pieces. </seg>
<seg id="134"> The man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man walks down a dirt path. </seg>
<seg id="136"> The man came out from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> The panda bear lay on the logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman cuts up a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man shows a trick by passing his hand underneath the feet of another man who lifts about a foot above the ground and comes back. </seg>
<seg id="140"> The rhinocerous is grazing. </seg>
<seg id="141"> People are playing soccer on the shore. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man prepared a snake for cooking. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Half an onion is sliced into wedges. </seg>
<seg id="144"> Someone is loading a gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> Food is put into a container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> The man enjoyed playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man breaks a board. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man shows a trick by passing his hand underneath the feet of another man who lifts about a foot above the ground and comes back. </seg>
<seg id="149"> The man used a sword to slice a boot. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lady is garnishing. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is chopping an onion and frozen green beans. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A kid is playing with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man speaks at a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man cuts up a hamburger bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man tries to feed a mouse to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is tossing a ball with his legs and head while in office, as a phone rings in the background. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A yacht is moving through the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> The person is slicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Grated cheese is added to the sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A person is chopping up potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="162"> The tiger roamed around its cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats fight while sitting on stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Moose are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> The woman is whisking the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman dumps vegetables into boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train strikes a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> someone is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> The jet lifted off the runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting in a corral. </seg>
<seg id="172"> Someone is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> The lady cut a vegetable and a cantaloupe. </seg>
<seg id="174"> An army sergeant is walking and talking to a line of soldiers standing next to their beds in their camp room. </seg>
<seg id="175"> An incividual cuts up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man answers a telephone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> The man is riding the motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> Men do flips from diving boards into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading an email message. </seg>
<seg id="180"> The lady cut a vegetable and a cantaloupe. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man provides the voice for a human skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> The woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> person preparing something </seg>
<seg id="184"> Someone chopped up a turnip. </seg>
<seg id="185"> The man used a sword to slice a boot. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is performing in a videoclip. </seg>
<seg id="187"> People are singing. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat rubs up against a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Many people dance in front of a house. </seg>
<seg id="193"> The panda bear lay on the logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> The lady cracked an egg for the mixer. </seg>
<seg id="195"> Food is cut into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="196"> The lady drove the convertible on the street. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is shoving food into his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two babies are sitting in baby seats. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is choppping the cucumber with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="200"> Meat is being mixed in a bowl with sauce. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman places two eggs into a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> The woman is whisking the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man chopped a log. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> The monkey is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Plastic toys are floating in water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman picks up her pet baby kangaroo and cuddles it. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A row of mushrooms is cut into slices. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A row of mushrooms is cut into slices. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat lying on its back on the floor beneath a sofa is moving ahead by pushing his paws against the underside of the sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is chopping an onion and frozen green beans. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A person cuts ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> The lady cut a vegetable and a cantaloupe. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a mobile phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> The man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A chef cleans the side of a bowl of vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub plays with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is cutting a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is preparing a sushi plate. </seg>
<seg id="224"> The man is riding the motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> The lady came down the tree on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> An old lady is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A hamster or guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman puts cosmetics on her eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl applied foundation to her face with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> taking man's shirt in a forest by researcher </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is make believe playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> The horse and rider trotted around the ring. </seg>
<seg id="234"> The dog is jumping on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman dices a boiled octopus into 1/2 inch pieces using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A girl knits. </seg>
<seg id="237"> The woman is slicing raw fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> The tiger roamed around its cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> Someone is folding a piece of paper into the shape of a triangle. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man slices a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref14">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people exercised to a video. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is holding a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A wrestler flips another wrestler over. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two martial artists fight it out. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A kid is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> The lady greased a baking pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> Woman hitting volleyballs. </seg>
<seg id="8"> The little girl wrung out her wet hair and used a brush. </seg>
<seg id="9"> The woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> The man is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="11"> The man is playing the keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> the man shimmied up the rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> The girl drummed her fingers on the tabletop. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is looking at numbers on a chart. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman applies cosmetics. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is shooting an automatic rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man shoots a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone stirred the ot of chili. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is dragging a tree. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A woman falls off of a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A person is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man rode a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> The woman is driving the car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> The woman is breading the pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="27"> Four young men are walking away from a car when it explodes </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog plays with a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is scratching a lemur under the armpits. </seg>
<seg id="30"> Te man did a wheelie on his motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> The man stirred the vegetables in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> The man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man shoots a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> Lionel Richie is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> The man is using a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> The woman is dipping shrimp into the batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man plays a piano. </seg>
<seg id="39"> Man washing and cleaning door windows </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man sprinkles seasoning on slices of bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> The tiger is walking. </seg>
<seg id="42"> The man talked on the telephone in the pizza kitchen. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman plays with a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man sitting on the back of a white horse is waiting on a river bank and looking around. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing the chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man cuts some paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> The men are moving the huge tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Someone is doing stunts on a bike. </seg>
<seg id="49"> the men is preparing the item </seg>
<seg id="50"> A potato is cut into half lengthwise and then sliced into a quarter. </seg>
<seg id="51"> The lady cooked the fish in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A slow lori hangs on some wires. </seg>
<seg id="53"> The baby was put into the trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> The baby was very active in the house. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is cutting a squash in small strips. </seg>
<seg id="56"> The man seasoned the sausages in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts some chicken in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man reads his email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> The woman is browning pork in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is grazing in a field. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A pet grey cat sitting next to a carton box kept open from the top, jumps high and leaps into the box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A gun fires a blast. </seg>
<seg id="63"> Holding a fiddle in his right hand, a man is playing the violin with his fingers instead. </seg>
<seg id="64"> The man is putting a gun together. </seg>
<seg id="65"> Fish swim away from a turtle. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking through a field. </seg>
<seg id="67"> Someone is whipping eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man seated is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> The man drove the girl on his motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man rides a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and a woman walk together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing the violin on top of a house. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person cleans a porcupine. </seg>
<seg id="75"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> The man is lounging on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man dances. </seg>
<seg id="78"> The surgeions worked on the man in the ER. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting the grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> the men is beeting the tread </seg>
<seg id="81"> Th chimpanzee did martial arts kicks with a man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> The lady stir fried the onions in oil. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A grey cat opens a cabinet draw with his left fore paw and thereafter enters the draw. </seg>
<seg id="84"> Janpanese cooking show competition about cooking duck. </seg>
<seg id="85"> Two women cook food in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> The man broke an egg into the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="89"> Two dogs are lying in a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Lionel Richie is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> The man rode his bike in a cirle in the parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> The woman is boiling pasta. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are singing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> The toddler played the guiter while standing on the couch. </seg>
<seg id="96"> The woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> The man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man seated is playing the guitar and humming a tune. </seg>
<seg id="100"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man dances. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is hitting a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three teenage girls danced in the room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man dances. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are fistfighting in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> The man is throwing knives at a target. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Several kids jump up and down on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing the chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are talking. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> The couple ran hand in hand to the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> The man is walking. </seg>
<seg id="114"> The man is putting a gun together. </seg>
<seg id="115"> The girl danced in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> The man sang and played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> potato is been cut in pieces </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A guy pushes a lawnmower across a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> a man drawing enclined plane on a white board </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing a video game on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A gun fires a blast. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A skateboarder is performing a trick in a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman reads a book in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is shown playing a wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is dicing half a tomato with a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down a wooded road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman pours a mixture into a bowl and mixes it. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A lady is removing the outer part of a papaya to make it smooth. </seg>
<seg id="133"> The lady chopped up the vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A frog crawls along a man's arm. </seg>
<seg id="135"> The man is walking. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is rising from the water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> The cut animal is sleeping </seg>
<seg id="138"> The woman is slicing eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A guy creates the illusion of levitating in the air. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is grazing in a field. </seg>
<seg id="141"> People kick a ball on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A cook is scaling an eel with a cleaver. </seg>
<seg id="143"> The chef sliced the onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> The man is loading his gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts some chicken in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> The man chopped the cement block on the man's stomach. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A guy creates the illusion of levitating in the air. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A man is putting pieces of strawberry on filling on a round slice of cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man shot his rifle at a target. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A small baby lying on his back on a bed is holding a large stuffed toy and biting it. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man speaks from a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> The man sliced the bun in half. </seg>
<seg id="156"> The man is feeding a mouse to the snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> The man played haki sak in the office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A yacht is sailing on the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Food is sliced. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Someone is putting cheese into pasta sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A person is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> The tiger is walking. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats play on a pair of stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Several deer are heading toward a forest. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is beating eggs in a bowl with chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Ocra is boiling in a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy trolley hits a car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> The plane took off the runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A potato is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two martial artists fight it out. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting the grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> a woman is cutting potato </seg>
<seg id="174"> An officer is talking to recruits. </seg>
<seg id="175"> The cook is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> The boy twirled his chair and answered the phone from his friend. </seg>
<seg id="177"> The man rode off on his motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> The boy did backward sommersaults from the diving board into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man reads his email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> a woman is cutting potato </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man talks with a human skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A lady is removing the outer part of a papaya to make it smooth. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Someone cut up an edible root. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> Only the silhouette of a band performing on stage is visible. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A person plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> The cat cuddled with the baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> The kids danced on the patio. </seg>
<seg id="193"> The cut animal is sleeping </seg>
<seg id="194"> The woman put an egg in the mixer. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman cuts up some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="196"> The woman is driving the car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man stuffed his face with food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> The baby sneezed and startled the other baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is cutting a squash in small strips. </seg>
<seg id="200"> Meat is being stirred. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman turns two eggs in boiling water, removes them after some time and places them in ice cold water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is beating eggs in a bowl with chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man cutting tree from axe </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man does floor exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> An animal rides a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> The bath toys swam in the red water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing and playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman plays with a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman slices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is chopping mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is chopping mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat moves around underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="215"> The lady sliced the ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> a woman is cutting potato </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man talks on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A potato is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man talks. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping the rim of a bowl clean. </seg>
<seg id="221"> The tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is dicing half a tomato with a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing a fish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> The man rode off on his motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> The woman came down on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman slices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> An old woman is peeling the skin of a potato with a vegetable peeler. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A small guinea pig is gnawing and eating a piece of carrot on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A young woman is applying eye shadow to her upper lid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl applying makeup by herself. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A guy is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man moves his hands. </seg>
<seg id="233"> The man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog bounces on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> The lady cut the octopus tentacle into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="236"> The girl sat on the couch to crochet. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man cuts up meat. </seg>
<seg id="238"> The tiger is walking. </seg>
<seg id="239"> Someone is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A potato is being chopped. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref15">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people jog in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> a picking up a water vase </seg>
<seg id="3"> The wrestler skidded across the ring on his forehead. </seg>
<seg id="4"> The man beat the other man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A young boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> The lady spread shortening on a baking sheet. </seg>
<seg id="7"> two girls playing with balls </seg>
<seg id="8"> young girl grooming her hair in front of bathroom mirror </seg>
<seg id="9"> Two people are riding horses on a track. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A guy playing the kids bass tuto. </seg>
<seg id="11"> The man played his keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A vaquero is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> The man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A girl sits in a chair with her hand over a white piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A school boy is looking at the calender. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A young woman is applying liquid lipstick to her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl shot an automatice rifle in the field. </seg>
<seg id="18"> Learn to shoot like a Cow Boy </seg>
<seg id="19"> there is a preparing the item </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man rowed a boat in the river. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A person moves a fallen tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="22"> Someone fell off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> Someone is cutting potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man rode his motorcycle through town. </seg>
<seg id="25"> Two people in a car talk. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman glazes some meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> Four young men stand still as a car explodes behind them. </seg>
<seg id="28"> The dog chewed a stuffed whale. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person plays with a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="30"> The man is doing moped tricks. </seg>
<seg id="31"> a lady preparing bean dish </seg>
<seg id="32"> a man is playing the guitar </seg>
<seg id="33"> A boy plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> Learn to shoot like a Cow Boy </seg>
<seg id="35"> Lionel Richie is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person types on a stenotype machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman dips a shrimp in butter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man plays an entire song on the piano. </seg>
<seg id="39"> The man is cleaning the glass doors. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A person is seasoning bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger walks around aimlessly. </seg>
<seg id="42"> The man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> the lady picked up the kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> The man rode his horse by the river. </seg>
<seg id="45"> The man erased what the other man had on the board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> The man cut a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men compete in a tire rolling race. </seg>
<seg id="48"> The boy did tricks on his bike. </seg>
<seg id="49"> a man sharpening his knife to cut wood </seg>
<seg id="50"> The man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A man cooking Onigiri. </seg>
<seg id="52"> The mammal hung from the rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A BABY IS CRAWLING ON THE BED. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is cutting cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="56"> a guy teaching how to make spheggati sauce </seg>
<seg id="57"> The man put the cooked chicken into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="58"> The man read an ad from a personals ad. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person stirs some meat. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino walks in a field. </seg>
<seg id="61"> The cat circled the box and then jumped inside. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A person shoots a gun in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="63"> Someone is playing an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="64"> The man put his gun barrel together. </seg>
<seg id="65"> The turtle swam after the fish. </seg>
<seg id="66"> The couple walked arm in arm down the path. </seg>
<seg id="67"> racipe for a japanese dish Tamaki Sushi...... </seg>
<seg id="68"> The rock star played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A young man plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> The man took the girl on a motorcycle ride. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man rode a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> The couple walked hand in hand down the path. </seg>
<seg id="73"> The man played the violin on the rooftop. </seg>
<seg id="74"> Someone tried to give the hedgehog a bath. </seg>
<seg id="75"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man lounges on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> The man did a funny dance for the girl. </seg>
<seg id="78"> doctors giving treatment to  a injured person </seg>
<seg id="79"> The boy cut the grass by the curb with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cut a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> the boy is figthing the monkey </seg>
<seg id="82"> The cook put oil, garlic, and onions into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> The cat opened a drawer and climbed inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> The chef is frying </seg>
<seg id="85"> Two women put a meat mixture into a hot frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="86"> The lady cracked an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> The man is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is chopping onions and chillies. </seg>
<seg id="89"> Two dogs are lying in a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Lionel Richie is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> The man rode his bike in the parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> The lady stirred the noodles in the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women in uniform are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A little boy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking three eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> The man rode his motorcycle dow the dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="99"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> a man is playing the guitar </seg>
<seg id="101"> The man did a funny dance for the girl. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is in the process of chopping down a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> The man did a funny dance for the girl. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men box in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a dart board on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Some children are jumping on Trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> The man erased what the other man had on the board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two people talk to each other. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is stuffing a banana into his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="112"> the people are running </seg>
<seg id="113"> A person walks down a lane. </seg>
<seg id="114"> The man put his gun barrel together. </seg>
<seg id="115"> The lady danced in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> The singer also played a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> someone is slicing potatoes </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is laying on her back on a mat and she is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> Someone sliced a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A vaquero is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> The man is mowing the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> a man is teaching on blackboard </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is working with his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A person shoots a gun in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A skater skates on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="126"> The girl read a book while lounging on the ground outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man plays a wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is slicing tomato. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man runs along a road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is slicing onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> The lady scrambled eggs in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man smoothly slicing the papaya to make juice. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A person is cooking the food </seg>
<seg id="134"> The man held a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A person walks down a lane. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A person rises out of the water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> the animal is playing </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman cuts up vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="139"> The man levitated off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino walks in a field. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Peoples are playing football in a beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> The man killed, skinned, and gutted the snake. </seg>
<seg id="143"> The man is slicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="144"> The man loaded his rifle. </seg>
<seg id="145"> The man put the cooked chicken into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="146"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man hits a cement block on another mans stomach with a sludgehammer. </seg>
<seg id="148"> The man levitated off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man cuts a boot with a huge knife. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A person is placing sliced pieces of strawberries on top of a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is chopping onions and chillies. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man standing in the woods fires a shot with his rifle at a far off target. </seg>
<seg id="153"> The baby hugged the stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man speaks from a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> the man show the demo how to prepare the bread and sand wich </seg>
<seg id="156"> The man is trying to feed the snake with a mouse. </seg>
<seg id="157"> The man is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A yacht moves across the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is preparing to dice an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> The cook is adding cheese into the pot. </seg>
<seg id="161"> Someone is cutting potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger walks around aimlessly. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats seated on separate stools are pawing and biting each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Some antelope (or similar animals) are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman beats two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Someone is boiling okra in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A train coming around a bend hits a stationary car on the track. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The rock star played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane takes off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A potato is cut. </seg>
<seg id="171"> The man beat the other man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="172"> The boy cut the grass by the curb with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A women is cutting a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="174"> The drill sargent is talking to his men. </seg>
<seg id="175"> An onion is being cut and chopped. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A guy, in a chair, swivels and talks on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> The man took off on a huge motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> The man dove off the board into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> The man read an ad from a personals ad. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A women is cutting a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="181"> Someone is holding a skull in their hands and is moving the  jaw to make it appear that the skull is talking. </seg>
<seg id="182"> The lady cracked an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man smoothly slicing the papaya to make juice. </seg>
<seg id="184"> The woman is dicing vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man cuts a boot with a huge knife. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band's profile displayed in the shadows on the wall. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> The cat is caressing the baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is slicing onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> a man is playing the guitar </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing on the balcony. </seg>
<seg id="193"> the animal is playing </seg>
<seg id="194"> A girl break an egg and she put in the machine </seg>
<seg id="195"> The lady sliced the clove of garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> Two people in a car talk. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A guy is licking his own hand. </seg>
<seg id="198"> The babies are sitting down. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is cutting cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="200"> Meat is mixed with the marinate. </seg>
<seg id="201"> The lady boiled two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman beats two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping a log. </seg>
<seg id="204"> The man demonstrated how to do an exercise on the floor mat. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey rides a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> The toys are in the tub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> The man strummed on his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> the lady picked up the kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman slices and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man chopped potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man chopped potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman slices a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat on his back is sliding around under a sofa using his paws to move around. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is chopping onions and chillies. </seg>
<seg id="215"> a person is cuttng the ginger </seg>
<seg id="216"> A women is cutting a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a telephone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A potato is cut. </seg>
<seg id="219"> The man gave a speech in front of some bookshelves. </seg>
<seg id="220"> The chef wiped the edge of the soup bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> The tiger played with an orange ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is slicing tomato. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing a meat into some pieces. </seg>
<seg id="224"> The man took off on a huge motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A women climbs down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman slices and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> The lady peeled a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="228"> The guinea pig is nibbling on a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> The girl is using an eye pencil on her eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl Glow Summer Skin </seg>
<seg id="231"> A MAN ALONE IN A FOREST. </seg>
<seg id="232"> The man played the harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A MAN IS RIDING ON THE HORSE. </seg>
<seg id="234"> The dog played on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> The woman is cutting cooked octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> she is doing the nail polish to the nailes </seg>
<seg id="237"> The lady sliced the raw fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger walks around aimlessly. </seg>
<seg id="239"> The boy folded the yellow piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A potato is cut. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref16">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people march in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A women in the garden </seg>
<seg id="3"> one wrestler is bumping another in such an extraordinary way, I have never seen it before. </seg>
<seg id="4"> the person is fighting </seg>
<seg id="5"> A youngster is sitting on a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> The man is greasing the pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A female volley ball player demonstrating spiking a volley ball. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl fixing her hair in front of the bathroom mirror. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A MAN IS PLAYING KEYBOARD. </seg>
<seg id="11"> The man played the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> The cowboy rode his horse in the desert. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> The woman is tapping her fingers on the table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A schoolboy is watching a calendar and counting the number of holidays for a particular month. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A lady is doing makeup. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is shooting with the gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is explain about single action gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring a pot of chilli. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is booting </seg>
<seg id="21"> The man moved a big tree branch away. </seg>
<seg id="22"> The horse and his rider fell down. </seg>
<seg id="23"> Someone is cutting potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A person rides a bike through the neighborhood. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A Girl Driving the Car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> The lady floured the meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> The car blew up behind the four boys. </seg>
<seg id="28"> The dog chewed a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> The person scratched the monkey's arm pits! </seg>
<seg id="30"> A Man is riding the bike. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone is stirring a pot of vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> The man played his drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is explain about single action gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> Lionel Ritchie dances while standing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> the man used a stenograph. </seg>
<seg id="37"> The lady dipped the shrimp in batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man plays the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> The mand is cleaning the door glass. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A person is seasoning slices of bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> The tiger paced in his cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man talks on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> The lady picked up the kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> The man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> The man is erasing the chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> the man cut the paper with sissors </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two people flipped tractor tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="48"> The boy flew up in the air with his bike. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a knife in a clamp. </seg>
<seg id="50"> cutting a potatoe into first half and then again in second half </seg>
<seg id="51"> A person making food </seg>
<seg id="52"> A slow loris is playing </seg>
<seg id="53"> The lady put the baby int a trashcan. </seg>
<seg id="54"> a baby is playing </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is cutting some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A person making Spaghetti Sauce </seg>
<seg id="57"> Learn to make Football Finger </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is talking to someone on his computer. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone browned the hamburger in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The rhino grazed on the grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> The cat jumped into the box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> The man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> a man fixing a silencer in a gun </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="66"> The man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A person is whipping eggs with other ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> man playing hard rock music on a electric quitar </seg>
<seg id="69"> The man is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> Two people are riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> The man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> a couple walking in a garden seems a clip from a south indian movie. </seg>
<seg id="73"> The man is on the roof playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="74"> the person is doing the something </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> The tide came in where the man was lounging on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> the boy and girl is dancing </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors are trying to resesitate a man. </seg>
<seg id="79"> The boy is using scissors to cut the grass. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> a monkey is hitting the man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> Food is poured and mixed on a hot plate. </seg>
<seg id="83"> The cat opened and climbed into the drawer. </seg>
<seg id="84"> super dotch cooking </seg>
<seg id="85"> Recipe of Beef Broccoli </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="89"> Two dogs are lying on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Lionel Ritchie dances while standing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding an electric bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Learn to make Yakibuta Ramen a Japanese noodle </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women sing and dance. </seg>
<seg id="95"> a cute baby playing the guitar...... </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A little girl jumped on top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A guy is sitting in the road. </seg>
<seg id="99"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> the boy and girl is dancing </seg>
<seg id="102"> The man cut down a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> three teenage girls dancing on music in their home </seg>
<seg id="104"> A musician plays a drum kit. </seg>
<seg id="105"> the boy and girl is dancing </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men fight each other in a boxing match. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a round target mounted on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> The boys did tricks on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> The man is erasing the chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> a clipping from the movie anbae shivam starring kamal hassan and madhavan </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is stuffing a peeled banana in his mouth as he is talking. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman are running together towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> a man fixing a silencer in a gun </seg>
<seg id="115"> The woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Two men are playing in a musical band. </seg>
<seg id="117"> the way of making french fries </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is performing some floor exercises. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A guy is cutting the bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> The cowboy rode his horse in the desert. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> the computer screen correcting the lines straightly </seg>
<seg id="123"> someone is playing a game on a laptop </seg>
<seg id="124"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> The man is riding a skateboard and doing tricks. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is laying on a rock reading a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man plays a wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> Someone is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="129"> The man ran down the road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman makes vertical and horizontal cuts on a white onion and thereafter chops it into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> a woman is cutting a papaya </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man holds a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> The man emerged from the muddy water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A dog is trying to sleep on a log </seg>
<seg id="138"> The lady sliced the eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> The man floated in the air. </seg>
<seg id="140"> The rhino grazed on the grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Some men are playing ball on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man cutes open a snake. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A chef demonstrates cutting onions. </seg>
<seg id="144"> The man loaded his rifle with bullets. </seg>
<seg id="145"> Learn to make Football Finger </seg>
<seg id="146"> A Man Playing Guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> a man learning to fight </seg>
<seg id="148"> The man floated in the air. </seg>
<seg id="149"> The man sliced through the toe of a boot with a big sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A person is placing strawberries atop a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man took aim and fired at a target. </seg>
<seg id="153"> The baby is playing with the stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man talks on a stand. </seg>
<seg id="155"> a man telling about a racipe about big mac </seg>
<seg id="156"> The man teased a snake with a live mouse. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing hacky sack in an office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> The boat cut through the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Half an onion is sliced horizontally and then vertically. </seg>
<seg id="160"> The lady added cheese to the sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> Someone is cutting potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="162"> The tiger paced in his cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two kittens each standing on stools are playfully fighting each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> The deer are crossing the road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman mixes a mixture. </seg>
<seg id="166"> The lady put the bean pods in the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A train crashes into a car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> man playing hard rock music on a electric quitar </seg>
<seg id="169"> The jet lifted off from the runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> The chef cut the potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="171"> the person is fighting </seg>
<seg id="172"> The boy is using scissors to cut the grass. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A women making tendon </seg>
<seg id="174"> The military officer barked at the recruits. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man sliced an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> The man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> the man is riding bike </seg>
<seg id="178"> swimming in the liver pool </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is talking to someone on his computer. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A women making tendon </seg>
<seg id="181"> The man is playing with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> a woman is cutting a papaya </seg>
<seg id="184"> A man is slicing some Mushroom. </seg>
<seg id="185"> The man sliced through the toe of a boot with a big sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing live on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> The cat snuggled with the baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman makes vertical and horizontal cuts on a white onion and thereafter chops it into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A dog is trying to sleep on a log </seg>
<seg id="194"> A lady break a egg and put in the machine. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man copping a garlick. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A Girl Driving the Car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> a man eating like animals. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two babies sit in their booster seats. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is cutting some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="200"> The cook is marinating meat. </seg>
<seg id="201"> The lady is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman mixes a mixture. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping down on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is working out. </seg>
<seg id="205"> The monkey rode her tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A fish swims in red-tinted water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A guy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> The lady picked up the kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> The girl sliced the onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is slicing mashroom. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is slicing mashroom. </seg>
<seg id="212"> Someone is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat slides along under the sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="215"> a lady is cutting the ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A women making tendon </seg>
<seg id="217"> The man talked on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> The chef cut the potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A gentleman giving a lecture with background of books on shelf. </seg>
<seg id="220"> there is preparing item </seg>
<seg id="221"> The tiger played with an orange ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> Someone is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing a strip of meat into small wedges. </seg>
<seg id="224"> the man is riding bike </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman climbs down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> The girl sliced the onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> The lady peeled the potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="228"> a rat is eating a piece of carrot </seg>
<seg id="229"> The woman is pencilling on eye shadow. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl is applying makeup. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man in the forest </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A girl is riding a horse in a stadium. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman cuts up some worms. </seg>
<seg id="236"> a woman's are preparing with woolen </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is cutting a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="238"> The tiger paced in his cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> The man is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> The chef cut the potatoe. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref17">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three persons are doing same exercise. </seg>
<seg id="2"> a girl is cutting the tree </seg>
<seg id="3"> Midgets are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> The boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> Lazy man's bread </seg>
<seg id="7"> A volleyball player named Alisha Zamparelli teaching a spike and hitting technique. </seg>
<seg id="8"> the small girl is combing the hair by herself. </seg>
<seg id="9"> The lady is riding on the horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> The cowboy rode his horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is clicking her nails on a counter top. </seg>
<seg id="15"> The boy is reading a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A GIRL IS DOING MAKE-UP. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is standing and continuosly  firing </seg>
<seg id="18"> the person is loading the gun and shooting </seg>
<seg id="19"> the person is cooking something </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is doing boating </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a fallen tree. </seg>
<seg id="22"> The horse and rider fell. </seg>
<seg id="23"> someone is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> The man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> The woman is riding the jeep </seg>
<seg id="26"> A person covers a steak in flour. </seg>
<seg id="27"> The car blew up, but the 4 passengers were out of the car. </seg>
<seg id="28"> The dog is chewing on a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person is playing with small animal </seg>
<seg id="30"> the boy is doing feats with bycycle </seg>
<seg id="31"> any one is making dish </seg>
<seg id="32"> Cucho - Me Duele Amarte  a boy plying gitar and singing song </seg>
<seg id="33"> the person is playing drums </seg>
<seg id="34"> the person is loading the gun and shooting </seg>
<seg id="35"> The man danced upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> the person is tyiping </seg>
<seg id="37"> there is a one curry with boiling </seg>
<seg id="38"> A person is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man demonstrates how to clean glass doors and windows in the proper way. </seg>
<seg id="40"> The man is seasoning the buttered bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> tiger is in a cave </seg>
<seg id="42"> The man talked on the phone in the pizza kitchen. </seg>
<seg id="43"> The woman picked up the kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man rides a horse near a river. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper in half. </seg>
<seg id="47"> the man is lifting the weight. </seg>
<seg id="48"> The man is riding a bike doing tricks. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is balancing a knife </seg>
<seg id="50"> preparing something </seg>
<seg id="51"> anyone is making dish </seg>
<seg id="52"> the loris playing with the roap very slowly </seg>
<seg id="53"> a small baby is crying </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is playing and advertisi9ng </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is dicing zuchinni. </seg>
<seg id="56"> any one is making dish </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man places cooked chicken in a container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> a man operating coumpter </seg>
<seg id="59"> the person is cooking the something </seg>
<seg id="60"> a rhino is eating grass </seg>
<seg id="61"> The cat was curious about the box and jumped inside. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is firing with a gun </seg>
<seg id="63"> The man played a ukelele on stage. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is clearing his gun </seg>
<seg id="65"> Fish vs. Turtle in the water </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> a person coking. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A Man performing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> The man played the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> Two people ride on a motor scooter. </seg>
<seg id="71"> The man rode a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man plays the violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> woman giving abath to mouse </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> One person is sleeping </seg>
<seg id="77"> This film is badri </seg>
<seg id="78"> doctors opration in the hospital </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is edging the lawn with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting the rope </seg>
<seg id="81"> THE MONKEY IS PRACTICE THE BOXING. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman mixes vegetables and cooking oil in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> The cat opened the drawer and got inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef cooks food in a large pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> a girl is making  a dish </seg>
<seg id="86"> she is cooking </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is chopping up a white onion and another vegetable which is green. </seg>
<seg id="89"> The dog is lying down on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> The man danced upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man circling in bi-cycle </seg>
<seg id="92"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> lady cooking ramen noodles </seg>
<seg id="94"> Women are dancing and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby playing a gitter </seg>
<seg id="96"> The lady cracked the egs. </seg>
<seg id="97"> the girl is jumping </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> Cucho - Me Duele Amarte  a boy plying gitar and singing song </seg>
<seg id="101"> This film is badri </seg>
<seg id="102"> The man is cutting a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are Dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> The drummer is playing his drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> This film is badri </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men fistfight in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives. </seg>
<seg id="108"> The kids are playing on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A man having scars in his face. </seg>
<seg id="111"> The man ate a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> a hero and the heroine are running. </seg>
<seg id="113"> The man walked down the path. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is clearing his gun </seg>
<seg id="115"> one girl is dancing </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is on a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> perparing something </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is working out. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is cutting a bread using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> The cowboy rode his horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man mows the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing a shape on a whiteboard. </seg>
<seg id="123"> holiday enjoyment is laptop only </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is firing with a gun </seg>
<seg id="125"> The skateboarder did a trick and fell off his board. </seg>
<seg id="126"> a woman is reading </seg>
<seg id="127"> The man is playing the wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> Someone sliced a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running up a street. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman slices and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> chiken rice </seg>
<seg id="132"> well a clip of peeling a papaya and making it smooth. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is cutting something </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> The man walked down the path. </seg>
<seg id="136"> the person is trying the out side </seg>
<seg id="137"> the bear is enjoying itself and take rest </seg>
<seg id="138"> She is cooking </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man floats over a hand. </seg>
<seg id="140"> a rhino is eating grass </seg>
<seg id="141"> The men are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> Someone cuts off a snake's head and then skins it. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A chef showing how to cut an onion the proper way. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading the gun </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man places cooked chicken in a container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A person broking a stone on the man </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man floats over a hand. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man slicing a boot. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A person is putting strawberries on a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is chopping up a white onion and another vegetable which is green. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man using a shotgun for target practice. </seg>
<seg id="153"> The baby hugged a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> The man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="155"> a men is slicing bread </seg>
<seg id="156"> The man tried to feed a live mouse to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man does balancing tricks with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="158"> The boat is on the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person cuts an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> The lady added cheese to the tomatoe sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> someone is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> tiger is in a cave </seg>
<seg id="163"> cats playing with each other </seg>
<seg id="164"> The herd of deer crossed the road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> The lady scrambled the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> there is a preparing curry </seg>
<seg id="167"> The toy train hit the red car on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A Man performing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> THE ATROPLANE FLYING </seg>
<seg id="170"> The chef cut up a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is edging the lawn with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> the women cutting the item </seg>
<seg id="174"> The seargeant inspected the recruits bunks. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A chef is chopping and dicing a onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A boy calls another. </seg>
<seg id="177"> this is Viper Biker </seg>
<seg id="178"> one person jumping into swimming pool </seg>
<seg id="179"> a man operating coumpter </seg>
<seg id="180"> the women cutting the item </seg>
<seg id="181"> The man talked to a puppet. </seg>
<seg id="182"> she is cooking </seg>
<seg id="183"> well a clip of peeling a papaya and making it smooth. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A man is making chips with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man slicing a boot. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A silhouetted band is playing. </seg>
<seg id="187"> The band performed on stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> The man played the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A funny cat is trying to from the car. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman slices and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> Cucho - Me Duele Amarte  a boy plying gitar and singing song </seg>
<seg id="192"> They are dancing </seg>
<seg id="193"> the bear is enjoying itself and take rest </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> the person is cutting the something </seg>
<seg id="196"> The woman is riding the jeep </seg>
<seg id="197"> a man eating the food in a very badly way </seg>
<seg id="198"> One baby's sneeze startled the other baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is dicing zuchinni. </seg>
<seg id="200"> Using a large spoon, a woman combines pieces of beef meat along with the seasonings in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> The layd put two eggs into the water to boil. </seg>
<seg id="202"> The lady scrambled the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> a men cut the tree with axe </seg>
<seg id="204"> someone doing exercise </seg>
<seg id="205"> Monkey Showboating On A Bicycle </seg>
<seg id="206"> The tub toys moved toward the girl's head in the red water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A guy is playing his guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="208"> The woman picked up the kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> The lady cut up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A guy is slicing the mushroom. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A guy is slicing the mushroom. </seg>
<seg id="212"> The lady sliced a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat us crawling under a sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is chopping up a white onion and another vegetable which is green. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing myona ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> the women cutting the item </seg>
<seg id="217"> the men is speaking to phone </seg>
<seg id="218"> The chef cut up a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="219"> He is speaking </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cooker is showing how to cook. </seg>
<seg id="221"> a baby tiger being trained to play with a ball </seg>
<seg id="222"> Someone sliced a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing fish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> this is Viper Biker </seg>
<seg id="225"> The lady came down from the tree on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> The lady cut up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> The woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> a baby guinea pig is eating a carrot </seg>
<seg id="229"> shading the upper portion of the eyes with lip color pencil </seg>
<seg id="230"> a girl is doing make up </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is on search in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> a man is playing instrument </seg>
<seg id="233"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> the dog is playing </seg>
<seg id="235"> The lady cut up an octopus tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A GIRL IS SEARCHING IN HER CHAIN. </seg>
<seg id="237"> flesh is been cut by the knife </seg>
<seg id="238"> tiger is in a cave </seg>
<seg id="239"> A guy is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> The chef cut up a potatoe. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref18">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Two women and a man are stamping their feet on the floor and swinging their hands in rhythmic fashion. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman picks up a large watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> the two persons are doing the boxing </seg>
<seg id="4"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="5"> The boy practiced his piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is covering the black tray with butter. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is passing balls to another woman who is practicing </seg>
<seg id="8"> A baby is standing in front of the mirror. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man playing keyboard </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> The man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> The man climbed up a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman drums her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> The boy looked at the calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl with gun </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man shoots a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man is stirring the contents of a pan. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is riding a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A forest in north manitou island in 2008 </seg>
<seg id="22"> The horse fell down with its rider. </seg>
<seg id="23"> The man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A guy is siting in the ground. </seg>
<seg id="25"> she is car driving </seg>
<seg id="26"> A person is cooking </seg>
<seg id="27"> The car exploded. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is trying to bite a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> the boy is playing the dog </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is doing a motorcycle trick. </seg>
<seg id="31"> the person is cooking </seg>
<seg id="32"> A person playing a gitter </seg>
<seg id="33"> A young man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man shoots a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> The man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is typing . </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is coating shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A person plays the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> a man is cleaning a glass door </seg>
<seg id="40"> The man seasoned the buttered bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> They are cooking </seg>
<seg id="43"> A lady hug her pet Kangaro. </seg>
<seg id="44"> The man rode his horse by the river. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man erases a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> a person doing something </seg>
<seg id="47"> men are flipping tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A person is doing tricks with a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="49"> one man is working </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> making of rice dish </seg>
<seg id="52"> the animal is playing with wire </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman places a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> a baby is playing around in a diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is finely slicing a zucchini into thin long strips. </seg>
<seg id="56"> jack shows how to prepare the food </seg>
<seg id="57"> Jack is picking leg piece with a fork </seg>
<seg id="58"> someone typing in the computer </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is making meat </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating some grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A black and white cat playing with a big cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> someone is shooting with the gun </seg>
<seg id="63"> the man is playing the guitar </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is preparing his gun </seg>
<seg id="65"> A terrapin is swimming. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and a woman walk through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> a woman is cooking Temaki Sushi (Japanese Hand Roll Sushi) </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> The man played the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> the boy and girl is going on the bike driving </seg>
<seg id="71"> Do like to ride a bull then watch this </seg>
<seg id="72"> A indian couple walk together in a field </seg>
<seg id="73"> The fiddler played the fiddle on the roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A little animal is getting a bath. </seg>
<seg id="75"> The man sang and played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> the person is taking the rest </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man dances in the street. </seg>
<seg id="78"> it is aoprration scene in the hospital </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy cuts grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man slices a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is doing karate. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A lady stir fried onions in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> the cat is playing with box </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef is cooking food in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> a lady cooking thai food </seg>
<seg id="86"> The woman is breaking egg in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> The man cracked eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is chopping up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog and a large dog are on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> The man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> a man is driving bicyle </seg>
<seg id="92"> the man played his guitar outside. </seg>
<seg id="93"> the women is preparing noodles </seg>
<seg id="94"> A lady policers are singing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> the old lady tells something about her breakfast </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl leaps onto the top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A person playing a gitter </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man dances in the street. </seg>
<seg id="102"> Three men are in the forest and one of them is felling a tree with an ax. </seg>
<seg id="103"> the three girls are dancing </seg>
<seg id="104"> The man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man dances in the street. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Heavyweight Boxing in the Net </seg>
<seg id="107"> a man is throughing the knife towards the tree </seg>
<seg id="108"> the two boys jumped on the tramplines. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man erases a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A man with scares in the face is standing. </seg>
<seg id="111"> The man ate a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A guy is singing the song in the water. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is preparing his gun </seg>
<seg id="115"> The girl is dancing and singing in the rain in a south indian movie. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Guitar is being played by artist. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A guy is teaching how to prepare the french fries recipe. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman lying on her back on an exercise mat is moving her legs back and forth and her head from side to side, held by her hands. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is cutting the breads. </seg>
<seg id="120"> The man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> The man mowed his grass. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man showing how a computer can understand what he is drawing and respond to it. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A guy is playing a pc video game. </seg>
<seg id="124"> someone is shooting with the gun </seg>
<seg id="125"> The skateboarder fell off his board while doing a trick. </seg>
<seg id="126"> featuring a girl reading book </seg>
<seg id="127"> The man played his wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> The cook is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="129"> a man running very fast and working out </seg>
<seg id="130"> The lady sliced an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A women is making  Omurice </seg>
<seg id="132"> a lady is cutting papaya </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman slices garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> it looks like a really cute walking scrotum that chirps Yeh supposed to be millions of years old hahahahah.And extinct hahaha.Cant bring the big ones on the boat obviously. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A guy is singing the song in the water. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is emerging from water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> she is cutting the something </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man inspects the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating some grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> The men played soccer at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is scaling a snake. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A cooker cuts onions for chinese cooking. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man Loads shells into a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> Jack is picking leg piece with a fork </seg>
<seg id="146"> the person playing the music </seg>
<seg id="147"> featuring a dare </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man inspects the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> the man is cut the shoes </seg>
<seg id="150"> A person is putting strawberries slices on top of a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is chopping up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="152"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is laying down with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man gives a speech on the podeum. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is cutting a bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man playing with rat and snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> The man played haki sak in the office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> The bot skimmed across the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> The lady sliced the onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> How to prepare Lasagna? </seg>
<seg id="161"> The man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> the two cat are fighting </seg>
<seg id="164"> The herd of deer crossed the road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is Beating eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> a lady is stirring  the lady finger which is in the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> The toy train hit the toy car on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> the flight is taking takeoff </seg>
<seg id="170"> The man is slicing a potato into cubes. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy cuts grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> women is slicing vegetable </seg>
<seg id="174"> A man is putting kneel down. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is cutting onion </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man talks on his cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man rides a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A boy is diving backwards from a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> someone typing in the computer </seg>
<seg id="180"> women is slicing vegetable </seg>
<seg id="181"> A Man Playing with scull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> The woman is breaking egg in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> a lady is cutting papaya </seg>
<seg id="184"> A woman is chopping garlic. </seg>
<seg id="185"> the man is cut the shoes </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band plays against a surreal backdrop. </seg>
<seg id="187"> The band is perfoming in front of an audience. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A Man Playing Guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A baby is playing with a cat. </seg>
<seg id="190"> The lady sliced an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A person playing a gitter </seg>
<seg id="192"> the women is get down the water </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is holding egg in her hand. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person is chopping a clove of garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> she is car driving </seg>
<seg id="197"> a man eating very ugly. </seg>
<seg id="198"> two kids are sitting </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is finely slicing a zucchini into thin long strips. </seg>
<seg id="200"> Someone is mixing food in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> The woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is Beating eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A men cuting the tree </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man doing exercise </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A woman is bathing in blood. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A guy is singing a song . </seg>
<seg id="208"> A lady hug her pet Kangaro. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is cutting mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is cutting mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> The lady sliced the tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="213"> The cat is crawling under the sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is chopping up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="215"> WOMAN IS CUTING AN ONION </seg>
<seg id="216"> women is slicing vegetable </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> The man is slicing a potato into cubes. </seg>
<seg id="219"> there is a one men </seg>
<seg id="220"> the  arusuvai arangam the two persons  demo how to prepare the food tasty </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> The cook is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing meat on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man rides a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> a lady is coming in a rope near the cage </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is slicing onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A rabbit is in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="229"> a woman is doing make-up </seg>
<seg id="230"> a girl putting make up to her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is researching the enchanted forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> a man playing a instrument </seg>
<seg id="233"> a man is rading a horse </seg>
<seg id="234"> the dog is jumping </seg>
<seg id="235"> octopus dumpling. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is putting string on a metal shaft. </seg>
<seg id="237"> is it just me or does world need a subway-esque sushi franchise qith high quality sea foods and vegetables that are otherwise unavailable outside asia </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A guy is making the paper butterfly. </seg>
<seg id="240"> The man is slicing a potato into cubes. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref19">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Women are doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A lady is pouring water </seg>
<seg id="3"> A WRESTLING MATCH. </seg>
<seg id="4"> two men are fighting in the film sequence. </seg>
<seg id="5"> The boy practiced the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person butters a tray. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A girl is playing volleyball. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A small girl is combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A men playing gitar. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A boy is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A guy is riding on the horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> a man climbing a rope </seg>
<seg id="14"> A girl drummed her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> The boy looked at the calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> a woman putting lipstick to her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> Fun with the Single Action Colt </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is stirring a pot of soup on he stove. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is sailing the boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> a man carrying a tree. </seg>
<seg id="22"> jockey falling from horse </seg>
<seg id="23"> The man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="24"> a man driving bike very speedly </seg>
<seg id="25"> the man is taking the girl in the car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> the women is cooking something </seg>
<seg id="27"> A Car Blast behind the People. </seg>
<seg id="28"> The dog is chewing the toys. </seg>
<seg id="29"> masagining monky </seg>
<seg id="30"> the man is playing with his motor cycle and doing something dofferent it is nice to see </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person is stirring ingredients in a pan on the stove. </seg>
<seg id="32"> the boy is playing the music </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is drumming. </seg>
<seg id="34"> Fun with the Single Action Colt </seg>
<seg id="35"> a dancer dancing in a very crazy style </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A lady is dipping the prawn in to the dough. </seg>
<seg id="38"> The man is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> a man is cleaning a window </seg>
<seg id="40"> The man seasoned the buttered bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> a tiger is walking </seg>
<seg id="42"> the boys are cooking the somethiung </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is petting and holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> The man erased the work on the board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting shapes out of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> two strongest man playing a game with tyre </seg>
<seg id="48"> The person is sliding the cycle </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is clamping down a knife. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is slicing a potato </seg>
<seg id="51"> Someone is cooking meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A BEAR IS PLAYING ON THE ROPE. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is wearing a pamper and chilling </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is slicing a cucumber into very thin strips. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is seasoning sausage in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is cooking. </seg>
<seg id="58"> the person is reading the something </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone is cooking meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> rhinos hanging in the garden </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat  jump and goes under the box </seg>
<seg id="62"> Shotgun in UltraSlo motion. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing benzo. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is chasing a fish underwater. </seg>
<seg id="66"> The couple walked down the path together. </seg>
<seg id="67"> The lady whisked the two raw eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> the person is playing the music </seg>
<seg id="69"> David sides playing piano </seg>
<seg id="70"> the tamil movie actor prassanna and the actoress sing vigallin </seg>
<seg id="71"> the person is playing </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and a woman are walking along a path. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is fiddling on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A hedgehog is being bathed in a sink. </seg>
<seg id="75"> the person is playing the music </seg>
<seg id="76"> Relaxing in the living room. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A young man and a woman freaking out in the hills. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A doctor is doing cpr. </seg>
<seg id="79"> The boy cut the grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> There is a white guy severing a rope using a Chinese sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey performing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman pours oil, garlic, and onions on a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="83"> the cat is inside the box. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef is cooking. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is preparing the beef broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A lady preparing food using eggs. </seg>
<seg id="87"> one man is braking egg in a bowl </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is cooking vegetable pot pie. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog is laying on a bed wagging his tail. </seg>
<seg id="90"> a dancer dancing in a very crazy style </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding an electric bike. </seg>
<seg id="92"> man playing quitar sitting on a bench </seg>
<seg id="93"> A woman cooks noodles. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Pranks and comedy at policeman's ball. </seg>
<seg id="95"> the baby is playing the guitar </seg>
<seg id="96"> the old lady is talking. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is jumping on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is sitting on the road. </seg>
<seg id="99"> Man playing guitar </seg>
<seg id="100"> the boy is playing the music </seg>
<seg id="101"> A young man and a woman freaking out in the hills. </seg>
<seg id="102"> Men are in the forest with axes, while one of them attempts to cut down a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three young women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> The man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A young man and a woman freaking out in the hills. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are boxing. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a target on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Two boy are playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> The man erased the work on the board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A men with talking with a boy </seg>
<seg id="111"> The man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> The girl and boy were running towards the sea. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> the girl is happily dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A person is singing and playing with the guitar </seg>
<seg id="117"> Chef John is showing how to make homemade french fries that are very crispy. </seg>
<seg id="118"> The girl exercised on a mat. </seg>
<seg id="119"> a man is cutting the pices of bun </seg>
<seg id="120"> A guy is riding on the horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing his grass. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A teacher teaches the computer programming </seg>
<seg id="123"> A kid is playing a game on the computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> Shotgun in UltraSlo motion. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Tony Hawk is doing skateboard tricks. </seg>
<seg id="126"> the lady sit in the garden and read books </seg>
<seg id="127"> The man played his wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> The lady sliced a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="129"> a men is running very fast </seg>
<seg id="130"> The lady sliced an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> a women is making a dish </seg>
<seg id="132"> A lady is explaining how to make a Papaya smoothie </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is cutting garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> the man is in the forest </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man emerges from mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> a panda is lying on the wood. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is chopping an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> The man levitated above the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> rhinos hanging in the garden </seg>
<seg id="141"> Soccer players on the beach kick a ball around. </seg>
<seg id="142"> The art of cooking. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting a onion </seg>
<seg id="144"> a man snow. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is cooking. </seg>
<seg id="146"> the man is playing guiter. </seg>
<seg id="147"> tamil film vijay practicing karate very seriously </seg>
<seg id="148"> The man levitated above the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man cuts a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman is decorating a pancake with strawberry slices. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is cooking vegetable pot pie. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a beaver </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is giving lecture about cricket </seg>
<seg id="155"> the boy is cutting the bread </seg>
<seg id="156"> the man is keeping food to snakes </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man playing with a ball inside his office </seg>
<seg id="158"> Boat on the Sea. </seg>
<seg id="159"> cutting the food </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is cooking </seg>
<seg id="161"> The man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="162"> a tiger is walking </seg>
<seg id="163"> the two cats are fighting againt each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Deer crossing the Road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Someone is boiling peppers. </seg>
<seg id="167"> The toy train ran into the toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> the person is playing the music </seg>
<seg id="169"> The plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A Man is slicing some Patotos. </seg>
<seg id="171"> two men are fighting in the film sequence. </seg>
<seg id="172"> The boy cut the grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A chef cutting brinjal into pieces </seg>
<seg id="174"> 10 Minutes of Boot Camp. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is cutting the vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="176"> The boy answered the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> a man riding a big bike </seg>
<seg id="178"> A guy is jumping into the swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> the person is reading the something </seg>
<seg id="180"> A chef cutting brinjal into pieces </seg>
<seg id="181"> the person is playing with skeleton </seg>
<seg id="182"> A lady preparing food using eggs. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A lady is explaining how to make a Papaya smoothie </seg>
<seg id="184"> she is teaching how to make Easy Chicken Curry. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man cuts a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> the band played in the shadows. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is playing and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> a small boy gaming on the cat </seg>
<seg id="190"> The lady sliced an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> the boy is playing the music </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="193"> a panda is lying on the wood. </seg>
<seg id="194"> Laura in the kitchen explains and shows how to make banana bread from scratch. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is slicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> the man is taking the girl in the car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man eats a bunch of different foods. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two babies react to something. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is slicing a cucumber into very thin strips. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A lady is preparing ""Beef Brocolli"". </seg>
<seg id="201"> how to make some delicious Yakibuta Ramen </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> Axe the Best Survival Tool. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man doing exercise in 8 minutes </seg>
<seg id="205"> monkey is driving cycle </seg>
<seg id="206"> She take both </seg>
<seg id="207"> a man playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is petting and holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> One lady is showing how to cut the onion into small peices </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is slicing up some mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is slicing up some mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> The woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> The cat scootched itself under the bed. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is cooking vegetable pot pie. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A chef cutting brinjal into pieces </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A Man is slicing some Patotos. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is speaking </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="221"> a baby tiger playing </seg>
<seg id="222"> The lady sliced a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing meat. </seg>
<seg id="224"> a man riding a big bike </seg>
<seg id="225"> A women ropells to the ground on a tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="226"> One lady is showing how to cut the onion into small peices </seg>
<seg id="227"> Woman peeling potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Several guinea pigs in their cage eating carrots. </seg>
<seg id="229"> a women is makeuping </seg>
<seg id="230"> A lady is makeup </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is searching something in the jungle. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A person singing a song </seg>
<seg id="233"> A men walking on horse </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is cutting up octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> They are talking </seg>
<seg id="237"> any one is slicing </seg>
<seg id="238"> a tiger is walking </seg>
<seg id="239"> A guy making a paper butterfly. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A Man is slicing some Patotos. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
</mteval>
