<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
                   <mteval>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref0">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A class doing a walking exercise. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman picks up a watering can, shows it, then puts it down. </seg>
<seg id="3"> One wrestler throws another wrestler, who slides across the floor on his face. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting, and one man hits the other man on his head with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A cook spreads butter on a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="7"> a woman practicing a volleyball </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is doing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A boy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a keyboard piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man rides his horse in the dessert. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing up a knotted rope suspended from the ceiling, when the scene flashes to the same man splashing water on his face from an outdoor container. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her nails. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is checking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is putting on lipstick with a brush and talking. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is firing a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> a man shooting a gun </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring chili in a kettle. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a large tree limb in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse falls down. </seg>
<seg id="23"> a man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man rides a street bike through the town. </seg>
<seg id="25"> a man and woman riding in a car </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is coating a pork chop with flour. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A black colored pet dog is biting a stuffed toy fish. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A lemur is holding up it's arms and someone is scratching him. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is riding a motor-cycle on the one wheel. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone stirs chopped vegetables in a kettle with a wooden spatula. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A young man is seated in a chair playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing on drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> a man shooting a gun </seg>
<seg id="35"> Lionel Richie dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman dips a shrimp in batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing the key board. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is window cleaning. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is adding spices on a bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around in an enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman picks up a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse by some water and a woman's head comes out of the water. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper in half lengthwise using scissors. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are rolling huge tires sideways down a street while spectators watch. </seg>
<seg id="48"> a man riding a bike on a half pipe </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man inserts the tip of a large knife into a vise and pulls the knife towards him, then removes the knife and appears to be checking the blade for straightness. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is stir frying pieces of meat using chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A raccoon-like animal is hanging off two ropes suspended from the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman carrying a baby puts him in a garbage can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby plays around in his diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A woman is slicing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is seasoning sausage in a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting cooked chicken wings in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is smiling as he reads an email message. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone is stir-frying a ground substance in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is grazing in the grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man a playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man puts together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A tortoise chases fish in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman and a man, with their arms around each other, are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is scrambling eggs and spices in a glass bowl with a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="68"> The group Slayer plays a song onstage. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A couple ride on a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A person riding a mechanical bull </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man has his arm around a woman and they are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man plays a violin on the roof of a house. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A gerbil is getting washed. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is lying on a lounge chair on the beach partially covered by a beach umbrella. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is being treated for an emergency in a hospital. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy cutting grass at the edge of a sidewalk turns and yells something. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cuts throw a rope, suspended from the ceiling, with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is karate kicking at someone's gloved hand. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is placing oil in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef cooking food </seg>
<seg id="85"> Meat is being cooked in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog laying on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Lionel Richie dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man rides a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man playing a guitar on a bench. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A chef boils noodles. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A couple of policewomen are singing karaoke. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A young boy, standing on a couch, is singing into a microphone and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> An older woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A young man is seated in a chair playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping a tree in the Forrest. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A group of girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man boxing a bigger man. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing blades into a close target outside. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy does flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A man has a conversation with a younger man. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A woman and a man are holding hands and running towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man puts together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman dances in the rain out side. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Jimmy Hendrix performing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="117"> a person cutting a potatoes </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman demonstrating abdominal exercises. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A person is slicing bread with a bread knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man rides his horse in the dessert. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing the grass with a lawn mower. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man draws a four sided shape on a screen and then puts an X inside of it. </seg>
<seg id="123"> a guy typing on a computer </seg>
<seg id="124"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is skateboarding on a half pipe and he tries to do a flip and fails. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is lying on a blanket on a rock and reading a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> a woman cutting chicken and vegetables </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down a street and the scene flashes to a man and woman bowing. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman cuts up some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is placing eggs into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="132"> a person cutting up a fruit </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping and dicing onions with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man emerges out of a puddle of muddy water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is cutting partially peeled zucchini into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A guy levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is grazing in the grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A man playing soccer on the beach </seg>
<seg id="142"> A chef is preparing a snake for dinning. </seg>
<seg id="143"> An onion is being cut. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading his gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting cooked chicken wings in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A..man..plays...a..guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man breaks a slab of concrete that is lying on a prone man with a sledge hammer. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A guy levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man cuts the toe off a brown boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A person adds strawberries to a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man takes a shot at a target outside. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby biting on a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is giving a lecture on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man slicing a bun in half with a knife appears to cut himself. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man dangles a mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is in an office and juggling a small ball off his feet and head. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is cruising through the waters. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Someone is cutting an onion with a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A chef pours shredded mozzarella into a sauce pan. </seg>
<seg id="161"> a man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around in an enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting each other on stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deer are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman puts four okra in a pan of boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A little car sits on toy railroad tracks, as a train approaches. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The group Slayer plays a song onstage. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An airplane takes off and the wheels are drawn up inside the plane. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting, and one man hits the other man on his head with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy cutting grass at the edge of a sidewalk turns and yells something. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is voicing over his troops. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is spinning in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A boy does a back flip into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is smiling as he reads an email message. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A boy made a skull ""talk"" by moving the mouth with his hands. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> a person cutting up a fruit </seg>
<seg id="184"> A piece of garlic is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man cuts the toe off a brown boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on stage with fire in the background. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat rubs up against an infant </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman cuts up some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A young man is seated in a chair playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A group of teenagers are dancing outdoors. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person chops garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> a man and woman riding in a car </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is stuffing all kinds of food into his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezes. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is slicing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman stirs beef in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman boils eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is felling a tree. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is lying down on a blue mat exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bicycle with training wheels in circles. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Toys are floating in a bathtub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman picks up a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A demonstration of how to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is slicing a row of mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is slicing a row of mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="212"> a woman cutting a tomato </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is sliding under a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is thinly slicing a white translucent with pinkish rind looking vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is smiling while talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man wearing glasses and a suit is standing and talking in front of a huge bookshelf. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping off the edge of a bowl filled with food with a paper towel. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger club is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> a woman cutting chicken and vegetables </seg>
<seg id="223"> a man is slicing meat </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman drops down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A demonstration of how to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A person is peeling the skin off a potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="228"> hamster eating cheese </seg>
<seg id="229"> A girl applied eye makeup with a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl is doing make-up on her cheeks and forehead with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> a person walking through the woods </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man, wearing a billed hat, is playing the harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman rides her horse at walking speed. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is bouncing his front paws on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> The woman is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Two women are sitting on a couch knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is slicing raw meat into strips. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around in an enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref1">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A group of people are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman lifts up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A midget wrestler receives a face plant. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A cook spreads Crisco on a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman hits volleyballs at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A child is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a keyboard piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A cowboy rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman with purple fingernails is drumming her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is checking a calender. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is painting her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is spraying the field with a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man aims a handgun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is mixing a pot. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling in a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is picking up a tree. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse and its rider fall down. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man cuts a potato into sections. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man gets on a motorcycle and rides it out of an area of chairs and onto the street. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A man and a woman are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman brushes flour on a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up behind four people. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A doberman pincher is chewing on a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person is tickling a slow loris. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is riding on one wheel on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man mixes vegetables in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man aims a handgun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man danced on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman dips shrimp into a batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A guy is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man cleans a building glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is making garlic bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="42"> Two men are standing in a kitchen and one is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A girl is hugging a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> One man is erasing a chalkboard while a second man is talking to someone that is not in viewing range. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man cuts a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A bicycle rider is doing tricks on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man puts a knife in a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting a potato in half. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A person is cooking beef. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A slow loris hanging on a cord. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trashcan. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby bounces around a room. </seg>
<seg id="55"> a woman is slicing a vegetable </seg>
<seg id="56"> A person seasons meatballs. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts chicken wings in a container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man checks his e-mail. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is cooking beef on a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating on a field. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumped into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is adding a silencer to a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman walking hold each other. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A person whisks eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> The rock star performed with his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and a woman are riding on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A boy is playing bull riding game. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is standing on a roof top playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person washes a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A doctor is giving chest compressions to a man in a stretcher. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man with a sword slices a rope. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimp is kicking a target. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A person is cooking onions. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A big cat opens a plastic drawer with his paws and then hops inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef is cooking breadcrumbs in a large pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman adds marinated beef meat into a large pan containing smoking hot oil and stir fries the meat using a pair of tongs. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A person cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A chihuahua lying on top of a bed is snarling while wagging its tail simultaneously. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man danced on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle around a parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cook puts some noodles in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A boy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girls jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man chops down a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are acting silly. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A boy is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Men are boxing in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing a knives. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy is doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> One man is erasing a chalkboard while a second man is talking to someone that is not in viewing range. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A man in a red shirt is talking to a man in a white shirt. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is adding a silencer to a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A girl dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A band is singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A cook cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A girl is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is using a knife to slice a loaf of bread into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A cowboy rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing grass. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man draws shapes on a board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is describing the game he is playing on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man doing freestyle on a skate ramp. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman reads a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A boy is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A chef is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping a onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman cooks scrambled eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A papaya is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A person holds a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man emerges from mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A baby panda relaxes on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman chops an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A young man standing on the ground appears to levitate, and another young man runs his hand along the space created below the first man's shoes </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating on a field. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of boys are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A fish is being cleaned and cut into pieces for Chinese cooking. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A chef is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man cleans his gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts chicken wings in a container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is passionately playing a guitar in front of an audience. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man </seg>
<seg id="148"> A young man standing on the ground appears to levitate, and another young man runs his hand along the space created below the first man's shoes </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> a person is making a pie. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man fires a shotgun at a target. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby hugs a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man gave a speech from a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man slices bread. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man grabs a live rat out of a snake's cage. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing is kicking a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is cruising through water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person slices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man adds a plate full of grated cheese to a pan is which tomato puree is being cooked. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man cuts a potato into sections. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The cats are playing with each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deer are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is whisking two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is boiling peppers. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model car is hit by a model train. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The rock star performed with his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane lifts off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A commander is inspecting his men. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Two boys are talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A boy does a flip into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man checks his e-mail. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man holding a skull in his hands is moving its jaws while he does the talking. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A papaya is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A food is chopped up. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A view of a band playing through what appears to be a hole in a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band plays onstage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A black and white colored cat is snuggling itself against a baby's face. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping a onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A baby panda relaxes on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl and discards the shell. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person is slicing a garlic into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man and a woman are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is hogging noodles and ice cream. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezes and startles another baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> a woman is slicing a vegetable </seg>
<seg id="200"> A lady mixed meat and spices together. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman boils two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is whisking two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a trunk with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> An orangutan is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Toys are floating in blood red water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A girl is hugging a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> The woman is dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is shown chopping several potatoes into small pieces using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is shown chopping several potatoes into small pieces using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A tomato is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling on its back under a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A person slices ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A person is cleaning a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A chef is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A man is slicing the meat for the dish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman climbs down a vine and kneels by a cage. </seg>
<seg id="226"> The woman is dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A potato is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A baby guinea pig is nibbling on a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A girl is making eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is applying makeup to her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man crosses a fallen tree trunk, as he is treading on dried leaves in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman slices some kind of seafood in chunks. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A woman slices a fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A man creases a yellow colored square sheet of paper by folding it diagonally at all sides and then opens it out. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref2">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> People exercise togther. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A midget wrestler is thrown in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting near cows. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is applying butter to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting a volleyball on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A kid is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A guy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is counting days by looking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is painting her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is shooting a gun multiple times. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man fires an empty revolver. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is mixing a pot of chili. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a tree. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse and rider are falling to the ground. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a bike on the road. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman and man are driving in a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is seasoning a steak. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up behind some men. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A doberman pinscher is chewing on a stuffed animal toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A slow loris is being tickled. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man popped a wheelie on his motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person mixes a bowl of vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a drum set. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man fires an empty revolver. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing on some kind of machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is dipping fish into batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a key-board by one hand. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is preparing garlic bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is pacing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman holds a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is cleaning a green-board and other man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are flipping large tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A bicyclist is performing tricks in a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man puts a knife into a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A male is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A person is cooking beef on a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="52"> An animal is suspended in air by holding onto two cords with it's hands and feet. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby climbs down from a sofa to the floor. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A women is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is sprinkling spices onto sausages in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting foods in a box. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is checking his email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone is putting raw ground meat into a wok. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing a guitar on a stage outside. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman whisks two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and a woman ride a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a bull machine. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing a violin on the roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A lady is washing a little hedgehog in the sink. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is dieing in an operating room. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A teenage boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man slices rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimp is doing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman pours some oil in a skillet, then some seasoning, and then some diced vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat climbs into a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef is preparing some food. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is cooking meat in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cracking an egg into a small dish. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog is wagging its tail on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle on the road. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A person is boiling noodles. </seg>
<seg id="94"> People sing and play instruments. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is coming up on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man cut a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing in a room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A guy is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The boxers fought in the ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knifes at tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is cleaning a green-board and other man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The boy confronted his dad. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking  with style. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing a guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man cuts a potato at both ends and thereafter slices it into thick strips. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A girl is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A guy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man cutting grass by the machine. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing a diagram on a white board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is looking at a picture on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A boy is showing skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A boy is playing flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person cuts a tomato into many pieces. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is scrambling eggs in a skillet using chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A person is carving the skin off a papaya fruit. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking  with style. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man's head rises out of a pile of mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing an eggplant into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man appears to float off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men are playing football by the beachside. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man chops the head of a snake, dips the body immediately in a bucket of water, cuts and peels the skin off. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A chef sliced up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man dressed in fatigues is loading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting foods in a box. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is paying guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man hammers a concrete slab on top of a man. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man appears to float off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> very look like beautiful </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is firing a shot gun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is hugging a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man gave a speech from the lectern. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a hamburger bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man holds a white rat close to his face after touching it to a snake's body in a glass enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with a ball in a office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is going through water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is adding something to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is pacing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The cats fought each other from two stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deer cross the road in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is stirring two eggs in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A person is boiling chile peppers. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model train crashes into a model car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An airplane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting near cows. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A teenage boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A Drill Sargent addresses his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is sitting in a swivel chair talking on a cordless telephone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A guy is doing a double back flip off the diving board into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is checking his email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man holding a skull is talking while manipulating the skull to look like it is talking. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A person is carving the skin off a papaya fruit. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cook cuts up some cauliflower. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A silhouette of a band playing is shown. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is playing on stage under blue lights when slowly the lights change to bright white. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A black-and-white-cat is snuggling heads with a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A chef slices a garlic clove. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman and man are driving in a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is stuffing food in his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two babies are sitting side by side in infant seats. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A women is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A lady mixed up a meat mixture in bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman boils two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is stirring two eggs in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping wood. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is stretching. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A woman is dead in a bathtub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman holds a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A girl is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is cutting up mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is cutting up mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman cuts a tomato into slices. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling under a piece of furniture on it's back. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is speaking into a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping the edge of a bowl off. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person cuts a tomato into many pieces. </seg>
<seg id="223"> chopping something </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A girl is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A potato is peeled. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig chews on food. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A makeup pencil is being applied to a female's eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is crossing a tree in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A jockey rides a horse around an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A woman is slicing fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is pacing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person folds a piece of paper several times. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref3">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> The people exercised to a video. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman bends over and picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A wrestler throws a man across the floor. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is in a cattle pen with some other men and he's hitting the other men with a wooden club. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is buttering a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting volleyballs over a net. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A kid playing a synthesizer. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man gallops on a horse across the desert. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope that is suspended from what looks like the ceiling of a warehouse. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingernails on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is applying lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man holding a revolver in front of him, turns it four times and then puts it down. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring a pot of chili with a spoon. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a fallen branch out of a pathway in a wooded area. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse and the person riding it fall down on the ground and then stand up after a while. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motor-cycle in the street. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman and man are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is coating a piece of pork with a flour mixture. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car blows up. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog chews his toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is petting a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man pops wheelies on his motor scooter. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone is stirring a pan full of chopped vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man holding a revolver in front of him, turns it four times and then puts it down. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing hanging upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is tying in the machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is dipping a piece of fish into some batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is putting garlic on some bread slices. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is carrying a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man with a bow and a quiver of arrows is riding a horse near a small body of water. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man erases a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a paper by scissor. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are moving tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A biker is performing stunts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is clamping the blade of a knife in a vise. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman sautes some beef. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A loris is swinging. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A young girl puts a small child into a metal trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is crawling off a bed. </seg>
<seg id="55"> chopping vegetables </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man seasons meat in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts chicken wings into tupperware. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is staring straight ahead and rubbing his hand over his chin and then the scene switches to a personal ad in some kind of paper or magazine. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is cooking beef. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is firing a shotgun and you can see the blast from the end of the barrel. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing a violin like a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is assembling a Silencerco 22 Sparrow gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is swimming underwater near the floor of a body of water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking arm in arm through a wooded area. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is beating two eggs in a bowl using a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding a motorbike. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and a woman are walking in the garden. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is on a roof dancing. </seg>
<seg id="74"> Someone is washing a small rodent looking animal in an aluminum pan. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is slipping at the sea-shore in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is injured and bleeding on a stretcher. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimpanzee and a man are practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is adding oil and paste into the pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat has opened a drawer and entered inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef prepared a meal. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is putting beef into a hot wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracked a egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog is wagging its tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing hanging upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A person is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="94"> The two officers danced and sang in front of the band. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> An old lady is adding an egg into the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping a tree down. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing with music. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing a drum set. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The men are in a boxing match with barehands. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a target. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A guy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man erases a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The man talked to the young man. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running through an open gate that leads to the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down the road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is assembling a Silencerco 22 Sparrow gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is chopping a potato. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A lady did exercises on a mat. </seg>
<seg id="119"> Bread is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man gallops on a horse across the desert. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing his lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing a diagram on the board and explaining it. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing a computer game. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is firing a shotgun and you can see the blast from the end of the barrel. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man does tricks on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A girl is reading a book in the wood. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person cuts up tomatos. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down a road and then the scene switches and he's doing push-ups in front of a woman. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is frying some eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A person peels an orange object. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is mincing a clove of garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is catching a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down the road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is coming out into the water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is sleeping on woods. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A chef is chopping a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is finding something on the road. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men play soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is cleaning a snake. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man cuts an onion into thin slivers with a cleaver. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a gun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts chicken wings into tupperware. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man breaks cinder blocks on another man. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man is finding something on the road. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man severs the toe of an empty leather boot using a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A cake is being decorated with strawberries. </seg>
<seg id="151"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is firing a shotgun at targets. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is hugging a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is delivering a lecture at an event celebrating the game of cricket. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is splitting a bread roll in half with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is dangling a live mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with a hackey sack in a work office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is moving across water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A chef is slicing into an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is putting cheese into a pan with sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The two cats fought with each other from their stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A group of deers are crossing road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is mixing eggs in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Someone is cooking okra in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model train hits a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An animated passenger jet is taking off from the runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is in a cattle pen with some other men and he's hitting the other men with a wooden club. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is inspecting a barracks. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A boy is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man does a back flip from a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is staring straight ahead and rubbing his hand over his chin and then the scene switches to a personal ad in some kind of paper or magazine. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is mimicking with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracked a egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A person peels an orange object. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cook is chopping a mushroom. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man severs the toe of an empty leather boot using a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> There are several views of a silhouette of group playing music. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is nuzzling a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is sleeping on woods. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl and puts it in the stand mixer. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is slicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman and man are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating noodles and ice creams. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby is sneezing and other baby is afraid. </seg>
<seg id="199"> chopping vegetables </seg>
<seg id="200"> A person is mixing a batch of beef in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling egg. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is mixing eggs in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting wood with axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing exercise. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A primate rides a little pink bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A girl with black lipstick on is laying in a tub filled with red liquid and a toy shark. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is carrying a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="210"> Mushrooms are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="211"> Mushrooms are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman cuts a tomato into two and thereafter slices one half of it. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling under a sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="215"> Someone is slicing a ginger root into very thin pieces. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is cleaning a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing with an orange ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person cuts up tomatos. </seg>
<seg id="223"> Fish is being sliced for a fancy dish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is hanging on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A Guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying a dark brown shade on the outer edge of her eyelid, using a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is powdering her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is stepping over a log in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man in a legionnaire uniform is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is jumping on a jumper. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is slicing octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> One girl is knitting while another girl is talking to her. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is cutting a red piece of meat into thin strips. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person folds a yellow piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref4">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> The women are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is picking a water-pot. </seg>
<seg id="3"> Men are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is greasing a sheet pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting volleyballs provided by another woman. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A girl plays with her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A girl is riding her horse in training in a riding ring. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a musical keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man in cowboy gear rides a horse in a circle. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing by a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A teenage girl is putting on lip gloss. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is firing with an assault rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is aiming a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is stirring a food with spoon. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man pushes a large tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse drops its rider. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle through a town. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman drives ""The Arnold"" down the street in a convertible. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is putting flour on a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car exploded. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog chews on a stuffed whale toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person is petting a baby sloth. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A moped driver pops a wheely in the street. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person is stirring salad. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is aiming a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is typing keys. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is putting fish into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is seasoning bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a mobile. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is cradling a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing something from a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are rolling big tyre. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A guy is riding a bike on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a hunting knife in a vise. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Meat is being cooked. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A sloth is hanging from some string. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman is putting a small baby in a water pip. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is playing while wearing a diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> SOMEONE SLICING VEGETABLE </seg>
<seg id="56"> A person is adding cumin seeds in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting chicken wings into a plastic storage container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading a message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Someone dumps a bowl of meat into a skillet and starts cooking it. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is fitting silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle and fishes are swimming under the water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is whisking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding a motorcycle down the street. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A couple are walking through a forest. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing the violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> Someone is cleaning a animal. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is relaxing on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A patient is lying in the operating room. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A BOY IS CUTTING A GRASS BY SCISSOR. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man sliced a robe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is fighting with a man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A chef is sauteing garlic and onions in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is climbing into a storage box. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A chef sautes food in a large pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman pours meat into a hot wok and mixes it around. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone cracked to eggs into a bowl </seg>
<seg id="88"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog is wagging its tail. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A woman is boiling noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> The women are singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A small child is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is jumping to a car top. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing drums </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The men boxed in the ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man is doing back flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing something from a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The men are having a conversation. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman are running toward the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is fitting silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing and signing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing the electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman does exercises on a floor mat. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A chef is slicing a bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man in cowboy gear rides a horse in a circle. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing a polygon with an X inside it. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing a video game on a laptop computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is doing some skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman reads a book on a rock. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is cutting a tomato into chunks. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping garlic with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding an amphibian. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man rises from a swamp. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is lounging around. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing a eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> Two kids are doing a magic trick. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group plays soccer at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is cutting a snack. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man cuts an onion with a butcher's knife. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a rifle with bullets. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting chicken wings into a plastic storage container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A brick is being broken on a mans body. </seg>
<seg id="148"> Two kids are doing a magic trick. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a shoe. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A cake is decorated with slices of strawberry. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is firing a shotgun down a range. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is hugging a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is delivering a speech on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is dangling a mouse near a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is tossing a ball with his feet. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is moving in the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is scooping pasta from a plate into a pan of sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of caribou are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman beats two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is boiling finger in the water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A model train is riding on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A BOY IS CUTTING A GRASS BY SCISSOR. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is speaking to soldiers standing in attention. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Two men are speaking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man does a backflip off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading a message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a human skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person dices a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a shoe. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is singing on a foggy stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing against a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A group of people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is lounging around. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is chopping up garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman drives ""The Arnold"" down the street in a convertible. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating various foods. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two babies are sitting in high chairs. </seg>
<seg id="199"> SOMEONE SLICING VEGETABLE </seg>
<seg id="200"> A person is mixing a meaty mixture in a glass bowl with a wooden spoon. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs in a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman beats two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping a tree trunk with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy fish is swimming in the water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is cradling a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman cuts a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling under sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A person is slicing a garlic into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> a man is talking on the telephone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man in a library is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man in a chef's hat is cleaning off the edge of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger is playing. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is cutting a tomato into chunks. </seg>
<seg id="223"> Man chops meat and puts it in a plate. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is climbing down a rope. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying cosmetics to her eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A girl is applying make-up with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is stepping over a log in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A person is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is riding a horse along a perimeter. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A couple of girls are sitting on a couch crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A person is slicing a meat into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref5">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three individuals do aerobic exercises. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is picking a can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is sliding on his forehead across the floor. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A couple of men are fighting in a corral full of cattle. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person is buttering a tray. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is hitting volleyballs. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl fusses with and brushes her wet hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse along the perimeter of a fenced area. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing the piano with a bass base. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse in the desert. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is applying lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is firing with a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A person is stirring a pot of chili on a stove. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a branch from a walking path. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse is falling in the sand. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman drives a man in her car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is adding flour to meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind 4 people. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog chews on a tennis shoe. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is petting a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person does wheelies on a motor scooter. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A person is stirring together ingredients in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is sitting in a chair playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is firing with a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling of a room. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is putting shrimp into a batter. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a piano keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is seasoning buttered bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking around a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking in phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is holding a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a white horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is wiping off a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man is doing bicycle tricks. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a knife to a machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting a skinny potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is frying something in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A animal is hanging from a string. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is playing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> Woman cuts cucomber very thinly. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A cook seasons some sausage. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting chicken to a box. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading a romantic email message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is frying a meat in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat is jumping into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> Someone is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A sea turtle is hunting for fish. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A couple is walking in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is mixing eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding a motorized bicycle through a town. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and woman is walking together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing a fiddle on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person is washing his pet rat. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is playing guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying in a chair by a lake. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A wounded man lying on the operation table is moving his legs and hands as doctors are treating him. </seg>
<seg id="79"> Someone is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is practicing martial arts moves with a man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> Someone is putting ingredients into a wok. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a box. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A cook stirs ingredients in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman pours the contents of a bowl into a hot wok and stirs it with a pair of tongs. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A person is adding eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> chopping vegitables </seg>
<seg id="89"> A dog on the bed growls as the camera approaches, </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling of a room. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A woman is putting noodles into boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two officers danced on the floor with the band. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A little kid is standing on a couch playing an acoustic guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl appears to be jumping from the ground to the top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is sitting in a chair playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping at a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two boxers fight each other in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Different children jump on different trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is wiping off a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two Indian men have a conversation. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="113"> Actor Surya is walking. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing and singing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A person is slicing potatoes into fries. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman exercise her ab muscles on a floor mat. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a french bread loaf. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse in the desert. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is cutting grass with machine. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing on a digital dry erase board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is playing computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> Someone is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is doing stunts on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down the road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is making scrambled egg. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is slicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding frog in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="135"> Actor Surya is walking. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is climbing up from mud water. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is lying on logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing egg plant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Boys are playing football at the sea-shore. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is cutting a snake to cook. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting an onion into slices. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting chicken to a box. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man is breaking a concrete slab placed over a man's chest. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting through a cowboy boot with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef carefully places straberries on his cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> chopping vegitables </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at a target with a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a doll. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is giving a lecture. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is feeding a mice to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with ball in office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is on water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man pours a plate of shredded cheese into a pot of sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking around a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting on stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of deer are crossing a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is adding cut green beans to boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy car is hit by a toy train. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An air plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting a potato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A couple of men are fighting in a corral full of cattle. </seg>
<seg id="172"> Someone is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is cutting sweet potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is speaking to some soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A an is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Two guys are talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding away on a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is diving in the swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading a romantic email message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is cutting sweet potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person is chopping garlic cloves. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting through a cowboy boot with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is playing in silhouette. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing onstage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing against a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is sitting in a chair playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Peoples are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is lying on logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is breaking an egg on the side of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person is slicing food with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman drives a man in her car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating food while his stomach grows bigger. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezed and scared another baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> Woman cuts cucomber very thinly. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A raw meat mixture is being stirred in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping a log with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is laying on a mat on the floor doing abdominal exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy fish is moving in water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing on a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is holding a baby kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A person is slicing an onion into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> chopping vegitables </seg>
<seg id="215"> A person is slicing ginger with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting sweet potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is taking on his mobile. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting a potato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A chef is preparing some food. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A baby tiger plays with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="223"> some one preparing nonveg </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding away on a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman swings down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A person is slicing an onion into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye liner to her eyelid using an eye pencil. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is applying cosmetics to her face with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man is stepping over a tree in woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man in a hat is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is bouncing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is cutting something. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Women are stitching. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A person is cutting meat into strips with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking around a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a potato into pieces with a knife. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref6">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three kids are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is picking up a water can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man slides across a wrestling ring on his head. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person is greasing a pan. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is practicing volley ball. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is brushing her wet hair in the mirror. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse in an open enclosed ground. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse on an open ground. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is making sound with finger. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A young woman is applying lip gloss to her lips. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is firing an assault rifle into a hill. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is pulling the hammer on a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A ]person is stirring something in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a large tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A horse stumbles and falls after a jump and the rider is knocked off. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman driving a car is having a conversation with her male passenger. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is flouring a piece of pork. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind a group of guys. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is chewing on a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A woman is stroking a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is doing a wheeling on his bike. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is stirring cooked vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is pulling the hammer on a revolver. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling, while a group of spectators are dancing on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A man is typing. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is placing shrimp in a bowl of sauce. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling seasoning on several split and buttered loaves of bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on the telephone as another man listens. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is wiping a board and speaking to other man. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are tumbling tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man is doing stunts on a bicycle ramp. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a knife into a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is frying some meat. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A slow loris is hanging on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman put a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is rolling around in its diaper. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A chef was slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A person is adding seasonings to a pot that is simmering on a stove. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A person is placing meat in a container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is smiling. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is putting meat in a skillet to cook. </seg>
<seg id="60"> Rhinos are grassing. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is swimming in water. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and a woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> Someone is beating some eggs with a whisk. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing en electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman are riding on a motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man and a woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing guitar standing on roof top. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person is washing a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is singing along as he strums the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is taking sun bath on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man dances on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors are trying to revive a man. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is demonstrating a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is showing fight stunts. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A person is frying onion. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a draw and climbing into it. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is cooking food in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> Meat is being cooked. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is pouring an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A chef cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A cook is slicing up an onion and green beans. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A puppy is sitting on a bed with a dog. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling, while a group of spectators are dancing on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A woman puts noodles in a pot of hot water. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two police women are singing and  dancing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is singing and playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> An old woman is breaking egg. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is jumping on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man dances on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Some teenage girls are dancing for the camera. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man dances on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two fighters are punching each other. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives at the tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Kids are doing tricks on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is wiping a board and speaking to other man. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two Indian men have a discussion. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and and woman are running together, holding hands. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking down a path. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting a silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain in a garden. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is singing and playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A person is using a knife to cut a potato into wedges. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is doing exercise in the room. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse on an open ground. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing his backyard. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing on an eraser board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man is working on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is riding a skateboard on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> a woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is preparing an egg in a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman dices a small onion. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man holds a small, slimey frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking down a path. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man rises up from a mud hole. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda rolls around on a stack of logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person with a knife is slicing an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is showing magic. </seg>
<seg id="140"> Rhinos are grassing. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are kicking a ball on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A man is preparing a snake for cooking. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is loading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A person is placing meat in a container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man is breaking a stone slab. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man is showing magic. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a shoe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef covers a cake with strawberries. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A cook is slicing up an onion and green beans. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at some targets. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is giving a speech. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing something. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is feeding a mouse to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> In man is doing tricks with a hacky sack in his office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is swimming on the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person dumps a plate of shredded cheese into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of deer are crossing the street. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is boiling some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train comes round the corner, dashes and throws off a red car parked on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing en electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A animated plane is lifting off a runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant is walking. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding his bike on the road. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is diving into a swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is smiling. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is pouring an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person is cutting garlic into pieces with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a shoe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is playing instruments. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing against baby's face. </seg>
<seg id="190"> a woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing together near a house. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda rolls around on a stack of logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is breaking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person carefully cuts and dices a small onion. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman driving a car is having a conversation with her male passenger. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man eats several different types of food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> Two baby are sitting. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A chef was slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is mixing meat. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man cuts a tree with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="205"> An orangutan is riding a tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Two electric toys are swimming in red water in a bathtub. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman cuts an onion into two and thereafter chops one half of it into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A person is quickly chopping mushrooms with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A cook is slicing up an onion and green beans. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing a piece of ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is cleaning the edge of a container of food. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is slicing a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="223"> the man making fish food </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding his bike on the road. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is descending from a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman cuts an onion into two and thereafter chops one half of it into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye liner. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman applies cosmetics to her face. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man steps over a fallen tree in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing some musical instrument. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is riding their horse in an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is jumping over trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is cutting an octopus tentacle into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A young woman is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A woman is cutting fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a square paper piece. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref7">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A girl is picking up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> Two men are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is attacking another man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person is wiping a pan with butter. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is practicing volleyball serves on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is playing with her hair in the bathroom. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is playing an electric keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is tapping her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is looking at numbers. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman applies lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman fires an assault rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is rolling the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man is stirring the contents of a pan. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is rowing a small boat in a river. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a huge tree branch into a clearing. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A man gets knocked off of a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman driving a car is talking to the man seated beside her. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is seasoning a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind four men standing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is eating a doll. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A loris is raising both its arms to be scratched underneath. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is doing some bike stunts. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is stirring some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is rolling the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person is typing on a stenographer. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman batters a piece of seafood. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing an electric keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning a glass of door. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling seasonings on bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a mobile phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting some paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Two men push monstrous tires along the ground. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man jumps his bike on a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is putting a knife in a vice. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is cutting up a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Someone is cooking meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A loris is hanging on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman is putting her baby in a waste bin. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby is walking. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A cook prepares a vegetable for a meal by slicing and dicing it. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is adding some spice to a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts chicken pieces in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is rubbing his face, and reading. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A woman is adding something to a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A shotgun is being shot off in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is plucking a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting a silencer onto a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle follows some fish around at the bottom of the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and a woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man and woman is riding on a mo-pad. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man, and a woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing the violin on the top of a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person washes a small porcupine in a pan of water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is resting on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors are trying to save an injured man. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A boy is cutting grass. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is doing martial arts moves. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is pouring ingredients into a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a drawer and climbing inside. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is cooking food on a large frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The lady poured a meat mixture into the wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Someone is cracking a egg. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A person is slicing up an onion into little pieces. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog is laying on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding an electric bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Noodles are being boiled. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two uniformed female police officers are dancing and singing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A child is playing guitar, and singing. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A small girl jumps from the ground to the roof of a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> The girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing the drums under spotlight. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are boxing each other in a boxing bout. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man is throwing knives on a distant wooden board fixed on a tree trunk ahead of him. </seg>
<seg id="108"> Kids doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are having a discussion. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and a woman run down a path. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking along a path through wilderness. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting a silencer onto a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is singing on stage as he strums a guitar too. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A potato is being cut. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is doing exercises on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man slices bread with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is mowing the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is drawing some figures. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man plays a game on his laptop computer. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A shotgun is being shot off in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is riding on a skateboard ramp. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A woman is reading. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running on a road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is chopping and slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is mixing yellow and red ingredients in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking along a path through wilderness. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is rising from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A baby panda is laying around. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman cuts up a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man demonstrates his ability to levitate. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are playing soccer on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A person is chopping the head off a snake and taking out its intestines. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting and onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is reloading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts chicken pieces in a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man is breaking a concrete slab on a mans belly with a hammer. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man demonstrates his ability to levitate. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man cuts of the toe end of a boot with a machete. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef is decorating a cake with cherry slices. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is slicing up an onion into little pieces. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at targets with a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is shown standing behind a lectern speaking </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing a bun. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is feeding a rat to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is playing with a hackey sack in an office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat is traversing some waves. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A person with a knife is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is adding rice in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A herd of deer cross a road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is mixing ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> okra is cooking in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train crashes into a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> An air plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is attacking another man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A boy is cutting grass. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A drill sergeant talks to his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A person is chopping a white vegetable with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is making a telephone call. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding his motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is diving off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is rubbing his face, and reading. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A person is dicing garlic. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man cuts of the toe end of a boot with a machete. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band is performing. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing out stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing its face on a small child. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is chopping and slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Some people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A baby panda is laying around. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking a egg. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman driving a car is talking to the man seated beside her. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is eating food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezing scares another baby. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A cook prepares a vegetable for a meal by slicing and dicing it. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is preparing chicken. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A person is mixing ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is chopping wood. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing some exercise. </seg>
<seg id="205"> An orangutan is riding a tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Toys are swimming in a bath of red liquid. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man sings while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is holding a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman cuts up a green onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man dices several mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man dices several mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is crawling upside down under the couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A person is slicing up an onion into little pieces. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking in a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man wearing a suit is talking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A chef wipes off the edge of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A person is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="223"> a man is preparing a dish </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding his motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman cuts up a green onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating food. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye makeup. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A young woman is applying makeup. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A man walks through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman is riding a horse in an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is pouncing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman is slicing octopus with a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A person is cutting a piece of fish into slices. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref8">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A girl picks up a water can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A wrestler throws another wrestler. </seg>
<seg id="4"> People are fighting in a cow pen. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy is sitting in a room playing a piano by lamp light. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person spreads lard on a tray. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is smashing a ball in a practice. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A little girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is striking a table with her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is pointing at a calender on the wall. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is putting on lip color. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is firing an automatic rifle. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring a pot of stew. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man paddles a canoe across a pond. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is moving a tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A man is falling down when he is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man sliced a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is driving a car while speaking with a man. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman puts flour on a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car explodes behind four people. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is playing with a toy. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person rubs a small furry animal. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is doing wheelies on a motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone is stirring a pot of stew. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing a guitar, and humming. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing some drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person types on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is breading shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning glass doors. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling spices on four sliced half loaves of buttered bread. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is pacing in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man talks on a cellphone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man riding a horse is looking around a forest. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalkboard with an eraser. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man on a bicycle jumps high in the air while riding on a metallic sheet curved at both ends. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man trys to break a knife blade. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is frying meet. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A furry animal hangs on a rope. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A woman is putting a baby into a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby plays on furniture. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A cucumber being cut into fine strips. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is seasoning some meat. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is putting chicken in a dish. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man is reading his email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is sauteing meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A person is firring a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is standing in front of a microphone holding a violin in one hand and a violin bow in the other. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is putting together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle walks on the bottom of the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and woman are walking together through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> Someone is beating eggs. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is rocking and playing the guitar on stage. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is dancing . </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A couple are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A young man is standing on a roof, playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A hedgehog is getting a bath. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man sings and plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man lounges on a chair at the beach. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors resuscitate a man. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A young man is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cuts a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A chimpanzee is doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman puts oil and food in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat is opening a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is cooking. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The lady poured the meat mixture into a wok and stirred. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman chops an onion into fine pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog lays on a bed and wags his tail. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding an electric bike on a concrete ground. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing the guitar on a park bench. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Noodles are being mixed. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are dancing and singing in front of a crowd. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A baby is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is pouring eggs into a dish. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl is jumping onto a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing a guitar, and humming. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> The girls danced around the room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are boxing in a ring. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man throws blades at a target on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> People are jumping on trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalkboard with an eraser. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are speaking each other. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man, and a woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man walks along a trail. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is putting together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man playing an electric guitar is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A potato is being sliced into many pieces. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man mows a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is writing on a  school board. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man plays a video game on a laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A person is firring a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is skateboarding on a ramp. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A girl is reading a book outside. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A tomato is sliced into smaller pieces. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running down a road. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman cooks eggs in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is peeling the skin of a ripe papaya using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is chopping onion. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A woman is handling a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man walks along a trail. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man rises up out of a swamp. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is cutting vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is levitating. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A snake is killed and skinned. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is cutting up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man loads a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is putting chicken in a dish. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="147"> One man is breaking cement on another man's chest. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man is levitating. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef is decorating a cake with strawberries. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman chops an onion into fine pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting at targets. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a stuffed toy. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is speaking at a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is splitting a piece of bread. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is holding a white rat by it's tale over an aquarium containing a large snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man plays hackysack in an office. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A boat sails along the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is adding shredded cheese to a pot. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man sliced a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is pacing in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are pawing at each other. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Animals are crossing the road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman stirs eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Someone is boiling some peppers. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train hit a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man is rocking and playing the guitar on stage. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A computerized plane is taking off a runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is cutting potatoes into small cubes. </seg>
<seg id="171"> People are fighting in a cow pen. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A young man is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A man is talking to a group of soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is having a conversation on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding off in a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is doing a back flip into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is reading his email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is playing with man's skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is peeling the skin of a ripe papaya using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A woman finely chops a few garlic pods using a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> People are playing instruments. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is playing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is rubbing it's head against a young child. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing a guitar, and humming. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Teenagers are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> Someone is slicing something </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman is driving a car while speaking with a man. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is stuffing various food items into his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby is surprising another baby with a sneeze. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A cucumber being cut into fine strips. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is stirring a marinade mixture into some beef. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling to eggs in a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman stirs eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a tree trunk using an axe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is doing crunches. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy shark swims in a bathtub full of red water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is cutting mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is cutting mushrooms. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is playing underneath a couch. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman chops an onion into fine pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is cutting potatoes into small cubes. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man speaks while standing in front of a bookcase. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A tomato is sliced into smaller pieces. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A chef was slicing raw fish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding off in a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is descending on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman is peeling potato. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guinea pig is eating. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye makeup. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A woman is applying some bronzing powder to the outer areas of her cheek and temple using a brush. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A person is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman is riding a horse in an arena. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman with a knife is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Two girls are knitting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is cutting some meat. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is pacing in its cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding a yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting potatoes into small cubes. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref9">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> Three people are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A woman is holding a water can. </seg>
<seg id="3"> Men are wrestling. </seg>
<seg id="4"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A boy plays a piano. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A person wipes butter on a tray. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is tossing and hitting volleyballs on the beach, while another woman standing nearby is passing the balls. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A small girl standing in front of the bathroom mirror is straightening her hair using her fingers and then combs it with a hair brush. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> An individual's right hand plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A man is playing on his keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A girl taps her fingernails on the counter. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A boy is pointing at days on a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A girl is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman standing on grassland is holding a rifle and shooting a series of bullets in the air. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A man is shooting a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="19"> Someone is stirring soup. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is carrying a tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A man is falling from horse. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man slices a peeled potato into thick slices and thereafter cuts each of them into half. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A woman is putting flour onto some meat. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A car is blasting. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A dog is playing with its stuffed toy whale. </seg>
<seg id="29"> Someone is petting a monkey. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is performing tricks on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Someone is stirring a pot. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is shooting a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="36"> Someone is using a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A woman is battering food to deep fry. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is cleaning the windows of two glass doors, using a couple of squegees. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is sprinkling spices over buttered bread slices. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man rides a horse through a river bed. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A guy cuts paper. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Men are moving tires. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A man on a bike performs jumps on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is clamping a knife into a vise. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A woman is cooking meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A monkey is hanging from some string. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A girl is putting a baby in a garbage can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A baby wearing only a diaper is walking and playing around actively in the house. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A lady is taking the top and bottom off a cucumber, then chops it length-wise into long thin pieces. </seg>
<seg id="56"> Someone is putting seasonings in a pot of sausage. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man puts wings into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Someone is reading an email. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A person is frying meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A guy is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man played an instrument and sang into a microphone on stage. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man modifies the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A man and a woman walk through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A person is whisking eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man jams on his electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A man is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is riding a motorcycle with a woman passenger. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="72"> Two people are walking. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is playing a fiddle on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="74"> An animal is being bathed. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A man is laying on a lounge. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> Doctors tend to an injured man lying on a gurney. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A teenager cuts a clump of grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cuts a thick rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A monkey is practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is frying onions. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is toasting nuts in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The woman is cooking meat in a wok. </seg>
<seg id="86"> a woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A person breaks an egg into a small bowl. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A woman cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A small dog lies on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A man is riding on a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A man is playing the guitar seated on a bench in an outdoor location. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Noodles are cooking in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two women are dancing and singing. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A kid is singing. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A girl jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is riding on a bike with his luggage. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is chopping down a very large tree. </seg>
<seg id="103"> Three girls are dancing in the room. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two men are boxing on the rope-stage. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A man throws knives at a target hanging on a tree. </seg>
<seg id="108"> People do flips on trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Two men are speaking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man and woman are running outside. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man modifies the barrel of a gun. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="116"> Jimi Hendrix is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A potato is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A woman is exercising her abs. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is slicing a whole bread loaf using a bread knife. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A guy is mowing the lawn. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A person is drawing on a large touchscreen. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A man using a laptop. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A guy is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A man is skateboarding. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A girl is reading a book. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A woman is cutting a tomato into small chunks. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is dicing an onion using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A woman is slicing a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A woman is mincing some garlic. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is emerging from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man appears to levitate off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are playing soccer on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A snake is prepared to be eaten. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man loads a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man puts wings into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A man breaks a stone. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A man appears to levitate off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A man is cutting a boot in half with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A chef is placing strawberries on top of a cake. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A woman cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is shooting shotgun slugs across a hill. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A baby is playing with a toy beaver. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is speaking at a podium. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A man is slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A man is showing a rat to snake. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is kicking around a foot bag. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man stands on the deck of a ship. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Someone dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A person is pouring cheese into a pot of red sauce. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man slices a peeled potato into thick slices and thereafter cuts each of them into half. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Two cats are playing while sitting on stools. </seg>
<seg id="164"> dears are passing the road. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is scrambling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A woman is adding vegetables to a pot. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A toy train is hitting a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A man jams on his electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A plane takes off of a runway. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="171"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A teenager cuts a clump of grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A man is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is talking on a cell phone while sitting in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is riding on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is doing a backwards double-flip off a diving board and into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="179"> Someone is reading an email. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A man is providing voice to a skull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> a woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is slicing a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A woman is chopping up garlic. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A man is cutting a boot in half with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A band performs in silhouette. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A cat is snuggling a baby. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is dicing an onion using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="192"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A woman is chopping garlic. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A woman is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man stuffing his face with food. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A baby sneezes. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A lady is taking the top and bottom off a cucumber, then chops it length-wise into long thin pieces. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A woman is stirring meat in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A woman is boiling two eggs in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is scrambling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man chopping a tree. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A toy fish is swimming. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A man is singing a song while simultaneously strumming his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A woman is picking up a kangaroo. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A man is rapidly chopping some mushrooms using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A man is rapidly chopping some mushrooms using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cat is pulling itself under a sofa. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A man is wiping food from a bowls rim. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A tiger cub is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is cutting a tomato into small chunks. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A cook is slicing fish. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A man is riding on a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is climbing down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A woman pealing a potato </seg>
<seg id="228"> A guineapig eats a piece of carrot. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A woman is applying eye make-up. </seg>
<seg id="230"> a indian girl puffing power on here </seg>
<seg id="231"> The man is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is playing the harp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A woman cuts up a piece of octopus. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Two women are crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Someone is cutting raw fish. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A tiger is walking in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
</mteval>
