<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
                  <mteval>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref0">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A man is holding a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A boy made a skull ""talk"" by moving the mouth with his hands. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man playing the accordion. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man cuts throw a rope, suspended from the ceiling, with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A boy is beating other boy by stick. </seg>
<seg id="7"> Someone is slicing raw meat into strips. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Someone is peeling cooked shrimp with their fingers then cutting into it lengthwise with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse when the video flashes to a man. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A young girl seated on stage is playing a baby-grand piano. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A group of men are playing basketball. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A raccoon-like animal is holding and eating something orange. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man inserts the tip of a large knife into a vise and pulls the knife towards him, then removes the knife and appears to be checking the blade for straightness. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A rhinoceros is grazing in the grass. </seg>
<seg id="17"> a old man playing the piano with his head </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman drops down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man is crying while tying a rope into a noose. </seg>
<seg id="20"> a person cutting a potatoes </seg>
<seg id="21"> A dog is at waiting at the counter. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A monkey pulls a dogs tail, runs away, then comes back and yanks at the dog's leg, again running away. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is giving a lecture on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A woman is tapping her nails. </seg>
<seg id="25"> a soccer player making a goal </seg>
<seg id="26"> A monkey is riding a bicycle with training wheels in circles. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A young girl lying in a bed appears to wake up. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A young man is running beside a truck being driven down the road. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A person is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man slicing butter into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is playing the key board. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A woman is slicing some potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A woman is scrambling eggs and spices in a glass bowl with a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man using a microwave </seg>
<seg id="36"> A person is cutting beef. </seg>
<seg id="37"> Someone is burning the tops of two cameras with a torch. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man in a suit is standing at a microphone and singing. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A guy is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> The group Slayer plays a song onstage. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A boy is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A woman is frying food. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A man wearing glasses and a suit is standing and talking in front of a huge bookshelf. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man puts cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A woman is peeling a potato with a peeler. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A woman is slicing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A woman is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="48"> hamster eating cheese </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone pours oil from a bottle into a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A woman cuts a green bell pepper in half, removes the seeds, and cuts it into chunks. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A boy is checking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man eats a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A boy does flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A woman is cutting partially peeled zucchini into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is playing the key board. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A demonstration of how to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A chef cooking food </seg>
<seg id="59"> A raccoon-like animal is hanging off two ropes suspended from the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Someone quarters a tomato using a cleaver. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A lion is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="63"> Jimmy Hendrix performing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A young man is hammering nails into a strip of wood with a camera. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A woman cuts up some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is stuffing all kinds of food into his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is felling a tree. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat stares out of the window. </seg>
<seg id="70"> An infant speaks into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man shoots two different guns. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man is eating a banana. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A person pealing potatoes </seg>
<seg id="74"> A rhinoceros is grazing in the grass. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man kneeling next to a woman lying on the floor keeps patting her back as they talk. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A boy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A boy is singing in the street. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A car is driven. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man cuts the toe off a brown boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is smiling as he reads an email message. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is peeling a potato with a peeler. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A man is making a call on his mobile. </seg>
<seg id="84"> a women cutting broccoli up </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A boy is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is window cleaning. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is adding spices on a bread. </seg>
<seg id="89"> a woman cutting chicken and vegetables </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is running down a street and the scene flashes to a man and woman bowing. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A fishing is chasing a boy. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A woman deep fries a coated pork chop using chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A man plays a violin on the roof of a house. </seg>
<seg id="94"> a girl in  the ocean on jet skii </seg>
<seg id="95"> A cook spreads butter on a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A lady cooking meat in a pan </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is lying on a lounge chair on the beach partially covered by a beach umbrella. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A panda looking dog is walking down a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A dog is bouncing his front paws on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="100"> The woman is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A dog barks at the screen. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man appears to be draining water off of pasta in a plastic container into a sink. </seg>
<seg id="103"> a man is peeling an apple </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man puts together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman, with one arm raised, is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A monkey pulls a dogs tail, runs away, then comes back and yanks at the dog's leg, again running away. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A demonstration of how to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A gray rabbit is playing with a stuffed white rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is wiping off the edge of a bowl filled with food with a paper towel. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man slicing a bun in half with a knife appears to cut himself. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is playing a large flute-like instrument. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is playing a keyboard piano. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> Someone pours olive oil into a bowl of tomato wedges. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A cat is standing on it's back paws and appears to be boxing with it's front paws. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A car is driven. </seg>
<seg id="120"> a chef cutting a carrot </seg>
<seg id="121"> A young girl seated on stage is playing a baby-grand piano. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A demonstration of how to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A woman is cutting shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is eating spaghetti from a large bowl while standing. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A woman is filling a pitcher with water. </seg>
<seg id="126"> a person walking through the woods </seg>
<seg id="127"> A boy does flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A lemur is holding up it's arms and someone is scratching him. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A clown is singing. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A man is cutting a piece of paper in half lengthwise using scissors. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A woman and a man are holding hands and running towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man drills holes into a board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A boy cutting grass at the edge of a sidewalk turns and yells something. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man slices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="137"> a person cutting a potatoes </seg>
<seg id="138"> The lady is filing her nails. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A woman demonstrating abdominal exercises. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A man fishing in the ocean </seg>
<seg id="142"> The girl is using sign  language. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A woman is firing a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A tiger club is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man rides a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A man is driving a car, and the man and woman passenger are smiling at each other. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A young woman is curling her hair with a round hairbrush. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A monkey is walking on water. </seg>
<seg id="149"> Two men are dancing like robots on stage. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lion is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="151"> Someone pours oil from a bottle into a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A woman is placing eggs into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A girl applied eye makeup with a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="154"> Three men are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is squeezing a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A boy is checking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="157"> a group of people dancing </seg>
<seg id="158"> A young man is running beside a truck being driven down the road. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A black colored pet dog is biting a stuffed toy fish. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A potato is being cut on a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man petting a crocodile. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A couple of policewomen are singing karaoke. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman slices a raw potato with the skin on. </seg>
<seg id="164"> The woman is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man enters a room. </seg>
<seg id="167"> a person playing a piano </seg>
<seg id="168"> A girl is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="170"> Someone is holding and petting a baby tiger. </seg>
<seg id="171"> a man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A girl wearing glasses is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is mowing the grass with a lawn mower. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A boy is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman cuts tofu into square cubes. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A group of men are running behind another man and mimicking all his actions. </seg>
<seg id="177"> Someone is dicing green onions. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is using an electric whisk. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A chef pours oil into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A kitten drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A white kitten is on a table lapping milk from a plate. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Someone is showing how to cut an onion in half. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A woman is holding a microphone and a bird is talking into it while three contestants laugh. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A kitten drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A young woman is dancing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A person is peeling the skin off a potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="187"> a man is cooking an egg </seg>
<seg id="188"> Jimmy Hendrix performing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="189"> a boy walking over a bridge </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is coating a pork chop with flour. </seg>
<seg id="191"> Paper is being cut with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="192"> The men are running a race. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A girl is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A man, wearing a billed hat, is playing the harp. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man playing a guitar on a bench. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A chef is preparing a snake for dinning. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is smiling as he reads an email message. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A chef doing a demonstration about slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="202"> a person playing a piano </seg>
<seg id="203"> A woman pours a clear liquid on both sides of a raw fish on a plate with a measuring spoon. </seg>
<seg id="204"> a guy typing on a computer </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman dances in front of a fire. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A man is giving a lecture on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A woman dances in the rain out side. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat sitting on the back edge of a couch jumps up and is rotated around a ceiling fan then tossed off. </seg>
<seg id="209"> Someone folds a flour tortilla with cheese in half in a metal pan, using their fingers and a spatula. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A little puppy is turning on its back. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A little puppy is turning on its back. </seg>
<seg id="212"> Three young men run, jump, and kick off of a Coke machine. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cheetah is chasing prey. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman carrying a baby puts him in a garbage can. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A cat is drinking water out of a faucet. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A man is climbing up a knotted rope suspended from the ceiling, when the scene flashes to the same man splashing water on his face from an outdoor container. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A baby gets licked by a dog. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A woman cracks an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man rides a street bike through the town. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is eating corn on the cob. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A chef boils noodles. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl applied eye makeup with a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A woman is slicing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is cutting partially peeled zucchini into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="226"> An airplane takes off and the wheels are drawn up inside the plane. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is tasting something from a bowl with a spoon while speaking. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A small red car is being driven down a road. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A boy is playing a cello. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A young boy playing guitar </seg>
<seg id="231"> A woman is thinly slicing a white translucent with pinkish rind looking vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is slicing the tape on a box to open it. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone stirs chopped vegetables in a kettle with a wooden spatula. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A black pet cat is walking in the house. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A guy is in water. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A small dog goes to the edge of the dock. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A guy levitates off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="238"> Lionel Richie dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A person is cutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A shirtless man is sitting in an armchair. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A man is playing the key board. </seg>
<seg id="242"> a person cutting a potatoes </seg>
<seg id="243"> Four men sawing on a log flashes to four men running in a field carrying something long on their shoulders. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A cat plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A badger digs a hole. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A girl jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="247"> A boy eating cereal, while talking to a girl. </seg>
<seg id="248"> A monkey is brushing the hair of a large white dog. </seg>
<seg id="249"> A man in a construction hat is dancing while two other seated men watch. </seg>
<seg id="250"> A man is slicing the tape on a box to open it. </seg>
<seg id="251"> A panda is sitting eating some kind of plant matter. </seg>
<seg id="252"> A man rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="253"> A cat playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="254"> Lionel Richie dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="255"> Three boys doing art work. </seg>
<seg id="256"> a man riding a bike on a half pipe </seg>
<seg id="257"> A person slices a bread. </seg>
<seg id="258"> A man is slicing a row of mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="259"> Two men are rolling huge tires sideways down a street while spectators watch. </seg>
<seg id="260"> Two men are fighting, and one man hits the other man on his head with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="261"> A monkey is karate kicking at someone's gloved hand. </seg>
<seg id="262"> A kid is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="263"> A man is loading his gun. </seg>
<seg id="264"> A man gets excited about the fire he lit. </seg>
<seg id="265"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="266"> A woman is scrambling eggs and spices in a glass bowl with a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="267"> A boy eating cereal, while talking to a girl. </seg>
<seg id="268"> A woman pours a sauce and some minced substance into a glass bowl containing meat. </seg>
<seg id="269"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="270"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="271"> A girl is doing make-up on her cheeks and forehead with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="272"> A woman stirs beef in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="273"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="274"> Someone is peeling an onion with their fingers. </seg>
<seg id="275"> a girl in  the ocean on jet skii </seg>
<seg id="276"> a person playing a piano </seg>
<seg id="277"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="278"> A man slicing butter into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="279"> A man puts together a gun. </seg>
<seg id="280"> A girl is riding a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="281"> A man puts cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="282"> A man does a magic card trick. </seg>
<seg id="283"> A gray rabbit is playing with a stuffed white rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="284"> A woman is placing skewers of meat on some kind of cooking apparatus. </seg>
<seg id="285"> A man puts cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="286"> A man cliff dives into the water. </seg>
<seg id="287"> A woman pours a liquid and seasonings in a small glass bowl and whips them with a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="288"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="289"> A woman dips a shrimp in batter. </seg>
<seg id="290"> Someone dices carrots into small pieces and adds them to a salad. </seg>
<seg id="291"> A band is performing on stage with fire in the background. </seg>
<seg id="292"> A man close up with crooked teeth speaks. </seg>
<seg id="293"> A man rides his horse in the dessert. </seg>
<seg id="294"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="295"> Someone is sewing quilt squares on a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="296"> A woman cuts up some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="297"> A man eats a piece of bread. </seg>
<seg id="298"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="299"> A man walking down the street singing is carrying suitcases on his head and a woman, with her arms around his neck, on his back. </seg>
<seg id="300"> A woman carrying a baby puts him in a garbage can. </seg>
<seg id="301"> A man is cleaning his sink. </seg>
<seg id="302"> A woman gallops on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="303"> Someone is cutting red bell peppers into thin slices. </seg>
<seg id="304"> A cat rubs up against an infant </seg>
<seg id="305"> A woman is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="306"> A squirrel is moving in circles. </seg>
<seg id="307"> Someone is scrubbing a zucchini with a brush under the running water from a faucet at a sink. </seg>
<seg id="308"> a man riding a bike on a half pipe </seg>
<seg id="309"> A man is mowing the grass with a lawn mower. </seg>
<seg id="310"> A woman peels a potato. </seg>
<seg id="311"> A man playing a guitar on a bench. </seg>
<seg id="312"> A monkey is karate kicking at someone's gloved hand. </seg>
<seg id="313"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="314"> Two men are boxing. </seg>
<seg id="315"> A girl is doing make-up on her cheeks and forehead with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="316"> A boy plays a flute. </seg>
<seg id="317"> A man is playing on drums. </seg>
<seg id="318"> A man is cutting a piece of paper in half lengthwise using scissors. </seg>
<seg id="319"> A woman is slicing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="320"> A monkey is karate kicking at someone's gloved hand. </seg>
<seg id="321"> A baby plays around in his diaper. </seg>
<seg id="322"> hamster eating cheese </seg>
<seg id="323"> A person riding a mechanical bull </seg>
<seg id="324"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="325"> A woman is putting on lipstick with a brush and talking. </seg>
<seg id="326"> A man rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="327"> A woman is stir frying pieces of meat using chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="328"> A man karate chops multiple boards while another man watches. </seg>
<seg id="329"> A dog barks at a walking electronic chicken. </seg>
<seg id="330"> A little girl is doing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="331"> A man breaks a slab of concrete that is lying on a prone man with a sledge hammer. </seg>
<seg id="332"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="333"> A person is cutting beef. </seg>
<seg id="334"> A cat is sliding under a couch. </seg>
<seg id="335"> a man and woman riding in a car </seg>
<seg id="336"> Two teams of men are playing soccer on a grass field. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref1">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A person holds a frog. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man holding a skull in his hands is moving its jaws while he does the talking. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is playing a keyboard instrument. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man with a sword slices a rope. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A boy smacks a mans back with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman slices a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A person peels shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A girl is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A group of people are playing basketball. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A slow loris is eating. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man puts a knife in a vice. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A rhino is eating on a field. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A man is playing a piano with his nose. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman climbs down a vine and kneels by a cage. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man ties a noose. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A cook cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A dog is in a newsstand. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A monkey attacks a dog. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man gave a speech from a podium. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A woman with purple fingernails is drumming her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A goal is made in soccer. </seg>
<seg id="26"> An orangutan is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A girl wakes up from bed. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man runs with a truck. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A child is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man cut up butter into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A guy is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="33"> a girl cutting in pottato </seg>
<seg id="34"> A person whisks eggs. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man heated a cup of coffee in the microwave. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman cuts a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A person is blow torching cameras. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is singing onstage. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing a guitar in the room. </seg>
<seg id="40"> The rock star performed with his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A boy is playing on a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A woman is deep frying a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is sprinkling shredded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="46"> a woman is slicing a vegetable </seg>
<seg id="47"> A woman is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A baby guinea pig is nibbling on a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person pours oil in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A woman is slicing peppers. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A boy is checking a calender. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is taking a bite of pizza. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A boy is doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A woman chops an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A guy is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="57"> The woman is dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A chef is cooking breadcrumbs in a large pan. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A slow loris hanging on a cord. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A man is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A lion is walking in an enclosed area. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A band is singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man hammers a nail with a camera. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A woman is chopping a onion. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A baby panda relaxes on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is hogging noodles and ice cream. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is cutting a trunk with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A baby boy is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man fires a carbine and a handgun. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man eats a banana very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is peeling a large raw potato using a vegetable peeler. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A rhino is eating on a field. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is waking up a woman. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is singing as he walks down a street. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A car is shown driving through a parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man checks his e-mail. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A man is making a cell phone call. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A person cuts up a stalk of broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is whisking two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man cleans a building glass door. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is making garlic bread. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A chef is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A young child is running around in circles trying to evade the fish on the rod he is holding, when he drops the pole and runs off. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A person is frying a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A man is standing on a roof top playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A girl is on jet skiis. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A cook spreads Crisco on a pan. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A girl is putting meat from a plastic packet into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is laying on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A dog is running with a person. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A dog is on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A woman slices some kind of seafood in chunks. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A dog barks excitedly. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is emptying a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A man is peeling the skin of a fig. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is adding a silencer to a gun. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman rides an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A monkey attacks a dog. </seg>
<seg id="107"> The woman is dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A rabbit plays with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A person is cleaning a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man slices bread. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man plays a flute. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is playing a keyboard piano. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man pours olive oil over tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A car is shown driving through a parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A carrot is being cut. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A girl is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="122"> The woman is dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A person slices a shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is eating. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A boy is filling a pitcher with water. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A man crosses a fallen tree trunk, as he is treading on dried leaves in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A boy is doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is tickling a slow loris. </seg>
<seg id="129"> Several people in clown costumes appear to be singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A man cuts a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man drilled holes into a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A chef slices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A cook cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="138"> Someone is filing their fingernails with an emery board. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A girl is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A man is cutting a potato in half. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A fisher tries to pull in his catch. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A girl is speaking using sign language. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A girl is spraying the field with a gun. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A baby tiger is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is riding a bicycle around a parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="146"> Two people are riding a car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A monkey is wading across a marsh. </seg>
<seg id="149"> Two men are robot dancing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lion is walking in an enclosed area. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person pours oil in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A woman cooks scrambled eggs. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A girl is making eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="154"> Three men wrapped in towels are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="155"> Someone is juicing a lemon using a glass juicer. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A boy is checking a calender. </seg>
<seg id="157"> The men danced in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man runs with a truck. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A doberman pincher is chewing on a toy. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man cubing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is patting an alligator on the mouth. </seg>
<seg id="162"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman slices some kind of seafood in chunks. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is entering a door. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A female plays an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A person is holding a baby tiger. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man cuts a potato into sections. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A girl is playing on a clarinet. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is mowing grass. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A boy is playing on a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman slices tofu. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Men are running. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A person chops green onions. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is using a hand mixer to mix the contents of a mixing bowl. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is adding an oil into the pan. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A cat drinks milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A bird is talking on a mic. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cat drinks milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A woman is dancing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A potato is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A band is singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A boy crossed a hanging bridge. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman brushes flour on a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A person cuts a piece of blue paper. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Men are running a race. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A woman is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A fish is being cleaned and cut into pieces for Chinese cooking. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man checks his e-mail. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A chef cuts a potato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A woman pours oil on a fish. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is describing the game he is playing on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A lady danced in front of a bonfire. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A man gave a speech from a podium. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A girl dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is spun by a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A person folds a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A dog is rolling from side to side. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A dog is rolling from side to side. </seg>
<seg id="212"> Three men bounce off a soda machine. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A panther is running after a deer. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman puts a baby in a trashcan. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A cat is drinking water from a faucet. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A baby boy is playing with a dog. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man gets on a motorcycle and rides it out of an area of chairs and onto the street. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is eating corn on the cob. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A cook puts some noodles in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A man is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is making eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="224"> a woman is slicing a vegetable </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman chops an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A plane lifts off. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is eating. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A man is riding a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A boy is playing a cello. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A boy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A person slices ginger. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is opening a box using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A man mixes vegetables in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A cat explores the kitchen. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A guy is riding a boogie board. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A brown dog reluctant to jump is walking along the edge of a diving board barking at a yellow ball which is floating in the water. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A young man standing on the ground appears to levitate, and another young man runs his hand along the space created below the first man's shoes </seg>
<seg id="238"> A man danced on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A fish is being gutted. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man without a shirt is sitting on a chair. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A guy is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A cook cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="243"> People are cutting wood. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A black cat is deftly playing the piano using her right fore paw. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A badger is burrowing a hole. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A girls jumps on a car. </seg>
<seg id="247"> A boy looks at something while he eats. </seg>
<seg id="248"> A monkey is brushing a dog. </seg>
<seg id="249"> A man with a hard hat is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="250"> A man is opening a box using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="251"> A panda is eating bamboo. </seg>
<seg id="252"> A man is riding a black horse. </seg>
<seg id="253"> A black pet cat is playing the piano using its right forepaw. </seg>
<seg id="254"> A man danced on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="255"> A man is adding finishing touches to a drawing on paper. </seg>
<seg id="256"> A bicycle rider is doing tricks on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="257"> Someone is slicing pieces of bread from a loaf of french bread. </seg>
<seg id="258"> A man is shown chopping several potatoes into small pieces using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="259"> Two men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="260"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="261"> A chimp is kicking a target. </seg>
<seg id="262"> A girl is playing a violin on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="263"> A man cleans his gun. </seg>
<seg id="264"> A man is burning a book of matches. </seg>
<seg id="265"> A bald man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="266"> A person whisks eggs. </seg>
<seg id="267"> A boy looks at something while he eats. </seg>
<seg id="268"> A woman puts ingredients on beef. </seg>
<seg id="269"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="270"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="271"> A woman is applying makeup to her face. </seg>
<seg id="272"> A lady mixed meat and spices together. </seg>
<seg id="273"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="274"> A person peels an onion. </seg>
<seg id="275"> A girl is on jet skiis. </seg>
<seg id="276"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="277"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="278"> A man cut up butter into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="279"> A man is adding a silencer to a gun. </seg>
<seg id="280"> A Baby girl is playing with her tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="281"> A man is sprinkling shredded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="282"> A man does a magic card trick. </seg>
<seg id="283"> A rabbit plays with a stuffed animal. </seg>
<seg id="284"> A person sets kebabs on a grill. </seg>
<seg id="285"> A man is sprinkling shredded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="286"> A man dived off the cliffs. </seg>
<seg id="287"> A woman puts ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="288"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="289"> A woman dips shrimp into a batter. </seg>
<seg id="290"> A person chops carrots. </seg>
<seg id="291"> A band plays onstage. </seg>
<seg id="292"> A man brings his face really close and says,"" My name is Mud"". </seg>
<seg id="293"> A cowboy rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="294"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="295"> A person is sewing with a machine. </seg>
<seg id="296"> A woman is chopping a onion. </seg>
<seg id="297"> A man eats bread. </seg>
<seg id="298"> A man is walking down a dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="299"> A man is carrying a woman on his back. </seg>
<seg id="300"> A woman puts a baby in a trashcan. </seg>
<seg id="301"> A man adds a scoop of Oxi Clean powder to a sink half filled with warm water and mixes it with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="302"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="303"> A man chops a pepper. </seg>
<seg id="304"> A black and white colored cat is snuggling itself against a baby's face. </seg>
<seg id="305"> A woman is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="306"> A girl is running in circles. </seg>
<seg id="307"> A woman is scrubbing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="308"> A bicycle rider is doing tricks on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="309"> A man is mowing grass. </seg>
<seg id="310"> A man is peeling a potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="311"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="312"> A chimp is kicking a target. </seg>
<seg id="313"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="314"> A man is karate kicking at another man wearing protective boxing gloves. </seg>
<seg id="315"> A woman is applying makeup to her face. </seg>
<seg id="316"> A boy is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="317"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="318"> A man cuts a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="319"> a woman is slicing a vegetable </seg>
<seg id="320"> A chimp is kicking a target. </seg>
<seg id="321"> A baby bounces around a room. </seg>
<seg id="322"> A baby guinea pig is nibbling on a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="323"> A boy is playing bull riding game. </seg>
<seg id="324"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="325"> A woman is painting her lips. </seg>
<seg id="326"> A man is riding a black horse. </seg>
<seg id="327"> A person is cooking beef. </seg>
<seg id="328"> A man is breaking wooden boards with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="329"> A dog is barking at a mechanical chicken. </seg>
<seg id="330"> A girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="331"> A man </seg>
<seg id="332"> A man is walking down a dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="333"> A woman cuts a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="334"> A cat is crawling on its back under a couch. </seg>
<seg id="335"> A man and a woman are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="336"> A man is playing soccer. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref2">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man holding a skull is talking while manipulating the skull to look like it is talking. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man slices rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A man is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A boy spanks a man with a plastic sword. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is slicing fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A woman is peeling a shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A little girl is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A group of people play basketball. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A slow loris is eating. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man puts a knife into a vice. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A rhino is eating. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A man is playing a piano with his nose. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man is tying a noose. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man cuts a potato at both ends and thereafter slices it into thick strips. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A dog is looking around </seg>
<seg id="22"> A monkey pulls the tail of a dog. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man gave a speech from the lectern. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A group of men are playing soccer. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A monkey is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A girls wakes up from bed. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is running down the road when a truck drives past him. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A kid is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man cutting butter into a mixing bowl. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is playing a key-board by one hand. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="33"> The girl is cutting a potato into several slices. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A woman whisks two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is operating a microwave oven. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman cuts up some meat. </seg>
<seg id="37"> Someone is blow-torching two cameras. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is singing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing a guitar on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A boy is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A woman is frying a food. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is spreading shredded cheese on an uncooked pizza. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A women is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A girl is playing an acoustic guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A guinea pig chews on food. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person is pouring olive oil into a pot on the stove. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A woman is cutting a bell pepper into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A boy is counting days by looking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="52"> Two men are talking and one of them has a piece of pizza which he samples. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A boy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A woman is slicing an eggplant into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is playing a key-board by one hand. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A girl is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A chef is preparing some food. </seg>
<seg id="59"> An animal is suspended in air by holding onto two cords with it's hands and feet. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is cutting a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A lion is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing a guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="64"> Un homme plante un clou. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A woman is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is stuffing food in his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is chopping wood. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A baby has headphones on. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man firing bullets with a rifle and a gun standing on an open ground is shown in separate sections of the video. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is peeling a potato using a peeler. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A rhino is eating. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is waking up a woman. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is singing while walking down the sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man drives a car. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is checking his email. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A man is making a clandestine phone call. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A woman chops a head of broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is stirring two eggs in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cleaning a glass door </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is preparing garlic bread. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A person cuts a tomato into many pieces. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is running. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A little kid is running around a fishing pole. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A woman is cooking a breaded pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A man is playing a violin on the roof. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A lady rode a jet ski in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A man is applying butter to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A person puts some ground beef in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is laying on the beach. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A man is walking a black and white dog. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A dog is jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A dog has a barking fit. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is draining liquid out of a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A man slicing vegetable </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A monkey pulls the tail of a dog. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A girl is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A live rabbit is playing with a stuffed animal bunny. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is wiping the edge of a bowl off. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is slicing a hamburger bun. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is playing a very large flute. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is adding oil on tomatoes pieces. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A cat plays with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man drives a car. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A carrot is carefully sliced. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A little girl is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A girl is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A woman is peeling a shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is eating food. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A person fills a plastic jug with water. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A man is crossing a tree in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A boy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A slow loris is being tickled. </seg>
<seg id="129"> Clowns are singing. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man drills holes in some wood. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A teenage boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A large white onion is sliced crosswise to get finger thick rings. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A man cuts a potato at both ends and thereafter slices it into thick strips. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person is filing her nails. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A girl is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A male is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A fisherman is trying to reel in something which has his rod bent almost double. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A girl is communicating with sign language. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A girl is shooting a gun multiple times. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A baby tiger is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is riding a bicycle on the road. </seg>
<seg id="146"> Two boys are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A monkey treads through water. </seg>
<seg id="149"> Two men are dancing like robots on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lion is walking in a pen. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is pouring olive oil into a pot on the stove. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A woman is scrambling eggs in a skillet using chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A makeup pencil is being applied to a female's eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="154"> Three men are doing same dance in the street. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is squeezing a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A boy is counting days by looking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A group of men are dancing in front of a plane. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man is running down the road when a truck drives past him. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A doberman pinscher is chewing on a stuffed animal toy. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man cuts and dices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is petting a crocodile on its nose. </seg>
<seg id="162"> People sing and play instruments. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is slicing a sweet-potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A man is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is going into a room. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A man is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A girl is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is holding a baby tiger. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A little girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man cutting grass by the machine. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A boy is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman is cutting tofu. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Men are running in a prison yard. </seg>
<seg id="177"> Someone is dicing a green onion. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is mixing. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is adding oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A cat drinks milk. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A very young kitten is trying to stand but it's wobbly on it's feet. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A woman is trying to cut an onion. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A bird is talking into a mic. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cat drinks milk. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A woman is dancing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A potato is peeled. </seg>
<seg id="187"> cooking something </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing a guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A boy crossing a swinging bridge. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is seasoning a steak. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A person is cutting a piece of blue paper with a pair of scissors. </seg>
<seg id="192"> Men  are running in the race. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A girl is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A man is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A man chops the head of a snake, dips the body immediately in a bucket of water, cuts and peels the skin off. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is checking his email. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A chef is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A man is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A woman is pouring water on fish. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is looking at a picture on his laptop. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A person is ritually dancing next to a fire. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A man gave a speech from the lectern. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is spun around by a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A man folds a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A small white dog is laying on his back on the floor rolling from one side to the other. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A small white dog is laying on his back on the floor rolling from one side to the other. </seg>
<seg id="212"> Men bounce off a wall. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A tiger is chasing a deer. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A cat is drinking water from the faucet. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A baby climbs on top of a sleeping dog. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is riding a bike on the road. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is eating corn on the cob. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A person is boiling noodles. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A makeup pencil is being applied to a female's eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A women is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is slicing an eggplant into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="226"> An airplane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is eating food. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A man is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A boy is playing the cello. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A boy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A woman is slicing ginger. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is opening a box with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person mixes a bowl of vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A cat is walking across the floor. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man body boards in a wave pool. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A dog barks at a ball floating in the water. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man appears to float off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A man dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A fish is being killed. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A shirtless man is sitting on a chair. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A man is playing a key-board by one hand. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man cuts a potato at both ends and thereafter slices it into thick strips. </seg>
<seg id="243"> Men are sawing wood. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A cat is hitting the keys on a piano. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A badger is digging a burrow. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A girl is coming up on a car. </seg>
<seg id="247"> A man eating cereal. </seg>
<seg id="248"> A monkey is brushing a dog's hair. </seg>
<seg id="249"> A man in a hard hat is dancing in front of several other men. </seg>
<seg id="250"> A man is opening a box with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="251"> A panda is eating bamboo. </seg>
<seg id="252"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="253"> A cat is hitting piano keys. </seg>
<seg id="254"> A man dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="255"> A man is drawing a picture. </seg>
<seg id="256"> A bicyclist is performing tricks in a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="257"> A person is slicing a bread. </seg>
<seg id="258"> A man is cutting up mushrooms very quickly. </seg>
<seg id="259"> Men are flipping large tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="260"> Two men are fighting near cows. </seg>
<seg id="261"> A chimp is doing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="262"> A girl is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="263"> A man dressed in fatigues is loading a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="264"> A man is burning matches. </seg>
<seg id="265"> A bearded bald man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="266"> A woman whisks two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="267"> A man eating cereal. </seg>
<seg id="268"> A woman adds ingredients to beef. </seg>
<seg id="269"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="270"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="271"> A woman is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="272"> A lady mixed up a meat mixture in bowl. </seg>
<seg id="273"> Someone is typing on some kind of machine. </seg>
<seg id="274"> A person is peeling an onion. </seg>
<seg id="275"> A lady rode a jet ski in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="276"> A man is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="277"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="278"> A man cutting butter into a mixing bowl. </seg>
<seg id="279"> A man is assembling a gun. </seg>
<seg id="280"> A little girl is riding on a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="281"> A man is spreading shredded cheese on an uncooked pizza. </seg>
<seg id="282"> Boys are playing a playing-card. </seg>
<seg id="283"> A live rabbit is playing with a stuffed animal bunny. </seg>
<seg id="284"> A person puts skewered meat on a grill. </seg>
<seg id="285"> A man is spreading shredded cheese on an uncooked pizza. </seg>
<seg id="286"> A man dives from a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="287"> A woman is pouring ingredients into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="288"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="289"> A woman is dipping fish into batter. </seg>
<seg id="290"> A person is chopping up a tomato into very small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="291"> A band is playing on stage under blue lights when slowly the lights change to bright white. </seg>
<seg id="292"> A man has his face close to the camera and he's speaking. </seg>
<seg id="293"> A guy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="294"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="295"> A woman is sewing two squares of fabric together on a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="296"> A woman is chopping an onion into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="297"> A man eats some food. </seg>
<seg id="298"> A man is walking  with style. </seg>
<seg id="299"> A man is carrying a woman on his back. </seg>
<seg id="300"> A woman puts a baby in a trash can. </seg>
<seg id="301"> A man is adding some detergent to sink full of water. </seg>
<seg id="302"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="303"> A person is slicing a capsicum. </seg>
<seg id="304"> A black-and-white-cat is snuggling heads with a baby. </seg>
<seg id="305"> A woman is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="306"> A squirrel is moving rapidly on a concrete floor in circles. </seg>
<seg id="307"> A person is scrubbing a zucchini. </seg>
<seg id="308"> A bicyclist is performing tricks in a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="309"> A man cutting grass by the machine. </seg>
<seg id="310"> A man is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="311"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="312"> A chimp is doing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="313"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="314"> A man is kicking and training with another man. </seg>
<seg id="315"> A woman is putting on makeup. </seg>
<seg id="316"> A boy is playing a wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="317"> A man is playing a drum set. </seg>
<seg id="318"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="319"> A women is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="320"> A chimp is doing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="321"> A baby climbs down from a sofa to the floor. </seg>
<seg id="322"> A guinea pig chews on food. </seg>
<seg id="323"> A man is riding a bull machine. </seg>
<seg id="324"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="325"> A woman is painting her lips. </seg>
<seg id="326"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="327"> A person is cooking beef on a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="328"> A man is breaking boards with a karate chop. </seg>
<seg id="329"> A dog is barking at a musical toy. </seg>
<seg id="330"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="331"> A man hammers a concrete slab on top of a man. </seg>
<seg id="332"> A man is walking  with style. </seg>
<seg id="333"> A woman cuts up some meat. </seg>
<seg id="334"> A cat is crawling under a piece of furniture on it's back. </seg>
<seg id="335"> A woman and man are driving in a car. </seg>
<seg id="336"> A man is playing soccer. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref3">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A man is catching a frog. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is mimicking with a skull. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A boy whacks a man with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="7"> Someone is cutting a red piece of meat into thin strips. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Someone is peeling the shells off of some shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A girl is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A group of people play basketball. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A small wide eyed animal is eating a piece of carrot. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is clamping the blade of a knife in a vise. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard with his nose. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is hanging on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man is making a hangman's noose out of a rope. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is chopping a potato. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A dog is looking over a counter. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A monkey is teasing a dog by grabbing at it and then running away. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is delivering a lecture at an event celebrating the game of cricket. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A woman is tapping her fingernails on a table. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A soccer player passes the ball across the field to a team mate and the team mate scores a goal. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A primate rides a little pink bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A little girl is sleeping in bed and then wakes up. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is running with a bus. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A kid playing a synthesizer. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is chopping butter into a container. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A woman slicing some potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A woman is beating two eggs in a bowl using a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is operating a microwave. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is cutting a meat. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A person is burning cameras. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man ia singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A boy sits on a bed, sings and plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A woman fries a slice of meat. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is spreading shreded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="45"> An older woman is peeling a potato with a potato peeler. </seg>
<seg id="46"> chopping vegetables </seg>
<seg id="47"> A girl is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A Guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person pours oil into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A woman is slicing a capsicum into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is eating a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A guy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A chef is chopping a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A chef prepared a meal. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A loris is swinging. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A man is firing a shotgun and you can see the blast from the end of the barrel. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A person is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A lion is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man hammers a nail with a camera. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A panda is sleeping on woods. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is eating noodles and ice creams. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is cutting wood with axe. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A baby is talking. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A rhino is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is patting a woman on her back. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is walking and singing. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man drives a car. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man severs the toe of an empty leather boot using a sword. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is staring straight ahead and rubbing his hand over his chin and then the scene switches to a personal ad in some kind of paper or magazine. </seg>
<seg id="82"> An older woman is peeling a potato with a potato peeler. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A man is making a phone call. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A woman cuts up broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman is mixing eggs in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is putting garlic on some bread slices. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A person cuts up tomatos. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is running down a road and then the scene switches and he's doing push-ups in front of a woman. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A little boy has a fishing rod in his hand with a fish on the end of the line and he's running around in a circle. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A woman is deep frying something that has a coating on it. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A man is on a roof dancing. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A person is riding a jetski in the waves. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A man is buttering a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is placing meat in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is slipping at the sea-shore in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A panda dog is running on the road. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A dog is jumping on a jumper. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A woman is slicing octopus. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A dog is barking at the camera. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is moving a box. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A vegetable is being cut. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is assembling a Silencerco 22 Sparrow gun. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman rides an elephant into a primitive village. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A monkey is teasing a dog by grabbing at it and then running away. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A rabbit is playing a toy-rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="110"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man is cleaning a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is splitting a bread roll in half with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man pours oil onto sliced tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A cat is playing with the antenna of a radio control device. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man drives a car. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A chef is slicing carrot. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A girl is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A woman butterflies a shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is eating from a plate. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A person is filling a plastic jug with tap water. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A man is stepping over a log in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A guy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="128"> Someone is petting a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A man dressed in a menacing clown costume is yelling. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A man is cutting a paper by scissor. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man and woman are running through an open gate that leads to the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man drills some screws into the wood. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A boy is cutting grass with scissors. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is slicing a peeled onion into four uniform slices of about 1/2"" thickness each. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A man is chopping a potato. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is filing her fingernails with an emery board. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A lady did exercises on a mat. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A man fishes. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A child is saying something with Sign Language. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A woman is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A baby tiger is playing with an orange ball. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="146"> Two young people are riding in a car laughing. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A monkey is walking through water. </seg>
<seg id="149"> Men are dancing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lion is walking in the cage. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person pours oil into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A woman is frying some eggs. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A woman is applying a dark brown shade on the outer edge of her eyelid, using a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="154"> Three people dance in towels. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A chef squeezes juice from a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="157"> a group of men are dancing in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man is running with a bus. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A dog chews his toy. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is petting a crocodile. </seg>
<seg id="162"> The two officers danced and sang in front of the band. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is slicing octopus. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A man is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is opening a door to enter a room. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A man is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A girl is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="170"> Someone is petting a tiger cub. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A young girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is mowing his lawn. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A boy sits on a bed, sings and plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman is cutting a block of tofu into small cubes. </seg>
<seg id="176"> Men are doing an exercise. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A person is slicing green onions leaf into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is kneading dough. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is pouring a liquid into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A cat drinks milk. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is eating its food from the plate. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A chef slices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A parrot is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cat drinks milk. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A girl is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="187"> Someone is cooking an omelet. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A boy is crossing a narrow rope bridge. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is coating a piece of pork with a flour mixture. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A person is cutting a piece of paper with a pair of scissors. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A group of men race down a track. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A young lady is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A man in a legionnaire uniform is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A man is cleaning a snake. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is staring straight ahead and rubbing his hand over his chin and then the scene switches to a personal ad in some kind of paper or magazine. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A chef slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A man is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A woman is spooning seasoning over a split fish in a plate. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is playing a computer game. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman dances by a bonfire. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A man is delivering a lecture at an event celebrating the game of cricket. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat gets caught on a fan. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A man folds a cheesy tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A little dog is rolling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A little dog is rolling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="212"> Two men are dancing in front of a couple of coke machines. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cheetah is running behind its prey. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A young girl puts a small child into a metal trash can. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A cat is drinking from a faucet. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A man is climbing a rope that is suspended from what looks like the ceiling of a warehouse. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A baby is climbing on and otherwise manhandling a dog. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A woman cracked a egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is riding a motor-cycle in the street. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is eating corn on the cob. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A person is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A woman is applying a dark brown shade on the outer edge of her eyelid, using a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="224"> chopping vegetables </seg>
<seg id="225"> A chef is chopping a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="226"> An animated passenger jet is taking off from the runway. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is eating a food. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A little red car is driving down the road. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A boy plays the cello. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A boy is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="231"> Someone is slicing a ginger root into very thin pieces. </seg>
<seg id="232"> Mail is being opened. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone is stirring a pan full of chopped vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A cat is walking around a house. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man body surfs on a waterpark wave ride. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A dog hesitates on a dock. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is finding something on the road. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A man is dancing hanging upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A fish is sliced and beheaded. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A bare chested man is sitting in a chair nodding his head. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is chopping a potato. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A group of men are cutting something using two man saws. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A cat is playing a key board. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A badger is digging a burrow. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A girl jumps on top of a car. </seg>
<seg id="247"> A man eats cereal and reads the back of a cereal box. </seg>
<seg id="248"> A chimp is brushing a dog. </seg>
<seg id="249"> A boy is dancing between the people. </seg>
<seg id="250"> Mail is being opened. </seg>
<seg id="251"> A panda is eating leaf. </seg>
<seg id="252"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="253"> A cat is playing a key board. </seg>
<seg id="254"> A man is dancing hanging upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="255"> A person draws a sketch. </seg>
<seg id="256"> A biker is performing stunts. </seg>
<seg id="257"> A chef is slicing a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="258"> Mushrooms are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="259"> Two men are moving tires. </seg>
<seg id="260"> A man is in a cattle pen with some other men and he's hitting the other men with a wooden club. </seg>
<seg id="261"> A chimpanzee and a man are practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="262"> A girl is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="263"> A man is loading a gun. </seg>
<seg id="264"> A man is holding a packet of burning matches. </seg>
<seg id="265"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="266"> A woman is beating two eggs in a bowl using a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="267"> A man eats cereal and reads the back of a cereal box. </seg>
<seg id="268"> A woman is adding spices on a meat. </seg>
<seg id="269"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="270"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="271"> A woman is powdering her face. </seg>
<seg id="272"> A person is mixing a batch of beef in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="273"> A man is tying in the machine. </seg>
<seg id="274"> A person is peeling an onion. </seg>
<seg id="275"> A person is riding a jetski in the waves. </seg>
<seg id="276"> A man is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="277"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="278"> A man is chopping butter into a container. </seg>
<seg id="279"> A man is assembling a Silencerco 22 Sparrow gun. </seg>
<seg id="280"> A young girl is riding her scooter. </seg>
<seg id="281"> A man is spreading shreded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="282"> A man does a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="283"> A rabbit is playing a toy-rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="284"> A woman is placing skewers of chicken over a grill. </seg>
<seg id="285"> A man is spreading shreded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="286"> A man dives off a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="287"> A woman is pouring ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="288"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="289"> A woman is dipping a piece of fish into some batter. </seg>
<seg id="290"> A woman is slicing carrots. </seg>
<seg id="291"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="292"> A man in a hat sings a song. </seg>
<seg id="293"> A man gallops on a horse across the desert. </seg>
<seg id="294"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="295"> A woman is sewing on a machine. </seg>
<seg id="296"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="297"> A man is eating a food. </seg>
<seg id="298"> A man is walking down the road. </seg>
<seg id="299"> A man is carrying a suitcase on his head and woman on his back. </seg>
<seg id="300"> A young girl puts a small child into a metal trash can. </seg>
<seg id="301"> A man is mixing Oxi Clean and water in a sink. </seg>
<seg id="302"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="303"> A chef slices a pepper. </seg>
<seg id="304"> A cat is nuzzling a baby. </seg>
<seg id="305"> A girl plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="306"> A squirrel is rotating repeatedly. </seg>
<seg id="307"> Someone is using a vegetable brush to clean a zucchini. </seg>
<seg id="308"> A biker is performing stunts. </seg>
<seg id="309"> A man is mowing his lawn. </seg>
<seg id="310"> A potato is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="311"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="312"> A chimpanzee and a man are practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="313"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="314"> Two men are sparring by kicking and jabbing. </seg>
<seg id="315"> A woman is powdering her face. </seg>
<seg id="316"> A boy is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="317"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="318"> A man is cutting a paper by scissor. </seg>
<seg id="319"> chopping vegetables </seg>
<seg id="320"> A chimpanzee and a man are practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="321"> A baby is crawling off a bed. </seg>
<seg id="322"> A Guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="323"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="324"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="325"> A woman is applying lipstick. </seg>
<seg id="326"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="327"> A woman sautes some beef. </seg>
<seg id="328"> A man karate chops several cinder blocks. </seg>
<seg id="329"> A dog is barking at a toy duck. </seg>
<seg id="330"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="331"> A man breaks cinder blocks on another man. </seg>
<seg id="332"> A man is walking down the road. </seg>
<seg id="333"> A woman is cutting a meat. </seg>
<seg id="334"> A cat is crawling under a sofa. </seg>
<seg id="335"> A woman and man are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="336"> Men are playing a football. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref4">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A man is holding an amphibian. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is playing with a human skull. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man sliced a robe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is beating another man. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A person is slicing a meat into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="8"> A woman is peeling cooked shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A person is riding a horse across the desert. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A little girl is playing a grand piano on stage. </seg>
<seg id="13"> Boys are playing a basket-ball. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A Lorie is eating its food. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is putting a hunting knife in a vise. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A man is playing piano with his nose. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is climbing down a rope. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A man binding a knot. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A dog is resting on a counter. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A monkey is teasing a dog. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A man is delivering a speech on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A soccer player scores a goal. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A monkey is riding a bike. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A little girl is waking up. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is running next to a truck. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is cutting a butter. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A woman cuts a potato in quarters. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A woman is whisking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is pressing microwave buttons. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is cutting meat. </seg>
<seg id="37"> Two cameras are sitting side by side one of them is in flames. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A man is playing an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A child is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A woman is frying meat. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A man in a library is talking. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A cook spreads cheese onto a raw pizza crust. </seg>
<seg id="45"> An older woman is peeling potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="46"> SOMEONE SLICING VEGETABLE </seg>
<seg id="47"> A woman is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="48"> A guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone is pouring olive oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A woman slices and pits a pepper. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man eats a slice of pizza. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A man is doing back flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A woman is slicing a eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A chef sautes food in a large pan. </seg>
<seg id="59"> A sloth is hanging from some string. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is cutting a tomato into pieces using a cleaver. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A lion is walking in circles. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is playing the electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A person is using a camera to pound a nail into a board. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A panda is lounging around. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is eating various foods. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A man is chopping a tree trunk with an axe. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A baby is wearing a headset. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A man eats a banana. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A man is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A rhinoceros is eating grass. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is tapping a sleeping woman. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A girl is riding her horse in training in a riding ring. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A man is walking down a city sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man is cutting a shoe. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is reading a message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="82"> An older woman is peeling potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A man is talking on cellphone inside a storeroom. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A woman first cuts the stem and then chops a broccoli flowerette into smaller pieces. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A woman beats two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A man is cleaning a glass door. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is seasoning bread. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A person is cutting a tomato into chunks. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="91"> A baby is running. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A woman is frying a food. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A man is playing the violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A woman is riding a jet ski. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A man is greasing a sheet pan. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A woman is putting a red meat in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is relaxing on a beach. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A dog follows a person. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A dog is barking incessantly. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is draining the water from cooked pasta. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A chef is peeling the skin of fresh vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is fitting silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is riding on an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A monkey is teasing a dog. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A real rabbit plays with a toy rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man in a chef's hat is cleaning off the edge of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is slicing a bun. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A man plays a wind instrument. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is playing a musical keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is pouring oil on tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A chef slicing carrots. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A little girl is playing a grand piano on stage. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A person is dicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="123"> A woman is cutting a shrimp. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A man is eating spaghetti out of a large bowl. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A person is filling a plastic pitcher at the kitchen sink. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A man is stepping over a log in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is doing back flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A person is petting a baby sloth. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A clown is singing and people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A man is cutting paper. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man and a woman are running toward the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man drills wood. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A BOY IS CUTTING A GRASS BY SCISSOR. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A man is slicing an onion in round shape. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A woman is filing her fingernail using an emery board </seg>
<seg id="139"> A woman does exercises on a floor mat. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A man is fishing in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A young girl is using sign language. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A woman is firing with an assault rifle. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A baby tiger is playing. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is riding a bicycle. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A boy is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A monkey is walking in a watery field. </seg>
<seg id="149"> Two men are doing the robot dance on stage. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lion is walking in circles. </seg>
<seg id="151"> Someone is pouring olive oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A woman is applying cosmetics to her eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="154"> Three men are dancing in beach towels. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is extracting juice from lemon. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A group of men are dancing to music on a concrete surface with aircrafts in the background. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man is running next to a truck. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A dog chews on a stuffed whale toy. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man dices a peeled potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A man is standing in front of a crocodile and he reaches out with his hand and touches the crocodile on the snout. </seg>
<seg id="162"> The women are singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A onion is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is opening a door. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A girl is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A man is riding a red motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A woman is petting a tiger cub. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is mowing a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A child is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman is slicing a block of tofu into cubes. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A group of men are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A chef is slicing a green onion. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is using an electric mixer to blend some ingredients. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A man is pouring oil into a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A cat is drinking from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A kitten is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Someone is slicing a onion. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A bird is speaking into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A cat is drinking from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A young woman is dancing in a cage. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="187"> someone preparing food </seg>
<seg id="188"> A man is playing the electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A boy is crossing a rope bridge. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A woman is putting flour on a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A person is cutting with scissors across a blue paper. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A group of men are running. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A woman is playing an acoustic guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A person is playing a harp. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy is playing piano. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A man is cutting a snack. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is reading a message on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A man chops the top and bottom ends of a peeled potato and thereafter chops a thin slice on one side. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A woman is adding oil on fishes. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is playing a video game on a laptop computer. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman dances in front of a fire. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A man is delivering a speech on a podium. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A woman is dancing and signing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is swinging from a ceiling fall and then gets thrown off of it. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A man is cooking a quesadilla in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A dog is rolling on its back. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A dog is rolling on its back. </seg>
<seg id="212"> Men are jumping. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A cheetah is chasing after a gazelle. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A woman is putting a small baby in a water pip. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A cat is drinking water from a faucet that is leaking. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A man is climbing by a rope. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A baby is laying on a dog. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A man is riding a motorcycle through a town. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is eating an ear of corn. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A woman is boiling noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A woman is applying cosmetics to her eyelid. </seg>
<seg id="224"> SOMEONE SLICING VEGETABLE </seg>
<seg id="225"> A woman is slicing a eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A plane is taking off. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is talking and eating a spoonful of chili. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A person is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A guy is playing an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A boy is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A person is slicing a garlic into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is opening a package by cutting. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is stirring salad. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A cat is walking around some drawers. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is boogie boarding in a wave pool. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A dog is afraid to jump into a lake to get his ball. </seg>
<seg id="237"> Two kids are doing a magic trick. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A man is dancing on ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A man cuts into a live fish. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is sitting on a chair. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A group of men are sawing through a log with giant two-person saws. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A cat is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A girl is jumping to a car top. </seg>
<seg id="247"> A man eats cereal and reads the box. </seg>
<seg id="248"> A chimpanzee is grooming a dog with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="249"> A man wearing a firehat is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="250"> A man is opening a package by cutting. </seg>
<seg id="251"> A panda bear is eating some bamboo. </seg>
<seg id="252"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="253"> A cat is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="254"> A man is dancing on ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="255"> A person draws an old woman's face on a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="256"> A guy is riding a bike on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="257"> A man is slicing a baguette. </seg>
<seg id="258"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="259"> Men are rolling big tyre. </seg>
<seg id="260"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="261"> A monkey is fighting with a man. </seg>
<seg id="262"> A girl is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="263"> A man is loading a rifle with bullets. </seg>
<seg id="264"> A man is lighting a match and sets the whole match box on fire. </seg>
<seg id="265"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="266"> A woman is whisking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="267"> A man eats cereal and reads the box. </seg>
<seg id="268"> A woman seasons some meat. </seg>
<seg id="269"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="270"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="271"> A girl is applying make-up with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="272"> A person is mixing a meaty mixture in a glass bowl with a wooden spoon. </seg>
<seg id="273"> A man is typing keys. </seg>
<seg id="274"> A chef is peeling an onion. </seg>
<seg id="275"> A woman is riding a jet ski. </seg>
<seg id="276"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="277"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="278"> A man is cutting a butter. </seg>
<seg id="279"> A man is fitting silencer on a pistol. </seg>
<seg id="280"> A toddler rides her scooter. </seg>
<seg id="281"> A cook spreads cheese onto a raw pizza crust. </seg>
<seg id="282"> A man is doing a magic trick with cards. </seg>
<seg id="283"> A real rabbit plays with a toy rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="284"> A woman is putting shish kabobs in a pan to cook. </seg>
<seg id="285"> A cook spreads cheese onto a raw pizza crust. </seg>
<seg id="286"> A man dives off of a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="287"> A woman is adding ingredients to a small glass dish. </seg>
<seg id="288"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="289"> A woman is putting fish into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="290"> A person is slicing a carrot into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="291"> A band is singing on a foggy stage. </seg>
<seg id="292"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="293"> A man in cowboy gear rides a horse in a circle. </seg>
<seg id="294"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="295"> A woman is sewing. </seg>
<seg id="296"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="297"> A man is eating a piece of bread. </seg>
<seg id="298"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="299"> A man is walking and singing. </seg>
<seg id="300"> A woman is putting a small baby in a water pip. </seg>
<seg id="301"> A man is pouring a scoop of OxiClean into a sink of water and stirring with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="302"> A girl rode a horse in the barn. </seg>
<seg id="303"> A man is cutting tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="304"> A cat is rubbing against a baby. </seg>
<seg id="305"> A girl is playing the electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="306"> A squirrel is running around in a circle on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="307"> A woman is scrubbing a zucchini with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="308"> A guy is riding a bike on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="309"> A man is mowing a lawn. </seg>
<seg id="310"> A woman is peeling a large potato. </seg>
<seg id="311"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="312"> A monkey is fighting with a man. </seg>
<seg id="313"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="314"> Two men are boxing. </seg>
<seg id="315"> A girl is applying make-up with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="316"> A child plays the flute. </seg>
<seg id="317"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="318"> A man is cutting paper. </seg>
<seg id="319"> SOMEONE SLICING VEGETABLE </seg>
<seg id="320"> A monkey is fighting with a man. </seg>
<seg id="321"> A baby is playing while wearing a diaper. </seg>
<seg id="322"> A guinea pig eats a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="323"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="324"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="325"> A teenage girl is putting on lip gloss. </seg>
<seg id="326"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="327"> Meat is being cooked. </seg>
<seg id="328"> A man is breaking wood with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="329"> A dog is barking at a toy. </seg>
<seg id="330"> A girl plays with her hair. </seg>
<seg id="331"> A brick is being broken on a mans body. </seg>
<seg id="332"> A man is walking down a road. </seg>
<seg id="333"> A woman is cutting meat. </seg>
<seg id="334"> A cat is crawling under sofa. </seg>
<seg id="335"> A woman drives ""The Arnold"" down the street in a convertible. </seg>
<seg id="336"> A soccer player dribbles past his opponents. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
</mteval>
