<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
                   <mteval>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref0">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is tasting something from a bowl with a spoon while speaking. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man lays his hand near his lip and appears to be thinking. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man holding a guitar is petting two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man dangles a mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is skinning a piece of fish with her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing table tennis in front of an audience. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A group of couples are dancing in an event. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A boy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A pencil is being sharpened. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman, with one arm raised, is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse inside a track. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is reading something, while another woman measures the first woman's ankle with a tape measure. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog biting on a can. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is at waiting at the counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man jumping rope </seg>
<seg id="22"> A boy is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman drops down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby laughing on the couch. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is pruning flowers on a bush. </seg>
<seg id="26"> An onion is being cut. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A girl is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A young man is talking to a woman on the computer via web cam when he gets up and moves the web cam to point in another direction. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="30"> Someone folds a flour tortilla with cheese in half in a metal pan, using their fingers and a spatula. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A couple walks through the jungle. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A football player is talking to a coach. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxaphone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing up a knotted rope suspended from the ceiling, when the scene flashes to the same man splashing water on his face from an outdoor container. </seg>
<seg id="35"> Someone is scrubbing the bottom of their bare foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling a potato with a peeler. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is being interviewed. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A person is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A raccoon-like animal is holding and eating something orange. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A drill sergeant is voicing over his troops. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A small dog laying on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two men are fighting, and one man hits the other man on his head with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man demonstrating how to clean a flower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Kids karate fight. </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing the key board. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five kittens in a row and then in a circle are eating off of plates. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog biting on a can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man wearing glasses and a suit is standing and talking in front of a huge bookshelf. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A big ball bounces over a nut. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is checking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man has a conversation with a younger man. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men are rolling huge tires sideways down a street while spectators watch. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman dances in the rain out side. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Jimmy Hendrix performing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A drill sergeant is voicing over his troops. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is smiling while talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A boy does a back flip into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man a playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating a piece of fried chicken. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man appears to be draining water off of pasta in a plastic container into a sink. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A young boy splashes muddy water on his face and clothes and gets up and looks sheepishly at a young girl. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A kitten drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man jumps up and goes over a wooden fence at night. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman boils eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A gerbil is getting washed. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man emerges out of a puddle of muddy water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> Three boys doing art work. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A toddler waters plants with a water gun. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man has a conversation with a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A girl is slicing onion </seg>
<seg id="80"> A woman and a man, with their arms around each other, are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A boy is beating other boy by stick. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman slices tofu in half lengthwise. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino is walking behind an adult rhino. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A big ball bounces over a nut. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man in a suit is standing at a microphone and singing. </seg>
<seg id="86"> A group of girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is karate kicking at someone's gloved hand. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A person is slicing bread with a bread knife. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two baby pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is playing with a telephone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is trying to use it's mouth and paws to get a small plastic bottle someone is holding. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A small dog laying on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> a person cutting up a fruit </seg>
<seg id="96"> Someone is pouring tomato sauce from a can into a saucepan containing meat pieces. </seg>
<seg id="97"> Someone pours oil from a bottle into a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> An older woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A woman and a man, with their arms around each other, are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man gets excited about the fire he lit. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is carrying a large tree limb in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman pours oil from a small glass bowl into a wok-like skillet. </seg>
<seg id="104"> Steve Martin  doing a magic act with eggs. </seg>
<seg id="105"> Someone is sewing quilt squares on a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man is instructing a boy about batting. </seg>
<seg id="107"> Someone is burning the tops of two cameras with a torch. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy is playing a cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> Someone is scrubbing a zucchini with a brush under the running water from a faucet at a sink. </seg>
<seg id="110"> a woman cutting a tomato </seg>
<seg id="111"> A woman and a man are holding hands and running towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is smiling while talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is coating a pork chop with flour. </seg>
<seg id="114"> Someone cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> Lionel Richie dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman cracks an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is slicing open a fish longways with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="118"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> a small furry animal is biting on someone's finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> Someone is scrubbing the bottom of their bare foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A body builder lifting alot of heavy weights </seg>
<seg id="123"> Kids karate fight. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse gets up off of the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five kittens in a row and then in a circle are eating off of plates. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A boy gets knocked down by a dog. </seg>
<seg id="127"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat stares out of the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman puts four okra in a pan of boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman peels a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man karate chops multiple boards while another man watches. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> Paper is being ripped apart. </seg>
<seg id="134"> Someone drills a hole in a strip of wood with a power drill. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man does a magic card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A female sits in a chair and plays an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A boy is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> Someone is stirring chili in a kettle. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man takes a shot at a target outside. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A horse falls down. </seg>
<seg id="141"> a group of people dancing </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A boy does flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man plays a violin on the roof of a house. </seg>
<seg id="145"> Someone folds a flour tortilla with cheese in half in a metal pan, using their fingers and a spatula. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A little car sits on toy railroad tracks, as a train approaches. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A boy is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is bouncing his front paws on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> The woman is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman picks up a watering can, shows it, then puts it down. </seg>
<seg id="151"> Someone is stirring a salad mixture in a large metal bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> Someone drills a hole in a strip of wood with a power drill. </seg>
<seg id="153"> Someone drills a hole in a strip of wood with a power drill. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man sings into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman sits down, opens a can of soft drink, and takes a drink. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A girl is riding a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is wiping off the edge of a bowl filled with food with a paper towel. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man cliff dives into the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is skateboarding on a half pipe and he tries to do a flip and fails. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A band is performing a song </seg>
<seg id="161"> A group of teenagers are dancing outdoors. </seg>
<seg id="162"> a man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> a women cutting broccoli up </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is cutting a green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man who is crying goes up to another man who appears to sympathize. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A smiling baby is crawling down a hallway. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A man getting face painted by a woman artist </seg>
<seg id="170"> Someone is petting a rabbit on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man riding his motorcycle down the street turns around towards a woman walking the opposite way. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A..man..plays...a..guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A class doing a walking exercise. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A young woman is taking a bite of the icing on a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A person riding a mechanical bull </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is trying to use it's mouth and paws to get a small plastic bottle someone is holding. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is skateboarding on a half pipe and he tries to do a flip and fails. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A tortoise chases fish in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is walking on water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat sitting on the back edge of a couch jumps up and is rotated around a ceiling fan then tossed off. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Four men sawing on a log flashes to four men running in a field carrying something long on their shoulders. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A chef a cooking meat </seg>
<seg id="184"> Three young men run, jump, and kick off of a Coke machine. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger digs a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man using a microwave </seg>
<seg id="187"> A white kitten is on a table lapping milk from a plate. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck or van is being driven down a road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is playing with a large watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> An extremely muscled man lifts a barbell with his right hand. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is doing a weight exercise. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man standing on a boat pulls a fish out of the water on his fishing line, but the man and a woman standing next to him are startled and he drops the fish back into the water. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A lemur is holding up it's arms and someone is scratching him. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is maneuvering a soccer ball with his feet. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man appears to be draining water off of pasta in a plastic container into a sink. </seg>
<seg id="197"> Someone drills a hole in a strip of wood with a power drill. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man held a baby monkey in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman cuts a small piece of rind off a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man draws a four sided shape on a screen and then puts an X inside of it. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A small dog goes to the edge of the dock. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A young woman is taking a bite of the icing on a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man cuts the toe off a brown boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man puts cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A girl is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A chef boils noodles. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog runs and hides behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is standing on it's back paws and appears to be boxing with it's front paws. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is cutting partially peeled zucchini into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A young woman is curling her hair with a round hairbrush. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is pruning flowers on a bush. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is tapping her nails. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A guy prays in the middle of the street. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A person is cutting beef. </seg>
<seg id="217"> a soccer player making a goal </seg>
<seg id="218"> A white cat is lying on it's back, and a man is brushing it's hair. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Women lined up on a dock dive into a lake and start swimming in a race. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A boy is singing in the street. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is frying food. </seg>
<seg id="223"> The girl is using sign  language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A chef boils noodles. </seg>
<seg id="225"> A couple of policewomen are singing karaoke. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman pours a liquid and seasonings in a small glass bowl and whips them with a wire whisk. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man playing the accordion. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A man is driving a car, and the man and woman passenger are smiling at each other. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A guy is singing while playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A smiling baby is crawling down a hallway. </seg>
<seg id="231"> Two women are sitting on a couch knitting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A drill sergeant is voicing over his troops. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone is holding a hedgehog in their hand. </seg>
<seg id="234"> Someone is petting a rabbit on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing on drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman dances in front of a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a large flute-like instrument. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A girl is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog biting on a can. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cuts throw a rope, suspended from the ceiling, with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A little girl is doing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man fishing in the ocean </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is frying food. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A little girl is doing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A person is mixing ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man dangles a mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref1">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is eating. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is sad. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is holding a guitar in his right hand and petting two dogs with his left. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat is jumped into a box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man grabs a live rat out of a snake's cage. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is removing bones from a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men play table tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A couple dances on a dance floor. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A man creases a yellow colored square sheet of paper by folding it diagonally at all sides and then opens it out. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is paddling in a boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A CNC lathe machine is sharpening a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman rides an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl and discards the shell. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is measuring another woman. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog fetches a small canned food tin in his mouth, bites and pulls off the lid and eats the food inside. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is in a newsstand. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A boy is skipping a rope. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A boy is playing on a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman climbs down a vine and kneels by a cage. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is laughing on a couch. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman prunes flowers. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A chef is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A lady played her violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is talking to a girl on webcam. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A hiker walks through the wilderness. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person folds a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="31"> The couple is walking throught the field. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is kneeling with a football. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man plays a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A person is scrubbing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man gives a press conference. </seg>
<seg id="38"> Two men are standing in a kitchen and one is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is whisking two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A child is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="42"> One man is erasing a chalkboard while a second man is talking to someone that is not in viewing range. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A slow loris is eating. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A commander is inspecting his men. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A chihuahua lying on top of a bed is snarling while wagging its tail simultaneously. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man brushes off the roots of a sunflower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Men are doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A guy is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Kittens are eating food. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog fetches a small canned food tin in his mouth, bites and pulls off the lid and eats the food inside. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A ball hits a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is checking a calender. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man in a red shirt is talking to a man in a white shirt. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A girl dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A band is singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A commander is inspecting his men. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A boy does a flip into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating chicken. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is emptying a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A boy slaps the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat drinks milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A bald man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man sits on a fence. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman boils two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A person washes a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man emerges from mud. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is adding finishing touches to a drawing on paper. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A baby panda relaxes on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A child is watering the plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A boy is talking to a girl. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A onion and greens are being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and woman walking hold each other. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A boy smacks a mans back with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is slicing tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> Two rhinos are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A ball hits a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing onstage. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Girls are acting silly. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A chimp is kicking a target. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A boy is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is using a knife to slice a loaf of bread into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two baby pandas are grabbing each other. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is playing with a toy phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is licking a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A chihuahua lying on top of a bed is snarling while wagging its tail simultaneously. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A papaya is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A person pours tomato sauce in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A person pours oil in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and woman walking hold each other. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is burning a book of matches. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is picking up a tree. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A person holds a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman pours oil on a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is on stage dressed in a tuxedo and he's pulling eggs out of the fly of his trousers. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A person is sewing with a machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A person is training a person to bat in cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person is blow torching cameras. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy is playing a cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman is scrubbing a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A tomato is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman brushes flour on a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A person cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man danced on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is gutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A man is shooting off a gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A slow loris bites a persons fingers. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a black horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A person is scrubbing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting a barbell. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Men are doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse stands up from the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Kittens are eating food. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A boy running in a flooded area is knocked down twice by a large dog. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman is boiling peppers. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A man is peeling a potato using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is breaking wooden boards with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="132"> One man is erasing a chalkboard while a second man is talking to someone that is not in viewing range. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A child tore a paper along a fold. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man drills a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man does a magic card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person is mixing a pot. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man fires a shotgun at a target. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A horse and its rider fall down. </seg>
<seg id="141"> The men danced in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman breaks two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A boy is doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is standing on a roof top playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A person folds a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A model car is hit by a model train. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman slices some kind of seafood in chunks. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman lifts up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A man is mixing a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man drills a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A man drills a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing in front of a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman drinks a can of soda. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A Baby girl is playing with her tricycle. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A person is cleaning a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man dived off the cliffs. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man doing freestyle on a skate ramp. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A band is performing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man cuts a potato into sections. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A person cuts up a stalk of broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is whisking two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A pepper is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man crys. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A big cat opens a plastic drawer with his paws and then hops inside. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A girl applied eye makeup to a guy. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man tickles a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is passionately playing a guitar in front of an audience. </seg>
<seg id="174"> A group of people are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl eats a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A boy is playing bull riding game. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is licking a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man doing freestyle on a skate ramp. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is wading across a marsh. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is spun by a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> People are cutting wood. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A cook spreads dough on a pan. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Three men bounce off a soda machine. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is burrowing a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man heated a cup of coffee in the microwave. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A cat is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck drives down a road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat plays with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is weightlifting. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is doing exercise. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man catches a fish. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A person is tickling a slow loris. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is kicking a soccer ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is emptying a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man drills a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man holds a baby monkey in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman slices orange peel. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man draws shapes on a board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A brown dog reluctant to jump is walking along the edge of a diving board barking at a yellow ball which is floating in the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl eats a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is sprinkling shredded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A female plays an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A cook puts some noodles in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog hides behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman chops an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman prunes flowers. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A black cat is deftly playing the piano using her right fore paw. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman with purple fingernails is drumming her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is cutting a potato in half. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man goes into the street and bows down. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman cuts a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A goal is made in soccer. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A cat is being brushed. </seg>
<seg id="219"> People jump into water to swim. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A big cat opens a plastic drawer with his paws and then hops inside. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is singing as he walks down a street. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is deep frying a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is speaking using sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A cook puts some noodles in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman puts ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing a keyboard instrument. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two people are riding a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A commander is inspecting his men. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person holds a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A man tickles a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A lady danced in front of a bonfire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man plays a flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A lady played her violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog fetches a small canned food tin in his mouth, bites and pulls off the lid and eats the food inside. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man with a sword slices a rope. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A fisher tries to pull in his catch. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is deep frying a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is adding all ingredient into the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man grabs a live rat out of a snake's cage. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref2">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is eating food. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is crying. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is petting two dogs while holding a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man holds a white rat close to his face after touching it to a snake's body in a glass enclosure. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is removing bones from a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing table tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A couple is performing dance moves. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person folds a piece of paper several times. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A lathe is sharpening a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman measures another woman's ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog is opening a can of dog food with its mouth. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is looking around </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is doing rope skipping. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A boy is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is laughing while sitting on a couch. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is cutting flowers. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A chef sliced up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is demonstrating as to how to play a violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is chatting on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man hikes in the forest. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man folds a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A couple is walking together. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is preparing to kick a football. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A girl is scrubbing the bottom of her foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is answering questions posed by reporters at an outdoor location. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is stirring two eggs in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A kid is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is cleaning a green-board and other man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A slow loris is eating. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A Drill Sargent addresses his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A dog is wagging its tail on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two men are fighting near cows. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man holding two dried sunflowers is talking while dusting off the center portion of one flower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Men are fighting in a field. </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone is typing on some kind of machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing a key-board by one hand. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five kittens are eating out of bowls on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog is opening a can of dog food with its mouth. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing on the road. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A ball knocked over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is counting days by looking a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> The boy confronted his dad. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Men are flipping large tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is playing a guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A Drill Sargent addresses his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is speaking into a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A guy is doing a double back flip off the diving board into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is playing a guitar on a stage outside. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating a meat. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is draining liquid out of a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A boy punches mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat drinks milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A bearded bald man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man jumps on a fence. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman boils two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A lady is washing a little hedgehog in the sink. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man's head rises out of a pile of mud. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A man is drawing a picture. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A girl is spraying flowers. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man and woman are speaking. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is slicing some onion </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A boy spanks a man with a plastic sword. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is slicing tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino is following an adult rhino. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A ball knocked over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Girls are dancing in a room. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A chimp is doing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A guy is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Baby pandas are hugging. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A little boy is playing with a toy phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is licking a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A dog is wagging its tail on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A person is carving the skin off a papaya fruit. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man is pouring a can of tomato sauce into a pan of sausages. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A person is pouring olive oil into a pot on the stove. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is burning matches. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is carrying a tree. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is pouring oil into a wok. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is performing some magic tick on stage. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is sewing two squares of fabric together on a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A kid is playing cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> Someone is blow-torching two cameras. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy is playing the cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A person is scrubbing a zucchini. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman cuts a tomato into slices. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and woman are running together. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is speaking into a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is seasoning a steak. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is cracking an egg into a small dish. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is gutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A slow loris is biting a persons finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A girl is scrubbing the bottom of her foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting a heavy barbell. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Men are fighting in a field. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse is rolling on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five kittens are eating out of bowls on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog is knocking a young boy down twice. </seg>
<seg id="127"> Someone is typing on some kind of machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A person is boiling chile peppers. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A man is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is breaking boards with a karate chop. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is cleaning a green-board and other man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A child tore a paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A person drills a hole in wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> Boys are playing a playing-card. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person is mixing a pot of chili. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is firing a shot gun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A horse and rider are falling to the ground. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men are dancing in front of a plane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman cracks an egg against the rim of a glass bowl and puts it inside. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A boy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing a violin on the roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man folds a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A model train crashes into a model car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is mixing a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A person drills a hole in wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A person drills a hole in wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is drinking a soda. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A little girl is riding on a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is wiping the edge of a bowl off. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man dives from a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A boy is showing skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A band is performing. </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman chops a head of broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is stirring two eggs in a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is cutting a capsicum into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is crying. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling on it's hands and knees from one room to another. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat climbs into a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A lady decorates a man's face. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A rabbit is trying to sit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man rides a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is paying guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="174"> People exercise togther. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl is taking a bite of a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a bull machine. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is licking a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A boy is showing skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey treads through water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is spun around by a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Men are sawing wood. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is laying out dough on a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Men bounce off a wall. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a burrow. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is operating a microwave oven. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A very young kitten is trying to stand but it's wobbly on it's feet. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A car is driving down a road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A kitten is playing with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is weightlifting. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man is fishing. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A slow loris is being tickled. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is kicking a soccer ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is draining liquid out of a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A person drills a hole in wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man holds a small animal in one hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman cut a small piece of lemon peel off of a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is drawing a diagram on a white board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog barks at a ball floating in the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl is taking a bite of a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man slices a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is spreading shredded cheese on an uncooked pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A girl is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A person is boiling noodles. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog runs and hides behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat plays with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing an eggplant into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman is combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is cutting flowers. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is hitting the keys on a piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A male is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man is bowing in the street. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman cuts up some meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A group of men are playing soccer. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A cat is being brushed. </seg>
<seg id="219"> People are diving into water to swim. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat climbs into a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is singing while walking down the sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is frying a food. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is communicating with sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A person is boiling noodles. </seg>
<seg id="225"> People sing and play instruments. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is pouring ingredients into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two boys are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling on it's hands and knees from one room to another. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A Drill Sargent addresses his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone is holding a small prickly looking animal in their hand. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A rabbit is trying to sit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing a drum set. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A person is ritually dancing next to a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a very large flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is demonstrating as to how to play a violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog is opening a can of dog food with its mouth. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man slices rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A fisherman is trying to reel in something which has his rod bent almost double. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is frying a food. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is adding ingredients into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man holds a white rat close to his face after touching it to a snake's body in a glass enclosure. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref3">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is eating a food. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is thinking. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is petting two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is dangling a live mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is breaking a fish on a plate into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing table-tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A group of couples are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person folds a yellow piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine is sharpening a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman rides an elephant into a primitive village. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl and puts it in the stand mixer. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> One woman is measuring other woman's ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog is opening a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is looking over a counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is jumping rope on a walkway. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A boy sits on a bed, sings and plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman is hanging on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is picking flowers. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man cuts an onion into thin slivers with a cleaver. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A boy is using a web camera on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man hiking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man folds a cheesy tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and a woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is talking to another man who kneels down holding a football. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope that is suspended from what looks like the ceiling of a warehouse. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A person is scrubbing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> An older woman is peeling a potato with a potato peeler. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is being interviewed by the press. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is mixing eggs in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A kid playing a synthesizer. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man erases a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A small wide eyed animal is eating a piece of carrot. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A drill sergeant is inspecting a barracks. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A dog is wagging its tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is in a cattle pen with some other men and he's hitting the other men with a wooden club. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is brushing dirt off a sunflower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> The boys did martial arts together in the field. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is tying in the machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Kittens are eating food on trays. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog is opening a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A ball knocks down a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> The man talked to the young man. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men are moving tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman dances in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is playing guitar and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A drill sergeant is inspecting a barracks. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man does a back flip from a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is playing a violin like a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating a chicken leg. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is moving a box. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A boy is jumping in the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat drinks milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man climbs over a short wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling egg. </seg>
<seg id="73"> Someone is washing a small rodent looking animal in an aluminum pan. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man is coming out into the water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person draws a sketch. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda is sleeping on woods. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A girl is spraying water on plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man and woman are talking with each other. </seg>
<seg id="79"> a woman is slicing some onions </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and woman are walking arm in arm through a wooded area. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A boy whacks a man with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is splitting a block of tofu in half. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A rhino and its kid are walking. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A ball knocks down a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man ia singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Girls are dancing with music. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A chimpanzee and a man are practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing a drum set. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Bread is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two pandas are playing with each other. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is playing on a toy telephone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> Someone is holding a small plastic bottle up to a cats nose and the cat is sniffing at it. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A dog is wagging its tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A person peels an orange object. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man puts tomato sauce in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A person pours oil into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> An old lady is adding an egg into the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and woman are walking arm in arm through a wooded area. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is holding a packet of burning matches. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is moving a fallen branch out of a pathway in a wooded area. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is catching a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman pours oil into a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is placing eggs from his crotch into a basket. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is sewing on a machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man is teaching a boy how to play cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person is burning cameras. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A boy plays the cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> Someone is using a vegetable brush to clean a zucchini. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman cuts a tomato into two and thereafter slices one half of it. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and woman are running through an open gate that leads to the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is coating a piece of pork with a flour mixture. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man cracks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing hanging upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman cracked a egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is cutting open a fish to cook it. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A man is firing a shotgun and you can see the blast from the end of the barrel. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A small furry animal has a man's finger in it's mouth. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A person is scrubbing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting a large set of dumbbells. </seg>
<seg id="123"> The boys did martial arts together in the field. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse is standing. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Kittens are eating food on trays. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog is pushes a boy to fall. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is tying in the machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> Someone is cooking okra in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A potato is being peeled. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man karate chops several cinder blocks. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man erases a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is cutting a paper by hands. </seg>
<seg id="134"> Someone is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man does a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> Someone is stirring a pot of chili with a spoon. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is firing a shotgun at targets. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A horse and the person riding it fall down on the ground and then stand up after a while. </seg>
<seg id="141"> a group of men are dancing in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman cracks an egg and puts it into a bowl with another egg. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A guy is flipping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is on a roof dancing. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man folds a cheesy tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A model train hits a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is jumping on a jumper. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is slicing octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman bends over and picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> Someone is using a spatula to stir the contents of a metal bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> Someone is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> Someone is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is drinking a drink. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A young girl is riding her scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is cleaning a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man dives off a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man does tricks on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A band is playing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man is slicing a potato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman cuts up broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is mixing eggs in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is cutting a green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Two men are talking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling happily. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat has opened a drawer and entered inside. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman applies Joker makeup to a man's face. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A person is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is driving a motor-cycle. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing a guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="174"> The people exercised to a video. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman is eating an cake-cup. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> Someone is holding a small plastic bottle up to a cats nose and the cat is sniffing at it. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man does tricks on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is swimming underwater near the floor of a body of water. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is walking through water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat gets caught on a fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A group of men are cutting something using two man saws. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is spreading dough onto a pan. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Two men are dancing in front of a couple of coke machines. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a burrow. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is operating a microwave. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A cat is eating its food from the plate. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A person is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is playing with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is lifting a barbell. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is exercising with small weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man and a woman are fishing in the water. </seg>
<seg id="194"> Someone is petting a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is playing a football. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is moving a box. </seg>
<seg id="197"> Someone is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man holds up an animal. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is slicing a peel of yellow lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is drawing a diagram on the board and explaining it. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog hesitates on a dock. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is eating an cake-cup. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man severs the toe of an empty leather boot using a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is spreading shreded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A girl is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A person is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog barks at something and then runs and hides behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with the antenna of a radio control device. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A chef is chopping a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is picking flowers. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is playing a key board. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is tapping her fingernails on a table. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man cuts a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man is on a road praying. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting a meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A soccer player passes the ball across the field to a team mate and the team mate scores a goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A person is combing a cat hair. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A group of women swimmers jump into a lake and race. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat has opened a drawer and entered inside. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking and singing. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman fries a slice of meat. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A child is saying something with Sign Language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A person is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="225"> The two officers danced and sang in front of the band. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is pouring ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two young people are riding in a car laughing. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling happily. </seg>
<seg id="231"> One girl is knitting while another girl is talking to her. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A drill sergeant is inspecting a barracks. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person holds a hedgehog in their hand. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A person is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman dances by a bonfire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog is opening a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man fishes. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman fries a slice of meat. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is adding ingredients to a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is dangling a live mouse for a snake to eat. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref4">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is talking and eating a spoonful of chili. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man has his hand raised to his face. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is petting two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat is jumping into a box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is dangling a mouse near a snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is removing the skin and bones from a cooked fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing ping pong. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A group of people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A girl is riding her horse in training in a riding ring. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine is sharpening a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding on an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is measuring leg of another woman. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog is opening a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is resting on a counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is jumping rope outside. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A child is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman is climbing down a rope. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is happily picking berries. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man cuts an onion with a butcher's knife. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is chatting with a woman on internet. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is cooking a quesadilla in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and a woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing by a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A man is brushing the sole of his bare foot using a tooth brush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> An older woman is peeling potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is giving an interview in front of a lot of microphones. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on a mobile. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman beats two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing something from a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A Lorie is eating its food. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A drill sergeant is speaking to soldiers standing in attention. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A dog is wagging its tail. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is brushing or patting the top of a sunflower with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="48"> The men are fighting using martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is typing keys. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five kittens are eating out of five dishes. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog is opening a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man in a library is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A balls rolls over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> The men are having a conversation. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Men are rolling big tyre. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing and signing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is playing the electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A drill sergeant is speaking to soldiers standing in attention. </seg>
<seg id="63"> a man is talking on the telephone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man does a backflip off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A girl is eating a piece of chicken. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is draining the water from cooked pasta. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A little boy is splashing around in the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is drinking from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is jumping a wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling eggs in a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="73"> Someone is cleaning a animal. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man rises from a swamp. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person draws an old woman's face on a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda is lounging around. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A girl is watering plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is angry with a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A women is chopping the onions and green chili,s. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is beating another man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A girl is slicing a butter into two pieces. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino follows it's parent. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A balls rolls over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is fighting with a man. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing drums </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A chef is slicing a bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two panda cubs play with each other. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is makes a call. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is licking a small bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A dog is wagging its tail. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A woman is peeling a papaya with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="96"> Someone is pouring a can of tomato sauce into a pan of sausages. </seg>
<seg id="97"> Someone is pouring olive oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman cracks an egg in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is lighting a match and sets the whole match box on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man pushes a large tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding an amphibian. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is pouring two small bowls of liquid into a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is pulling a ball out of his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is sewing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man is training a boy to bat. </seg>
<seg id="107"> Two cameras are sitting side by side one of them is in flames. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A guy is playing an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman is scrubbing a zucchini with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman cuts a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and a woman are running toward the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="112"> a man is talking on the telephone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is putting flour on a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> Someone cracked to eggs into a bowl </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing on ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is cutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A loris is biting a man's figure. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A man is brushing the sole of his bare foot using a tooth brush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting a very heavy barbell. </seg>
<seg id="123"> The men are fighting using martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse is rolling on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five kittens are eating out of five dishes. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog knocks a boy into the water twice. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is typing keys. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman is boiling finger in the water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is peeling a large potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is breaking wood with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing something from a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is cutting a paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> Yakati machinthi lakadama kanu pade che. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is doing a magic trick with cards. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person is stirring a food with spoon. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is firing a shotgun down a range. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A horse drops its rider. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men are dancing to music on a concrete surface with aircrafts in the background. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman cracks eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> A man is doing back flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing the violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is cooking a quesadilla in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A model train is riding on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A girl is riding her horse in training in a riding ring. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is chopping octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman is picking a water-pot. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is mixing food together in a large metal bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> Yakati machinthi lakadama kanu pade che. </seg>
<seg id="153"> Yakati machinthi lakadama kanu pade che. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A girl pops a Pepsi can and takes a sip. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A toddler rides her scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man in a chef's hat is cleaning off the edge of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man dives off of a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is doing some skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A band is playing onstage. </seg>
<seg id="161"> A group of people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman first cuts the stem and then chops a broccoli flowerette into smaller pieces. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman beats two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is cutting a green vegetable with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is pretending to cry. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is smiling and laughing and crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat is climbing into a storage box. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is applying cosmetics to a man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A person is petting a squirming rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> The women are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl eats a cup cake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is licking a small bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is doing some skating stunts. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle and fishes are swimming under the water. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is walking in a watery field. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is swinging from a ceiling fall and then gets thrown off of it. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A group of men are sawing through a log with giant two-person saws. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is spreading out dough. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Men are jumping. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is pressing microwave buttons. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck is driving down a street. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is trying to eat a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is doing exercise. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man catches a fish. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A person is petting a baby sloth. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is juggling a soccer ball with his feet in a parking lot. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is draining the water from cooked pasta. </seg>
<seg id="197"> Yakati machinthi lakadama kanu pade che. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a baby monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is peeling an orange. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is drawing a polygon with an X inside it. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is afraid to jump into a lake to get his ball. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl eats a cup cake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a shoe. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A cook spreads cheese onto a raw pizza crust. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A girl is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A woman is boiling noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog is running on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing a eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman is combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is happily picking berries. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is tapping her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man is praying in the center of road. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A soccer player scores a goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A person is brushing a cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Girls are swimming in the swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is climbing into a storage box. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking down a city sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is frying meat. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A young girl is using sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A woman is boiling noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> The women are singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is adding ingredients to a small glass dish. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A boy is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is smiling and laughing and crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A couple of girls are sitting on a couch crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A drill sergeant is speaking to soldiers standing in attention. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is carrying a rat in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A person is petting a squirming rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman dances in front of a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man plays a wind instrument. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog is opening a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man sliced a robe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A girl plays with her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is fishing in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is frying meat. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A girl plays with her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is adding vinegar, sugar and black pepper to ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is dangling a mouse near a snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref5">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman is riding a horse down a field. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is tasting something in a spoon. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is thinking. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is petting two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat is jumping into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is feeding a mice to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is removing the skin and bones from a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing table tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A man and a woman are dancing together to music in a ball room. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is riding a horse along the perimeter of a fenced area. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine is sharpening a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is breaking an egg on the side of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is measuring another woman. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog is opening a can of dogfood with his mouth and starts to eat. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is sitting at a counter in a store. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is jumping rope. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A child is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman swings down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is clipping flowers. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is cutting an onion into slices. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A young man a double thumb up to a video he is watching. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is cooking a tortilla in a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and a woman are walking through a field. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man kneels down with a football. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A person is rubbing a feet with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is giving an interview to a number of tv reporters. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking in phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing on a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A man is playing the piano with a bass base. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is wiping off a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A baby sloth is eating a carrot. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A drill sergeant is speaking to some soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A dog on the bed growls as the camera approaches, </seg>
<seg id="46"> A couple of men are fighting in a corral full of cattle. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is holding dead sunflowers. </seg>
<seg id="48"> The men did martial arts together in the field. </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing a piano keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Kittens are eating their foods. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog is opening a can of dogfood with his mouth and starts to eat. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing on a road. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A big green ball is rolling and knocking over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two Indian men have a conversation. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing and singing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A drill sergeant is speaking to some soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is taking on his mobile. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is diving in the swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is adding something to a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A little boy is splashing mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is drinking milk from a plate. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is jumping up onto a stone wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A person is washing his pet rat. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man is climbing up from mud water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing a picture on a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda is lying on logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A girl toddler is watering some plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is speaking to a woman </seg>
<seg id="79"> chopping vegitables </seg>
<seg id="80"> A couple is walking in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is being hit on the buttock with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman in slicing through a block of tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino is walking behind its mother. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A big green ball is rolling and knocking over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is practicing martial arts moves with a man. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is playing on a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is slicing a french bread loaf. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two baby pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A child plays with a toy phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A man is feeding a cat. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A dog on the bed growls as the camera approaches, </seg>
<seg id="95"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A person is pouring a souse in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A person is pouring oil in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A couple is walking in a forest. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is lighting a matchbook cover on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is moving a branch from a walking path. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding frog in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is adding  oil in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is pulling eggs from his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is stitching clothes. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A person is showing how to bat in cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A camera is burning. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man is playing a cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman is washing vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is cutting a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and a woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is taking on his mobile. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is adding flour to meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A person is adding eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing on the ceiling of a room. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is gutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> Someone is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A person is petting a baby sloth. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A person is rubbing a feet with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting weight. </seg>
<seg id="123"> The men did martial arts together in the field. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A black horse is rolling on the ground and then stands up. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Kittens are eating their foods. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog knocks a little boy over in a puddle. </seg>
<seg id="127"> Someone is typing on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is looking out of the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman is adding cut green beans to boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is breaking tiles with his hands. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is wiping off a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is cutting a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A woman is drilling a hole through a board. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is doing trick with play cards. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person is stirring a pot of chili on a stove. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is shooting at a target with a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A horse is falling in the sand. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman cracks open two eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Different children jump on different trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing a fiddle on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is cooking a tortilla in a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy car is hit by a toy train. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is riding a horse along the perimeter of a fenced area. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is bouncing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is cutting something. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman is picking a can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A man is stirring something in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A woman is drilling a hole through a board. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A woman is drilling a hole through a board. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is opening a can of pop and drinking it. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A girl is riding a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A chef is preparing some food. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man dives off of a stone cliff into a river below. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is doing stunts on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A band is singing. </seg>
<seg id="161"> Peoples are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is chopping broccoli with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is taking the seeds out of a pepper and then dicing it. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is weeping. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat is opening a box. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is applying makeup around a man's eye. </seg>
<seg id="170"> Someone is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a motorcycle down a pathway past a woman. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three individuals do aerobic exercises. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A man is feeding a cat. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is doing stunts on a skateboard. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A sea turtle is hunting for fish. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is wading through water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is caught on a fan and spinning. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Men are cutting wood. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is spreading out dough. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Men jump off of vending machines. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is pushing buttons on a microwave oven. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck is going down a hill. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat plays with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A bodybuilder is doing bicep curls with weights. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is lifting dumbbells. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man is fishing. </seg>
<seg id="194"> Someone is petting a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="195"> Men are doing tricks with football. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is adding something to a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A woman is drilling a hole through a board. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a monkey in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is peeling a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is drawing on a digital dry erase board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is afraid to jump into the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting through a cowboy boot with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is putting shredded cheese on two pizzas. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A girl is shown playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A woman is putting noodles into boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog plays by a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing egg plant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman is curling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is clipping flowers. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is tapping her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is cutting a skinny potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man is praying in the middle of the road. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A soccer player scores a goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is brushing a cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> A group of swimmers are diving into the water for a race. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is opening a box. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking down a sidewalk singing. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is frying something. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is talking with action. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A woman is putting noodles into boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two officers danced on the floor with the band. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A man is adding something to a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing two keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A young man is driving a car while smiling at his passenger. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling. </seg>
<seg id="231"> Women are stitching. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A drill sergeant is speaking to some soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is holding a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="234"> Someone is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman dances next to a bonfire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog is opening a can of dogfood with his mouth and starts to eat. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A little girl fusses with and brushes her wet hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is fishing in the river. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is frying something. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A little girl fusses with and brushes her wet hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is mixing food in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is feeding a mice to a snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref6">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is tasting something. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man putting his fingers beside his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is petting two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps into a box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is feeding a mouse to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is preparing fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two players are playing table tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A man and woman is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding a square paper piece. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is riding a horse in an open enclosed ground. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is rowing a boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine sharpens a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A blonde woman is riding an elephant through a group of people. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is breaking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is measuring a woman's ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog is opening a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is sitting at a magazine booth. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is jumping rope. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A child plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman is descending from a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is cutting flowers. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is cutting an onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is positioning a web camera. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and a woman are walking together through a field. </seg>
<seg id="32"> A man kneels down. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man plays a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A person is scrubbing their feet with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling potatoes with a vegetable peeler. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is giving an interview. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on the telephone as another man listens. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is wiping a board and speaking to other man. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A slow loris is eating something. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A drill sergeant is walking. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A puppy is sitting on a bed with a dog. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is holding huge sunflowers. </seg>
<seg id="48"> three boys are doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is typing. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="51"> A group of kittens are lined up eating from dishes. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog is opening a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man dances on a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A big green ball knocks a potato over. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is looking at a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two Indian men have a discussion. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Men are tumbling tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing in the rain in a garden. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is singing and playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A drill sergeant is walking. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is diving into a swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating chicken. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is draining pasta water into a sink. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A boy is playing in mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is drinking milk from the plate. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is jumping over a fence. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A person is washing a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man rises up from a mud hole. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing a picture. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda rolls around on a stack of logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A little girl is watering plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is speaking to a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A cook is slicing up an onion and green beans. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and a woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is getting hit in the butt. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is slicing some butter. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhinoceros follows his mother as they walk around a pen. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A big green ball knocks a potato over. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Some teenage girls are dancing for the camera. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is showing fight stunts. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is making a phone call. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is playing. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A puppy is sitting on a bed with a dog. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A chef pours sauce into a sausage pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A chef oils a pan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> An old woman is breaking egg. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and a woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is lighting a matchbook on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is moving a large tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man holds a small, slimey frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is pouring liquid into a skillet on the stove. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is pulling eggs out of his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A person is using a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man teaches a boy the proper cricket stance. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person is heating up a camera with a blowtorch. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man is playing a cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman is scrubbing a zucchini with a vegetable brush. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and and woman are running together, holding hands. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is flouring a piece of pork. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A chef cracks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing on the ceiling, while a group of spectators are dancing on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman is pouring an egg into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man cuts the skin off of a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A man is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A slow loris is biting a person's hand. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A person is scrubbing their feet with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting weight. </seg>
<seg id="123"> three boys are doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse is standing up. </seg>
<seg id="125"> A group of kittens are lined up eating from dishes. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog knocks down a child, twice. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is typing. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is looking out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman is boiling some vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is karate chopping bricks. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is wiping a board and speaking to other man. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is ripping a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is performing a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A ]person is stirring something in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is shooting at some targets. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A horse stumbles and falls after a jump and the rider is knocked off. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men dance in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman cracks two eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Kids are doing tricks on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing guitar standing on roof top. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is cooking something. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train comes round the corner, dashes and throws off a red car parked on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is riding a horse in an open enclosed ground. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is jumping over trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is cutting an octopus tentacle into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman is picking up a water can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is mixing food in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A man is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is drinking a coke. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A small girl is riding a scooter on the pathway of her house. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is cleaning the edge of a container of food. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man does a high dive off of a cliff into the river below. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is riding a skateboard on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is singing and playing the guitar on stage along with a band of musicians. </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing together near a house. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is chopping broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is mixing eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person slices and dices a large green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is crying on another man. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A bay is crawling. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat is opening a draw and climbing into it. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is applying makeup to a mans face. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is stroking a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a mo-pad. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three kids are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl is eating cup cake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is playing. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is riding a skateboard on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is swimming in water. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is wading through marshland. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is swinging on a fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Several men are first sawing, then carrying palm trees. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is unrolling a coiled sheet of readymade dough on the kithen counter. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Three men are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is putting a cup into the microwave oven. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is drinking milk from a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A car is moving. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is playing with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is lifting dumbbells. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man is fishing off a pier with a woman. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A woman is stroking a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is doing tricks with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is draining pasta water into a sink. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is peeling orange. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is drawing on an eraser board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is barking at a ball. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl is eating cup cake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a shoe with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is making pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> A woman puts noodles in a pot of hot water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog is hiding behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is amusing himself with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A person with a knife is slicing an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A girl brushes her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is cutting flowers. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is making sound with finger. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is cutting potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man is praying in the street. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is cutting up some meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A soccer team scores a goal on a rebound. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A cats fur is being brushed. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Peoples are swimming. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is opening a draw and climbing into it. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking down a sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is frying a piece of meat in a large skillet. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is doing sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A woman puts noodles in a pot of hot water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two police women are singing and  dancing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is placing some ingredients into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing two keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A man is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A bay is crawling. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A young woman is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A drill sergeant is walking. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person holds a small porcupine in one hand. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A man is stroking a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing by a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog is opening a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is demonstrating a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A little girl is brushing her wet hair in the mirror. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is fishing. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is frying a piece of meat in a large skillet. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A little girl is brushing her wet hair in the mirror. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is mixing ingrediants. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is feeding a mouse to a snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref7">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A girl is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is eating chili. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is picking his teeth. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is petting two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is feeding a rat to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is deboning a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing table tennis rather aggressively. </seg>
<seg id="9"> Men and women are dancing in their pair on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding a yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is rowing a small boat in a river. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine sharpens a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is cracking a egg. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse along a perimeter. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A girl is measuring another girls ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog is playing with a can. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is sitting behind a store counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is jumping rope. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A kid plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman trims a flower plant. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is cutting and onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A teenager talks to a girl over a webcam. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is making a quesadilla in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and a woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="32"> One boy is talking with other man. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A boy is cleaning his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman peels a potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is speaking into microphones. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on a mobile phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man sings while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A person is mixing ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A person is playing an electric keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A loris is eating a piece of food. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A drill sergeant talks to his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A small dog is laying on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> A man is attacking another man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is holding two sunflowers. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three boys in karate costumes are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person is typing on a stenographer. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing an electric keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Kittens are drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog is playing with a can. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man wearing a suit is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A green ball knocks over a potato that was standing on end. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is looking at numbers. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are having a discussion. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men push monstrous tires along the ground. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is singing on stage as he strums a guitar too. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A drill sergeant talks to his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking in a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is diving off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is plucking a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating a chicken wing. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is shaking a container over a kitchen sink. </seg>
<seg id="68"> An angry boy is splashing mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man jumps onto a short wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A person washes a small porcupine in a pan of water. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man is rising from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing on a paper. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A baby panda is laying around. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A little girl sprays her plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is standing behind a woman talking to her. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A person is slicing up an onion into little pieces. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and a woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is hitting another with a bat. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is carefully slicing tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino is following it's mother. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A green ball knocks over a potato that was standing on end. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man sings into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="86"> The girls are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is doing martial arts moves. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing the drums under spotlight. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man sings while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man slices bread with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two baby pandas are wrestling with each other. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A little boy plays with a toy phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is licking, and rubbing a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A small dog is laying on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A woman is peeling a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man is adding sauce to pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> Someone is pouring oil into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and a woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is lighting a pack of matches on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is carrying a huge tree branch into a clearing. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is adding oil to frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is taking eggs from his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is using a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man is instructing another man how to bat in cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person is burning cameras. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A person scrubs a vegetable with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and a woman run down a path. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking in a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is seasoning a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> Someone is cracking a egg. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is cutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A shotgun is being shot off in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A loris is biting a person's finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A boy is cleaning his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three boys in karate costumes are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse is standing. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Kittens are drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog knocks over a boy twice. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A person is typing on a stenographer. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is perched on a box with it's front paws on a window sill looking out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> okra is cooking in boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is striking wooden boards with his fist. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is tearing paper along a crease. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is drilling a wood block. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man performs a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A man is stirring the contents of a pan. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is shooting at targets with a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A man gets knocked off of a horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of people are performing a  musical act. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman cracks two eggs into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Kids doing flips on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing the violin on the top of a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is making a quesadilla in a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train crashes into a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is pouncing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is slicing octopus with a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A girl is picking up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person stirs a bowl full of food. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is drilling a wood block. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A man is drilling a wood block. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman drinks from a can of soda pop. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A little girl peddling a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A chef wipes off the edge of a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man is diving in the river. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is riding on a skateboard ramp. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A man is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="161"> Some people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man is slicing potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is chopping broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A person is mixing ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman chops a capsicum into two, deseeds one half and thereafter chops it into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Two men ham it up. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat is opening a drawer and climbing inside. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is doing a joker make up on a man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A rabbit is getting pet. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl is eating a small cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is licking, and rubbing a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is riding on a skateboard ramp. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle follows some fish around at the bottom of the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A small monkey walks through water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat gets stuck on a moving ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Some men are sawing. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is unrolling a flour crust on a cookie sheet. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man microwaves a teacup. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is drinking from a dish of milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck is driving down a road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A kitten is playing with a water melon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man pulls a fish out of the water with his fishing pole. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A loris is raising both its arms to be scratched underneath. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy is kicking a soccer ball around. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is shaking a container over a kitchen sink. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is drilling a wood block. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman carefully slices off a piece of lemon rind. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is drawing some figures. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is trying to jump into water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl is eating a small cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man cuts of the toe end of a boot with a machete. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is sprinkling something to pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Noodles are being boiled. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog is barking. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman cuts up a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman trims a flower plant. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is rubbing its head on piano keys while tapping one of the keys with its paw. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is tapping her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is cutting up a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man runs and sits in front of still traffic and bends down back and forth, touching his hands on the road. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> A soccer team scores a goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A woman is combing a cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Several women are lining up to do a swimming racing in a lake. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is opening a drawer and climbing inside. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking down the city sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is placing food in a pot of hot water. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is acting something. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Noodles are being boiled. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two uniformed female police officers are dancing and singing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> Someone is mixing ingrediants. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing two pianos. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two friends are laughing while taking a drive in car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A woman is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A drill sergeant talks to his recruits. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone is holding a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A rabbit is getting pet. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing by a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog is playing with a can. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A little girl is playing with her hair in the bathroom. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is fishing. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is placing food in a pot of hot water. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A little girl is playing with her hair in the bathroom. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is pouring ingredients into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is feeding a rat to a snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref8">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman is riding a brown horse on a muddy pathway surrounded by greenery. </seg>
<seg id="2"> Someone is tasting food. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is looking. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is singing and stroking dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is holding a white rat by it's tale over an aquarium containing a large snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is removing skin, and bones from a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Men are playing ping pong. </seg>
<seg id="9"> Men and women are dancing slowly. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding a yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man paddles a canoe across a pond. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A new white colored pencil is sharpened at the tip by a CNC lathe machine. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman rides an elephant in front of an adoring crowd. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A young woman rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> One woman is measuring another woman's ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog is trying to eat from a tin. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is sitting in a book shop. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is jumproping. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A little boy is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman is descending on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby is sitting on a couch laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is cutting some flowers. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is cutting up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is talking to a woman via internet video chat. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is folding a tortilla in half. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and a woman walk across a field. </seg>
<seg id="32"> One man knelt with a football in front of another man. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A woman is brushing her feet. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is speaking to reporters. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man talks on a cellphone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman stirs eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A person is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a chalkboard with an eraser. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A loris is eating a fruit. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is talking to a group of soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A small dog lays on a bed and wags his tail. </seg>
<seg id="46"> People are fighting in a cow pen. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is knocking seeds out of a sunflower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three boys sparring. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person types on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five cats are eating together. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog is trying to eat from a tin. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man speaks while standing in front of a bookcase. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A green ball rolls over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is pointing at a calender on the wall. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are speaking each other. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Men are pushing large tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man playing an electric guitar is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is talking to a group of soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is doing a back flip into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is standing in front of a microphone holding a violin in one hand and a violin bow in the other. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating meat. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is shaking a container. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A boy is playing in the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man is hopping onto a wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling to eggs in a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A hedgehog is getting a bath. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man rises up out of a swamp. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing on paper. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda bear is laying down. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A small girl is spraying water on the potted plants in her garden using a garden water sprayer. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is talking sternly to a woman with a bruise on her forehead, standing very close to her. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman chops an onion into fine pieces after slicing it initially. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and woman are walking together through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man is striking another man in the butt with an object. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman with a knife is horizontally slicing a block of tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino is following its mom. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A green ball rolls over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="86"> The girls danced around the room. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A chimpanzee is doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Baby pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A little boy is playing with a toy telephone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is sniffing a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A small dog lays on a bed and wags his tail. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A woman is peeling the skin of a ripe papaya using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man pours tomato sauce into a pan with meat. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is adding oil to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is pouring eggs into a dish. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and woman are walking together through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is mimicking by looking fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is moving a tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A woman is handling a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is pouring oil into frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man pulls ping pong balls out of his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is sewing with a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man teaches a boy how to swing a cricket bat. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person is torching two cameras to test their durability. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman is washing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man, and a woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman puts flour on a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is gutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A person is firring a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> An animal bites a person's finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A woman is brushing her feet. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man lifts heavy weights. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three boys sparring. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse rolls over on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five cats are eating together. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog knocks over a child in a flooded lawn. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A person types on a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat looks out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> Someone is boiling some peppers. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man karate chops a stack of bricks. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a chalkboard with an eraser. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man tears a piece of paper in half. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A woman is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A guy is performing a magic trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> Someone is stirring a pot of stew. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is shooting at targets. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A man is falling down when he is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A line of people are dancing in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman is adding an egg into the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> People are jumping on trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A young man is standing on a roof, playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A person is folding a tortilla in half. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train hit a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is riding on a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman with a knife is cutting a tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A girl picks up a water can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A man is stirring some ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A woman is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A woman is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman opens, and drinks a cola. </seg>
<seg id="156"> The little girl rode her scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is wiping a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man is diving into the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is skateboarding on a ramp. </seg>
<seg id="160"> A three-piece band plays. </seg>
<seg id="161"> Teenagers are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man sliced a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is chopping broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman stirs eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is chopping and preparing a green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is crying. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling along the floor while smiling. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat is opening a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is painting a man's face. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A bunny is squirming as a person touches it. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing guitar on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is sniffing a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is skateboarding on a ramp. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle walks on the bottom of the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is wading through the water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is swinging on a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Men are sawing logs. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is unrolling dough and spreading it in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Three men are jumping off a vending machine. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man puts a cup in the microwave. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten drinks milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck is being driven on a road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is playing with a watermelon on a floor. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is lifting a weight. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man is catching a fish. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A person rubs a small furry animal. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy is playing with a ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is shaking a container. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A woman is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a small monkey in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is cutting a piece of peeling off a food. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is writing on a  school board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is walking back and forth on a dock. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is putting shredded cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman is playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Noodles are being mixed. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog is hiding behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat plays with a small antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is cutting vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman is combing her hair and curls the ends using a hair roller brush. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is cutting some flowers. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is striking a piano key repeatedly. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is striking a table with her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man runs into the middle of the street and makes worshiping gestures. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing meat with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="217"> Men are playing a foot-ball on the play ground. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man is brushing a cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> People are diving into water. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat is opening a drawer. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking down the sidewalk and singing. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman deep fries a piece of breaded meat. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is using signing language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Noodles are being mixed. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women are dancing and singing in front of a crowd. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is adding several ingredients to a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man is playing two pianos. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A driver is talking with his passenger. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling along the floor while smiling. </seg>
<seg id="231"> Two girls are knitting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is talking to a group of soldiers. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone is holding a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A bunny is squirming as a person touches it. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing some drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing by a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog is trying to eat from a tin. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cuts a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A little girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is fishing. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman deep fries a piece of breaded meat. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A little girl is styling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is pouring oil and seasoning into a bowl of cut up vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is holding a white rat by it's tale over an aquarium containing a large snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref9">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman riding a horse very fast </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is eating some chili. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is holding his hand to his mouth. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is sitting on the front steps of a building holding a guitar while he pets two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps into a cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is showing a rat to snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is removing bones from a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men play ping pong. </seg>
<seg id="9"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is paddling a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A pencil is being sharpened with a robotic lathe. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding on an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> The lady measured the other woman's ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog opens a can by itself. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is sitting on a shopping desk. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is skipping on the pathway outside his house. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A little boy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman is climbing down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby moves around on a sofa. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A young lady is cutting flowers. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A guy is setting up a web cam. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man folds a tortilla over in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and a woman walking in a garden are talking to each other as music plays in the background. </seg>
<seg id="32"> The man knelt down with the football. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing the saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A boy is scrubbing his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is speaking to reporters. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is singing a song while simultaneously strumming his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is scrambling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> An individual's right hand plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> An animal eats a piece of fruit. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A small dog lies on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is rubbing the head of a sunflower with his hand. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three guys are karate fighting. </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone is using a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing an electronic keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Kittens are eating from dishes. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding on a bike with his luggage. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog opens a can by itself. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A large ball knocks over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is pointing at days on a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are speaking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Men are moving tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Jimi Hendrix is playing the guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is doing a backwards double-flip off a diving board and into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man played an instrument and sang into a microphone on stage. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman eats a chicken drumstick. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is draining a dish of food. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A kid is playing in dirt. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> Someone is jumping over a wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling two eggs in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="73"> An animal is being bathed. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man is emerging from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing some cartoon. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A small girl is watering the plant. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is talking to a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman cuts and dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and a woman walk through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man strikes another man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is slicing tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> An animal is walking around. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A large ball knocks over a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three girls are dancing in the room. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is practicing karate. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is singing a song while simultaneously strumming his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is slicing a whole bread loaf using a bread knife. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two pandas wrestle with each other. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is playing on a toy phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is licking a container. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A small dog lies on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A woman is slicing a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A person pours a can of sauce into a pot of meat. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is pouring oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman breaks an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and a woman walk through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man is screaming,looking at the fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is carrying a tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is pouring oil into a frying pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man removes eggs from his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> Someone is sewing things. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man is helping a boy with his cricket stance. </seg>
<seg id="107"> Someone is burning cameras with a torch. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man is playing the cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman is cleaning a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and woman are running outside. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is putting flour onto some meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A person breaks an egg into a small bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> a woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is cutting up a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A guy is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A small animal is chewing on a finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is sitting on the back of a shiny black horse, which is prancing on an open ground. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A boy is scrubbing his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man lifts weights upto his thigh level and then puts it back on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three guys are karate fighting. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse is standing up. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Kittens are eating from dishes. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog makes a child fall into water. </seg>
<seg id="127"> Someone is using a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat stares out a window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman is adding vegetables to a pot. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman peels a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is chopping boards in half. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man tears off the excess from a folded sheet of white paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A person drills a hole through a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is doing a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl plays a flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> Someone is stirring soup. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is shooting shotgun slugs across a hill. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A man is falling from horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are dancing in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman is breaking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="143"> People do flips on trampolines. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing a fiddle on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man folds a tortilla over in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train is hitting a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman cuts up a piece of octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman is holding a water can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A man is stirring a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A person drills a hole through a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A person drills a hole through a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is drinking a soda pop. </seg>
<seg id="156"> The little girl is riding her scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is wiping food from a bowls rim. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man is diving off a high cliff into the water below. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man is skateboarding. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Bob Marley is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man slices a peeled potato into thick slices and thereafter cuts each of them into half. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is cutting a stalk of broccoli into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is scrambling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is slicing a big pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> Two men are crying. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby crawls along the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is painting the area around the left eye of a man, in black. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A rabbit struggles away from a human hand. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a motor scooter. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people are exercising. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl nibbles a tiny cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is licking a container. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man is skateboarding. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is walking underwater. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey walking thru a shallow body of water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is swinging from a fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Four men are cutting wood. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is unrolling dough on a pan. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Three men jump up and push themselves off a counter. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man sets the timing/temperature knobs on the menu of the microwave owen in the kitchen and is waiting. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is drinking some milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck is moving down the street. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat attacks a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is pumping iron. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> People are catching fish. </seg>
<seg id="194"> Someone is petting a monkey. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is kicking a soccer ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is draining a dish of food. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A person drills a hole through a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a small monkey in his left hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman cuts off a piece of lemon rind. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A person is drawing on a large touchscreen. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is walking back and forth on a pier. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl nibbles a tiny cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a boot in half with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A person is spreading cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman is playing the fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Noodles are cooking in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog is running behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with a toy. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A girl doing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A young lady is cutting flowers. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is tapping keys on a piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A girl taps her fingernails on the counter. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man runs into the middle of the street where he gets down on his knees and starts to bow down. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> Men are playing soccer. </seg>
<seg id="218"> Someone is brushing a cats hair. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Some women dive into the water. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs in. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking down the street singing. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is deep frying a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is practicing her sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Noodles are cooking in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women are dancing and singing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> the lady added ingredients to the water in the bowl and whisked it. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man played the organ. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two people are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby crawls along the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> Two women are crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone is holding an animal. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A rabbit struggles away from a human hand. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing near a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a large flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog opens a can by itself. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cuts a thick rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A small girl standing in front of the bathroom mirror is straightening her hair using her fingers and then combs it with a hair brush. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is fishing. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is deep frying a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A small girl standing in front of the bathroom mirror is straightening her hair using her fingers and then combs it with a hair brush. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is preparing some food. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is showing a rat to snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref10">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> The horse and rider ran down a dirt rode. </seg>
<seg id="2"> The man tasted his chili. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man has his left hand fingers placed on his mouth wondering what to say. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man pets a couple of dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps into a really tall box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is teasing a snake with a mouse. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is peeling some fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing ping pong. </seg>
<seg id="9"> Several couples are dancing on the dance floor. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A young woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is rowing a boat on water using an oar. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A pencil is being sharpened. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is cracking an egg open into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse which is trotting slowly along the periphery of a sandy enclosure in the open. </seg>
<seg id="18"> The woman is measuring the other woman. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog opens a can of food with his teeth. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is standing with it's front paws resting on a counter filled with magazines. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man jumps rope in his front yard. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A little boy is playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman climbs down off of a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby on a couch is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A girl is pruning a bush. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is slicing an onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A guy is using a webcam. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is tracking in the wood. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is folding something in a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and woman are walking in a meadow. </seg>
<seg id="32"> The men are talking. </seg>
<seg id="33"> The man played the sax in the room. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> Someone is washing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is speaking. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> Someone is beating an egg. </seg>
<seg id="41"> Someone is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man erases writing on a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A Slow Loris is eating something. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A military officer is instructing subordinates. </seg>
<seg id="45"> Dogs are lying on a bed, one is wagging its tail. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is showing sunflowers. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three guys have a martial arts fight. </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone is typing. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man is playing keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five cats eat food from saucers. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding on a motor bike. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog opens a can of food with his teeth. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is dancing in the street. </seg>
<seg id="55"> Someone is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A large green ball hits a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy is pointing at numbers on a chart, then turns around and says something. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are talking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men are flipping over oversized tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Jimi Hendrix is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A military officer is instructing subordinates. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man is jumping off a low diving board and doing a back flip dive. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man plays a string instrument. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating something. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is draining some pasta. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A boy is hitting the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is licking from a saucer of milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing his acoustic guitar </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man jumps up on a wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A person is bathing a hedgehog in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man raises up out of muddy water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing with a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="76"> The panda rested on the logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A very young girl sprays water on plants and flowers. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is talking to a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman cutting onions. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man, and woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A man whacks another guy in the rear with a wooden club. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is cutting tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino is walking around his pen with his mother. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A large green ball hits a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three girls are dancing in their room. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is karate kicking a person. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Someone slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A kid is playing on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is sniffing a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Dogs are lying on a bed, one is wagging its tail. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A woman is using a large knife to peel a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man is pouring some sauce into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A woman is pouring olive oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man, and woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man lights a match and the whole book of matches burst into flames. </seg>
<seg id="101"> Someone is moving a tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is putting oil into a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="104"> Steve Martin performs onstage. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman is sewing fabric squares. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Two guys are demonstrating a game. </seg>
<seg id="107"> Someone is burning cameras with a blow torch. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man plays the violin. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A person is scrubbing a zucchini. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and woman are running down the street. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is breading meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is breaking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is dancing upside-down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man cuts a raw fish with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="118"> Someone is firing a gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A monkey is biting a finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man rides a horse through a field. </seg>
<seg id="121"> Someone is washing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man lifts weights. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three guys have a martial arts fight. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse stands up. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five cats eat food from saucers. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A dog pushes a toddler into a rain puddle. </seg>
<seg id="127"> Someone is typing. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat, perched on a table, looks out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> The lady added the pea pods to the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman peels a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man breaks something with his hands. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man erases writing on a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A person is tearing a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> Someone is drilling a hole. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is doing a magic trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl plays a wind instrument. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person is stirring some chili. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is shooting with a gun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A person falls off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are dancing in front of the plane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman is cracking an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> People jump on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A guy plays a fiddle while standing on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is folding something in a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train is striking a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A young woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is cutting octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> The lady picked up the watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is mixing a salad. </seg>
<seg id="152"> Someone is drilling a hole. </seg>
<seg id="153"> Someone is drilling a hole. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man sang into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A girl opens a drink. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A girl is riding a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A chef is cleaning up a bowl of soup. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A man is jumping into water from a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man moving rapidly on a skateboard goes up a slope, does a couple of summersaults and falls down while landing. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Bob Marley performs a song on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="161"> Several people are dancing on the patio. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A man slices a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is cutting broccoli with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="164"> Someone is beating an egg. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A woman is slicing a pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is crying. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling across the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs inside. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is painting the face of a man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A girl is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> Someone is riding a moped. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people are marching in place. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl is eating a cup cake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is sniffing a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man moving rapidly on a skateboard goes up a slope, does a couple of summersaults and falls down while landing. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle swims. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey swinging its fore arms is walking on its hind legs in a rice field. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat swings on a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> The men are sawing wood. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man roles out a dough-like substance onto a cutting board. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Some men are jumping, and running. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man turns on the microwave. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> Someone is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is playing with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> Someone is working out. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is rapidly lifting small weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> Two men are fishing. </seg>
<seg id="194"> Someone is scratching an animals belly. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A man is tossing and playing around with a football using his legs. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is draining some pasta. </seg>
<seg id="197"> Someone is drilling a hole. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a small primate in one hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is cutting a bit of peel off of a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A teacher drawing a line </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog jumps looks at water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl is eating a cup cake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> Someone cuts a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man puts cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman is playing the fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Pasta is added to a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog runs and hides behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is batting an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> someone is slicing a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="210"> The girl curled her hair with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A girl is pruning a bush. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A girl is drumming her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is slicing a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man runs out into the street and bows down. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> Men are playing soccer. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A person is brushing a cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Swimmers are racing in a lake. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs inside. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking down the street. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is deep frying food. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A young girl is communicating with sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Pasta is added to a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women are dancing together. </seg>
<seg id="226"> The woman is seasoning the oil. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man plays an electronic organ. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two boys are driving. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling across the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A woman seated on a sofa is crocheting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A military officer is instructing subordinates. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person holds a hedgehog in their hand. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A girl is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> Someone is playing drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing to music standing near a bonfire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a wind instrument. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog opens a can of food with his teeth. </seg>
<seg id="240"> The man slced through a thick rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A young girl is playing with her wet hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is holding a fishing rod while sailing on the sea. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is deep frying food. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A young girl is playing with her wet hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is putting ingredients in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is teasing a snake with a mouse. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref11">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A woman rides a horse down a path. </seg>
<seg id="2"> The man is eating. </seg>
<seg id="3"> The man was thinking about something. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man pets a dog. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps into a very large cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man is trying to fed a snake a mouse. </seg>
<seg id="7"> The woman is removing the skin and bones of the fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two people are playing ping pong. </seg>
<seg id="9"> Several couples dance ballroom style. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A person is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> Ladies horseback riding competition . </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is paddling a boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A power lathe is cutting a wooden dowel. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> An egg is cracked and added to the mix. </seg>
<seg id="17"> a woman riding a horse </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman measures another woman's leg. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog opens a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog is watching a store counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A person is skipping rope. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A little boy is singing and playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman slides down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby seated on a sofa is happily laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is cutting flowers from a bush. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is slicing one half of a peeled white onion using a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is talking to a girl on the internet. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is trekking on a mountainous forest pathway with a loaded backpack. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is frying a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and woman are walking together. </seg>
<seg id="32"> Two boys are talking. </seg>
<seg id="33"> The man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A girl is cleaning her foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> The lady peeled the potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is talking to numerous reporters. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> The man sang and played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is scrambling two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="41"> Someone played the keyboard with his right hand. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a blackboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A monkey is eating. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A soldier walks through a barracks and talks. </seg>
<seg id="45"> The dog is on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two men are fighting in a cow pasture. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man is tapping a sunflower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three men are doing karate in a field. </seg>
<seg id="49"> Someone is typing. </seg>
<seg id="50"> a man is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Some kittens are eating. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man rides a motorcycle across a field. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog opens a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man is doing some footwork moves on a road in a scenic location as music plays in the background. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man with glasses is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A large green ball is pushed against a potato kept erect on a table and bounces after falling on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy points out dates on a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are talking to each other. </seg>
<seg id="59"> In a race held, each of the two men is moving a huge tire by tumbling them repeatedly on a road lined with people. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Jimi Hendrix plays an electric guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A soldier walks through a barracks and talks. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man jumps off a diving board, does summersaults and dives into the water of a swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating a piece of chicken. </seg>
<seg id="67"> The man shook the water from the container. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A small boy repeatedly punches a slushy ground and then stands up. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is licking milk from a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> The man jumped over a short wall at night. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is boiling two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> The hedgehog tried to get out of its bath. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man is coming up out of a mud pit. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> The panda is lying down. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A young girl is spraying water on to small plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is talking to a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman dices an onion. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A couple are walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> One man is hitting another man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is slicing tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino follows its mother while walking in an enclosed area filled with grass. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A large green ball is pushed against a potato kept erect on a table and bounces after falling on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The man sang into the microphone on stage. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three girls dance and plays. </seg>
<seg id="87"> The monkey is doing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man is sitting at a set of drums playing them. </seg>
<seg id="89"> The man sang and played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> The lady sliced a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two panda cubs are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is playing with a toy telephone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> The kitten rubbed its face against the bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> The dog is on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> The woman is peeling an orange vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="96"> Someone is pouring tomato sauce into a pot of meat. </seg>
<seg id="97"> Someone is putting oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A couple are walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man lights a match book on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dragging a tree limb. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A purple frog held by a man in his hands is making noise. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is pouring oil into a pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> Steve Martin pulls eggs out of his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A woman stitches a couple of square printed materials together on one side using a sewing machine. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Someone is staning up. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person is torching two cameras. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man plays the violin. </seg>
<seg id="109"> The woman is washing the vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> The man and woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a cell phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A girl is putting flour on meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> Someone is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is singing and dancing on a ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman cracks an egg on a wooden top in the kitchen and puts it into a glass bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> The man is slicing a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A man fires a rifle. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A small mammal is chewing on a person's finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A girl is cleaning her foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A weighlifter picks up a barbell. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three men are doing karate in a field. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse rolls on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Some kittens are eating. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A little boy is knocked down by a dog. </seg>
<seg id="127"> Someone is typing. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A white cat is looking out a window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> The woman is boiling okra. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman peels a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is karate chopping a stack of blocks. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a blackboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A person is tearing a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man does a trick with playing cards. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A woman is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> The man stirred the chili in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is target shooting. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A rider on a horse goes down with the horse and both get back up apparently unharmed. </seg>
<seg id="141"> People are dancing in front of a plane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Peoples are jumping on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is fiddling on a rooftop. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is frying a tortilla. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train runs into a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> Ladies horseback riding competition . </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dogs is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is slicing octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> The woman picked up the watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A man stirs all the ingredients of a Greek salad placed in a large bowl with a flat steel spoon to mix them well. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man sings into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman is opening a soda and drinking it. </seg>
<seg id="156"> The girl is riding a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="157"> The chef is wiping the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A person dives off a cliff into water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man rides his skateboard on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Men are playing musical instruments. </seg>
<seg id="161"> The kids danced on the patio. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A person cuts up potatos. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is cutting broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is scrambling two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="165"> Someone cut a green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is crying. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A small baby is gurgling happily as he crawls on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs into it. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is putting makeup on a man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A animal is being pet. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people are marching. </seg>
<seg id="175"> Someone is eating cupcakes. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is riding on something. </seg>
<seg id="177"> The kitten rubbed its face against the bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man rides his skateboard on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is walking under water. </seg>
<seg id="180"> into the wild </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat gets caught on a ceiling fan and spins around. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Four people saw logs. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man unrolls dough and spreads it over a pan. </seg>
<seg id="184"> A man is jumping off a wall. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging in the dirt. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man uses a microwave. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck is driving down the street. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A kitten is playing with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man is using hand weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man caught a fish. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A lemur with outstretched arms is being scratched by a person. </seg>
<seg id="195"> The man did tricks with a soccer ball with his feet. </seg>
<seg id="196"> The man shook the water from the container. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a tiny monkey in one hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A man is cutting lemon peel. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A teacher is drawing a diagram on the board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog looks at a tennis ball floating in the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> Someone is eating cupcakes. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a cowboy boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is putting cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman is playing the voilin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Someone is cooking noodles. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog runs and hides behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is slicing an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman curls her hair with a brush. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is cutting flowers from a bush. </seg>
<seg id="212"> The cat is playing the piano with his paw. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A girl is tapping her finger nails on a table. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man slices a raw potato into two halves using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man runs to the middle of the street and starts genuflecting. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing pork. </seg>
<seg id="217"> Players are playing football. </seg>
<seg id="218"> The man brushed the white cat's stomach. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Several swimmers jump into the water. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat opens a drawer and climbs into it. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is cooking meat. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl does sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Someone is cooking noodles. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman uses an egg beater on a mixture. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two men are driving in a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A small baby is gurgling happily as he crawls on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> The girls sat on a couch and crocheted. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A soldier walks through a barracks and talks. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone held a hedgehog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A animal is being pet. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man plays a large flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog opens a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="240"> The man used a sword to cut the thick rope. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A young girl is standing in front of a mirror working on her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is pulling on a fishing rod. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is cooking meat. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A young girl is standing in front of a mirror working on her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman is putting ingredients into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man is trying to fed a snake a mouse. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref12">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> The woman is riding the horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man eats chili. </seg>
<seg id="3"> The man is thinking. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man pets his dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps into an empty box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man picks up a mouse from a case holding a snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is removing fish skin and bones with her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing table tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> The couple danced with other couples. </seg>
<seg id="10"> Someone folded a square yellow paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> The girl trotted the horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> The man rowed his boat in the river. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A tool formed the tip of the pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> Egg is cracked into a mixture and blended. </seg>
<seg id="17"> The horse and rider trotted around the ring. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A lady measured the ankles of the woman. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog opens a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog leans against a counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> An overweight man is skipping rope. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A little kid is playing a guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman with a weird hairdo comes down a creeper and lands on the ground. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A baby sits on a couch and laughs. </seg>
<seg id="25"> The woman is tending her garden. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A onion is being sliced. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man chatting with his girl friend on the computer shows a thumbs-up sign, turns the web camera away and walks off. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man with camping gear is walking along a forest trail. </seg>
<seg id="30"> someone is flipping a tortila/ </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and woman is walking in the grand. </seg>
<seg id="32"> Two men are facing each other, one of them has a football in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A person is scrubbing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> The woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A guy plays guitar and sings. </seg>
<seg id="40"> The lady stirred two raw eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> Someone played the keyboard with his right hand. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A animal is eating. </seg>
<seg id="44"> An army drill sergeant inspects his nervous troop. </seg>
<seg id="45"> The dog is wagging his tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> The men are fighting each other. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man rubs a sunflower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three men are doing karate. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is tying on a stenographers machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man played the organ. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five kittens are eating. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man rode his motorcycle on the dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog opens a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="54"> The man did a funny dance! </seg>
<seg id="55"> The man spoke in front of the bookshelves. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A large green ball is rolling into a potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A boy studies a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are talking. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two people flipped tractor tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Jimi Hendrix plays the guitar and sings into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="62"> An army drill sergeant inspects his nervous troop. </seg>
<seg id="63"> The man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A man jumps off a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man standing at a microphone is holding a violin like a guitar and plucking it. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A girl is eating chicken. </seg>
<seg id="67"> The man is shaking the plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="68"> the little boy pounded his fist in the dirt and got dirty. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat laps milk from a dish. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> The man jumped on the wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman is cooking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> The hedgehog is getting a bath. </seg>
<seg id="74"> The man emerged from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A person is drawing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda lounges on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> The girl is spraying the plants with water. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man is talking with a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman dicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A couple is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> The man hit the other man with a bat. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman slices a block of tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> The baby rhino followed his mother. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A large green ball is rolling into a potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three girls dance around. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A chimpanzee is performing karate kicks. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man played his drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A guy plays guitar and sings. </seg>
<seg id="90"> The cook is slicing bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> The boy talked on his play phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> The cat is licking a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> The dog is wagging his tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> The woman is peeling the skin off a papaya. </seg>
<seg id="96"> Someone is pouring ingrediants into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is adding oil to a pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is cracking open eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A couple is walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man lights a matchbook on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> The man moved a large tree branch away. </seg>
<seg id="102"> The man picked up the frog in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is adding oil to a pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> Steve Martin removes two eggs from the zipper area of his pants and places them in a hung basket on the stage. </seg>
<seg id="105"> The lady sewed the materials. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man is instructing a boy on how to play cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> The person lit the cameras on fire. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A man seated is playing the cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman cleans fruit. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A couple are running towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="112"> The man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman is coating a pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="114"> Someone is cracking an egg open. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A man is singing and dancing on the ceiling as other people are dancing on the floor of the room. </seg>
<seg id="116"> The lady cracked the egg in to the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is cutting the skin off a fish with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="118"> The man shot his gun in the air. </seg>
<seg id="119"> An animal is biting a persons finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man rides a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A person is scrubbing their foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A weight lifter lifts a set of barbells from the floor. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three men are doing karate. </seg>
<seg id="124"> The horse rolled in the grass. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five kittens are eating. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A little boy is knocked over by a dog. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is tying on a stenographers machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A white cat is staring out a window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman is boiling okra. </seg>
<seg id="130"> An elderly woman is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> The man chopped through a stack of wood. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A person is tearing paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A person is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is performing a trick with playing cards in front of two other men. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A woman plays on a flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl plays a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> The man is stirring the chili in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A woman falls off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Peoples are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Several groups of children are shown doing flips on trampolines </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is fiddling on a rooftop. </seg>
<seg id="145"> someone is flipping a tortila/ </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train runs over a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> The girl trotted the horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> The dog played on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is slicing up some octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman picks up a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> The cook is stirring the vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A person is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A person is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man sings into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> The girl opened a soda can and took a sip. </seg>
<seg id="156"> a cute small girl driving a bicycle </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is cleaning the edges of a full bowl. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A person is cliff diving into water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A man skateboards on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="160"> People are singing. </seg>
<seg id="161"> The people are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A person is chopping a vegetable into thick slices. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is cutting broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> The lady stirred two raw eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> Someone cut up a green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> On man cried on another man's shoulder. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is laughing and crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat opens the drawer of a storage box and squeezes into it. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman paints a man's face. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A person is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> The man rode his motorcycle to the girl. </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people are walking in place. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man is sitting on the back of a toy bull which is swiveling wildly in different directions. </seg>
<seg id="177"> The cat is licking a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A man skateboards on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="179"> The turtle followed the fish. </seg>
<seg id="180"> The monkey waded through the water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> The cat jumped on the fan pull and spun around the room. </seg>
<seg id="182"> Men are sawing a tree. </seg>
<seg id="183"> The chef is rolling out dough. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Two men jump. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging the earth. </seg>
<seg id="186"> The man is using the microwave. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten is licking up milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> The truck is moving down the road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat plays with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> The man lifted a barbell in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man lifts hand weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> The man dropped the fish he caught back into the water. </seg>
<seg id="194"> The lady scratched the little monkey's armpits! </seg>
<seg id="195"> The man is playing ball with his feet. </seg>
<seg id="196"> The man is shaking the plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A person is drilling a hole in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a tiny monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is peeling something. </seg>
<seg id="200"> The man is drawing on the board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog swims after a tennis ball. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> The man cut through the boot with a large sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> Men are making pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman plays a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Someone is sitring noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog is hiding behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> The cat is playing with a wire. </seg>
<seg id="209"> The lady cut the eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> The woman is curling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> The woman is tending her garden. </seg>
<seg id="212"> The cat is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A girl is tapping her finger nails. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A person is cutting up a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> The Indian knelt in the street and worshipped. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman is slicing tofu to put in the micro wave oven. </seg>
<seg id="217"> Soccer players are kicking a soccer ball into the goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> The man is combing the cat's hair. </seg>
<seg id="219"> The women jumped into the lake and started swimming. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat opens the drawer of a storage box and squeezes into it. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man walks along the sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is deep frying some meat. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is speaking in sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Someone is sitring noodles in water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> The lady whisked the ingredients in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A man plays two keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="228"> The boys are riding a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man plays an acoustic guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is laughing and crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> The woman is knitting. </seg>
<seg id="232"> An army drill sergeant inspects his nervous troop. </seg>
<seg id="233"> The person is holding hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A person is petting a rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man seated is playing a set of drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog opens a can of food. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man uses a huge knife to cut some rope. </seg>
<seg id="241"> The little girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is reeling in a fish. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is deep frying some meat. </seg>
<seg id="244"> The little girl is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman mixes food in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man picks up a mouse from a case holding a snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref13">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A horse is being rode. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is tasting some food while talking into the camera. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man looks perplexed. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man pets some dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat jumps up into a box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man tries to feed a mouse to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman skins some fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing a table tennis match as the audience watches them. </seg>
<seg id="9"> The man and woman are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="10"> Someone is folding a piece of paper into the shape of a triangle. </seg>
<seg id="11"> The horse and rider trotted by the fence. </seg>
<seg id="12"> The man is paddling in a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="13"> Someone is using a lathe to sharpen a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> The girl held her arm up while riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> The lady cracked an egg for the mixer. </seg>
<seg id="17"> The woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is measuring another womans ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog opens a small can of food with its mouth. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog leans on a counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> The man is jumping rope. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A small baby is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> The lady came down the tree on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A small baby is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman trims hedges. </seg>
<seg id="26"> Half an onion is sliced into wedges. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> The man talked to a girl over the internet camera. </seg>
<seg id="29"> The backpacker is hiking. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A man is folding over a tortilla in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and woman is walking together. </seg>
<seg id="32"> Two men are playing football. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man plays the tuba. </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A woman standing uses a toothbrush to scrub off the mud from the sole of her left foot. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman peels vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man is talking over the phone standing in a restaurant kitchen. </seg>
<seg id="39"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> The woman is whisking the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> The keyboards are being played. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A small animal is eating some food. </seg>
<seg id="44"> An army sergeant is walking and talking to a line of soldiers standing next to their beds in their camp room. </seg>
<seg id="45"> The dog wagged his tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two men are fighting in a corral. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man rubs a sunflower. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three men are doing karate. </seg>
<seg id="49"> The lady typed on the stenograph. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five kittens are eating food. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man speeding on a bike on a muddy road suddenly comes to a halt. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog opens a small can of food with its mouth. </seg>
<seg id="54"> The man is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="55"> The man is talking. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A large inflatable ball knocks over a potato propped vertically on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A kid is pointing out days on a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are talking. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men each flip a huge tire down the pavement. </seg>
<seg id="60"> A woman is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="61"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> An army sergeant is walking and talking to a line of soldiers standing next to their beds in their camp room. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a mobile phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> Men do flips from diving boards into a pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man strums a violin on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating a piece of chicken. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is pouring water out of a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="68"> The boy is playing in the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat licks milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man sits on a bridge railing. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman places two eggs into a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="73"> An animal is washed. </seg>
<seg id="74"> The man came out from the mud. </seg>
<seg id="75"> An artist drew a picture. </seg>
<seg id="76"> The panda bear lay on the logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> The little girl is watering the plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man menaces a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is chopping an onion and frozen green beans. </seg>
<seg id="80"> Two people are walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> The man hit the other man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="82"> The woman is slicing tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> The baby rhino is following her mom. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A large inflatable ball knocks over a potato propped vertically on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A singer sings. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three teenage girls dance in a room. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey pratices martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man plays the drum. </seg>
<seg id="89"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Bread is sliced. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> The little boy is using the telephone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat plays with a small bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> The dog wagged his tail on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> person preparing something </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man is adding tomato sauce to a pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man drizzles olive oil to cover the bottom of a pan placed on the gas stove. </seg>
<seg id="98"> The lady cracked the eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> Two people are walking through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man lights a pack of matches. </seg>
<seg id="101"> The man is carrying a branch of leaves. </seg>
<seg id="102"> The man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman pours oil in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> The comedian pulled eggs out of his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> The woman is sewing. </seg>
<seg id="106"> Standing on the field, a coach is guiding another man on how to bat the right way in cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> Someone is burning two cameras. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A yo9ung man is playing the cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> The lady scrubbed the cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and a woman run toward the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a mobile phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> The lady floured the meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is cracking open eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> A singer dances on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> The woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man cuts some meat. </seg>
<seg id="118"> The man is shooting a gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A small critter is chewing on a persons finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> The man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A woman standing uses a toothbrush to scrub off the mud from the sole of her left foot. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A weightlifter is lifting weight. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three men are doing karate. </seg>
<seg id="124"> The horse stood up. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five kittens are eating food. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A rambunctious dog knocks over a child. </seg>
<seg id="127"> The lady typed on the stenograph. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A white cat perched on a small wooden cabinet is looking outside the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> A woman dumps vegetables into boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> An old woman is peeling a large raw potato using a vegetable peeler. </seg>
<seg id="131"> The man broke the chair. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> Paper is being ripped in half. </seg>
<seg id="134"> The man drilled a hole into the piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man picked a king out of a deck of cards. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A woman plays the clarinet. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A girl plays an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person stirs some vegetables and sauce. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man shoots a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A woman falls off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> The men are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman is cracking eggs. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Several kids are doing tricks on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing a violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A man is folding over a tortilla in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy train strikes a toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> The horse and rider trotted by the fence. </seg>
<seg id="148"> The dog is jumping on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman dices a boiled octopus into 1/2 inch pieces using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="150"> The lady picked up the watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A man is mixing ingredients in a large mixing bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> The man drilled a hole into the piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> The man drilled a hole into the piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A person is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> The girl opened a soda can and started drinking. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A group of babies are  playing. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A chef cleans the side of a bowl of vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="158"> A person jumps off a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A skateboarder does tricks on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="160"> The band performed on stage. </seg>
<seg id="161"> Many people dance in front of a house. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A person is chopping up potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is cutting broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> The woman is whisking the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> The cook is slicing a green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> The man is crying. </seg>
<seg id="167"> The baby crawled through the doorway. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A cat pulls a plastic drawer out. </seg>
<seg id="169"> The girl applied face makeup to a man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> The rabbit was being petted on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man plays a flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> The man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="173"> The man enjoyed playing his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people exercise. </seg>
<seg id="175"> The girl ate a tiny cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man rides a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat plays with a small bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A skateboarder does tricks on a half-pipe. </seg>
<seg id="179"> The turtle is walking under water. </seg>
<seg id="180"> An animal walks on its hind legs through a swampy area. </seg>
<seg id="181"> The cat is swinging from the ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A group of men are sawing, then carrying trees. </seg>
<seg id="183"> The cook is spreading the dough. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Three men are jumping off a wall. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger, whose back alone is visible, is digging a hole in the ground. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is using a microwave. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A baby kitten is eating milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A car drives down the road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is attacking a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> The man is exercising. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A man lifts weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> The man caught a fish. </seg>
<seg id="194"> The animal is being scratched under the arms. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boy attempts to perform a trick with a soccer ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is pouring water out of a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="197"> The man drilled a hole into the piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holding a very small monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman is slicing a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> The man is drawing on the board. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog wants to jump in the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> The girl ate a tiny cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> The man used a sword to slice a boot. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man is adding cheese to a pizza crust. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A woman plays a string instrument. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Someone stirred the noodles into the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog is barking and runs around a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman cuts up a cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A woman is brushing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman trims hedges. </seg>
<seg id="212"> The cat played the piano with his paw. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is tapping her fingernails on the counter. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A potato is being cut into pieces. </seg>
<seg id="215"> The man bowed down in the middle of the street. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman sliced a piece of meat into three pieces. </seg>
<seg id="217"> The blue soccer team scored a goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man brushes a cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Women swimmers are diving in from the starting platform. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A cat pulls a plastic drawer out. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man walks down a city sidewalk. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman places a coated pork slab into hot oil and deep fries it till golden brown. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is signing. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Someone stirred the noodles into the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women are singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is pouring things into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> A person is playing a key-board. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A boy and a girl are riding in a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> The baby crawled through the doorway. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A girl knits. </seg>
<seg id="232"> An army sergeant is walking and talking to a line of soldiers standing next to their beds in their camp room. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person holds a porcupine. </seg>
<seg id="234"> The rabbit was being petted on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="235"> The drummer played his drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A guy is playing an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman is playing violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog opens a small can of food with its mouth. </seg>
<seg id="240"> The man chopped through the hanging rope with a large sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> The little girl is putting her hair into a pony tail. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is trying to reel in a fish. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman places a coated pork slab into hot oil and deep fries it till golden brown. </seg>
<seg id="244"> The little girl is putting her hair into a pony tail. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman puts various ingredients into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man tries to feed a mouse to a snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref14">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> The horse and rider ran down the path. </seg>
<seg id="2"> The man tried a bite of his cooking. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is thinking about something. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man sitting on steps with a guitar is petting some dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A pet grey cat sitting next to a carton box kept open from the top, jumps high and leaps into the box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> The man is feeding a mouse to the snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> The lady peeled the skin off the fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two men are playing table tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> The stars danced while the other dancers stood still. </seg>
<seg id="10"> Someone is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> The woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is rowing a canoe. </seg>
<seg id="13"> The machine is sharpening a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> The woman is riding an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> A man seated is playing the guitar and humming a tune. </seg>
<seg id="16"> The woman put an egg in the mixer. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> something weird a Double for venus is good </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog picks up a small can it found on the floor and carries it in it's mouth. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog sat at the counter of a store. </seg>
<seg id="21"> one man doing skipping excerise infront of his home </seg>
<seg id="22"> A small boy seated on the bed is holding a guitar and humming a tune. </seg>
<seg id="23"> The woman came down on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A toddler sitting on the couch coos and giggles. </seg>
<seg id="25"> The lady cut flowers off the bush. </seg>
<seg id="26"> The chef sliced the onion. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman plays a violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> The man and woman are communicating with the webcam. </seg>
<seg id="29"> The man is hiking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="30"> The man turned the quesadilla in half in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="31"> A man and woman walk down a field. </seg>
<seg id="32"> Two men are practicing football. </seg>
<seg id="33"> The man played the sax. </seg>
<seg id="34"> the man shimmied up the rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> The person is scrubbing the bottom of his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> The lady peeled the potatoe skin. </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man speaks into a bunch of microphones. </seg>
<seg id="38"> The man talked on the telephone in the pizza kitchen. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A man is singing and playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is beating eggs in a bowl with chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="41"> The man is playing keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing the chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A loris seated on a bed is eating a piece of mango held in its fore limbs. </seg>
<seg id="44"> An officer is talking to recruits. </seg>
<seg id="45"> Two dogs are lying in a bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two martial artists fight it out. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A man showed a sunflower head. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three men are practicing karate moves in a field. </seg>
<seg id="49"> The man is using a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man plays a piano. </seg>
<seg id="51"> The kittens are eating. </seg>
<seg id="52"> The man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog picks up a small can it found on the floor and carries it in it's mouth. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man dances. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man talks. </seg>
<seg id="56"> A man is colliding a potato with a green ball. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A man is looking at numbers on a chart. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two men are talking. </seg>
<seg id="59"> The men are moving the huge tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The girl danced in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> The man sang and played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> An officer is talking to recruits. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man talks on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> The boy did backward sommersaults from the diving board into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> Holding a fiddle in his right hand, a man is playing the violin with his fingers instead. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman wearing a red dress is eating a chicken lollipop standing in a room as she thinks something. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man shakes a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A boy plays in the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A white cat is licking and drinking milk kept on a plate. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man plays the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> The man climbed over the short wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> A woman turns two eggs in boiling water, removes them after some time and places them in ice cold water. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A person cleans a porcupine. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man is rising from the water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> Someone is drawing a face on a piece of paper when suddenly the scene shifts to two men painting a room. </seg>
<seg id="76"> The cut animal is sleeping </seg>
<seg id="77"> a litlegirl is watering the plants </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man talks to a woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is chopping an onion. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and woman are walking through a field. </seg>
<seg id="81"> The man spanked the other man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman cuts tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> Two rhinos walk around a pen. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A man is colliding a potato with a green ball. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The man sang on stage into the microphone. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three teenage girls danced in the room. </seg>
<seg id="87"> Th chimpanzee did martial arts kicks with a man. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A man is singing and playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is slicing a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> The panda bears piled on top of each other. </seg>
<seg id="92"> A kid plays with a toy phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is grabbing, rubbing, and licking a vial in someones hand. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two dogs are lying in a bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A lady is removing the outer part of a papaya to make it smooth. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man empties a can of crushed tomatoes into a pan containing cooked and seasoned sausages. </seg>
<seg id="97"> The lady poured oil in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> The woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and woman are walking through a field. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man lit a book of matches on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is dragging a tree. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A frog crawls along a man's arm. </seg>
<seg id="103"> The woman is pouring oil into the pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> The comedian pulled eggs out of his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A person sews a quilt. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The man coached the boy with his swing. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A person uses a blowtorch on two cameras. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A young man is playing a cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> there is a cleaning the items </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman is slicing tomatoes. </seg>
<seg id="111"> The couple ran hand in hand to the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man talks on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> The woman is breading the pork chop. </seg>
<seg id="114"> The man broke an egg into the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> Lionel Richie is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is slicing open a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A gun fires a blast. </seg>
<seg id="119"> The animal bit the person's finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> The man rode a black horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> The person is scrubbing the bottom of his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> The man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three men are practicing karate moves in a field. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse gets off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> The kittens are eating. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A white dog runs past and pushes a small boy running on a water logged garden, not once but twice! </seg>
<seg id="127"> The man is using a stenography machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> The cat is looking out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> Ocra is boiling in a pot of water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> An old woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is breaking boards with his hand using a karate chop. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing the chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> Paper is being torn. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="135"> The man is doing a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> A young girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A woman is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> Someone stirred the ot of chili. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man shot his rifle at a target. </seg>
<seg id="140"> A woman falls off of a horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> The people danced in front of the airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> A woman is pouring eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Several kids jump up and down on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is playing the violin on top of a house. </seg>
<seg id="145"> The man turned the quesadilla in half in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A toy trolley hits a car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> The woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog bounces on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> The lady cut the octopus tentacle into small pieces. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman is holding a watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> Someone is mixing salad in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A singer sings. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman opens and drinks from a can of soft drink. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A little girl playing outside </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is wiping the rim of a bowl clean. </seg>
<seg id="158"> Someone dived off a cliff into the water far below. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A skateboarder is performing a trick in a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="160"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="161"> The kids danced on the patio. </seg>
<seg id="162"> A person is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is cutting up a stalk of broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is beating eggs in a bowl with chopsticks. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A Man is slicing some Capcicum. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man does hand movements to illustrate something to another man. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby happily crawls through a doorway. </seg>
<seg id="168"> A grey cat opens a cabinet draw with his left fore paw and thereafter enters the draw. </seg>
<seg id="169"> The woman is putting makeup on the man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> The person is tickling the rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man plays the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man rides a bike down a road. </seg>
<seg id="173"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people exercised to a video. </seg>
<seg id="175"> The woman is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man rides a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is grabbing, rubbing, and licking a vial in someones hand. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A skateboarder is performing a trick in a halfpipe. </seg>
<seg id="179"> Fish swim away from a turtle. </seg>
<seg id="180"> The monkey is wading through the water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat swing on a fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> The men sawed the tree trunk together. </seg>
<seg id="183"> person is preparing something </seg>
<seg id="184"> The men are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="185"> An animal digs a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> pressing keys of the oven </seg>
<seg id="187"> The kitten lapped the milk in the saucer. </seg>
<seg id="188"> A pickup truck is coming down a road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> A man seated is playing the guitar and humming a tune. </seg>
<seg id="190"> The cat rolled around on the ground with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man lifts weights. </seg>
<seg id="192"> The man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man reels in a fish. </seg>
<seg id="194"> Someone is scratching a lemur under the armpits. </seg>
<seg id="195"> A couple of guys are individually trying to keep a ball in the air with their feet. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man shakes a plastic container. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man is drilling a hole in a board. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is holing a small monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman cuts a small thin round peel from a yuzu fruit using a large knife. </seg>
<seg id="200"> a man drawing enclined plane on a white board </seg>
<seg id="201"> The dog could not get its ball out of the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> The woman is eating a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man is cutting a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man sprinkles cheese on top of a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A young lady is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> The woman is boiling pasta. </seg>
<seg id="207"> The dog ran behind a tree to hide. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is interested in the reflected light. </seg>
<seg id="209"> The woman is slicing eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A girl is curling her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> The lady cut flowers off the bush. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat is playing the piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> The girl drummed her fingers on the tabletop. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A potato is cut into half lengthwise and then sliced into a quarter. </seg>
<seg id="215"> The man knelt down the street. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman slices a piece of cooked pork meat into three portions using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="217"> The blue uniformed soccer team scored a goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> The man brushed the white cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> Many swimmers start a swimming race. </seg>
<seg id="220"> A grey cat opens a cabinet draw with his left fore paw and thereafter enters the draw. </seg>
<seg id="221"> The boy sang as he walked down the street. </seg>
<seg id="222"> The lady fried the breaded meat in hot oil. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A child speaks with sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> The woman is boiling pasta. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women are singing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> any one is making dish </seg>
<seg id="227"> A person is playing double keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two people talk in a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> A man seated is playing the guitar and humming a tune. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby happily crawls through a doorway. </seg>
<seg id="231"> The girl sat on the couch to crochet. </seg>
<seg id="232"> An officer is talking to recruits. </seg>
<seg id="233"> Someone tried to give the hedgehog a bath in the sink. </seg>
<seg id="234"> The person is tickling the rabbit. </seg>
<seg id="235"> The man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is singing and dancing while standing near a fire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a large flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman plays a violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog picks up a small can it found on the floor and carries it in it's mouth. </seg>
<seg id="240"> the men is beeting the tread </seg>
<seg id="241"> The little girl wrung out her wet hair and used a brush. </seg>
<seg id="242"> The man fished with a rod. </seg>
<seg id="243"> The lady fried the breaded meat in hot oil. </seg>
<seg id="244"> The little girl wrung out her wet hair and used a brush. </seg>
<seg id="245"> A woman seasons a vegetable mixture. </seg>
<seg id="246"> The man is feeding a mouse to the snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref15">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A  man is riding horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> a man is eating </seg>
<seg id="3"> The man was perplexed. </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man with a guitar is petting two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> The cat circled the box and then jumped inside. </seg>
<seg id="6"> The man is trying to feed the snake with a mouse. </seg>
<seg id="7"> the dog is cooking the something </seg>
<seg id="8"> The ladies played a game of ping pong. </seg>
<seg id="9"> There are about eight couples ball room dancing. </seg>
<seg id="10"> The boy folded the yellow piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> Two people are riding horses on a track. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man rowed a boat in the river. </seg>
<seg id="13"> The machine shaved the end of the pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding an elephant and people are bowing to her. </seg>
<seg id="15"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A girl break an egg and she put in the machine </seg>
<seg id="17"> Someone rode a horse in the ring. </seg>
<seg id="18"> Two women measure their ankles. </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog retrieves a can of dog food and tries to open it. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog tends a bookshop. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is doing  skipping excercise </seg>
<seg id="22"> A young boy is singing while playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A women climbs down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A young child is laughing while sitting on a couch. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A girl is cutting flower </seg>
<seg id="26"> The man is slicing onions. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A woman plays the violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A boy chats on webcam. </seg>
<seg id="29"> a man is waling with his laugage. </seg>
<seg id="30"> The man is cooking a crepe. </seg>
<seg id="31"> Couples enjoy happy times. </seg>
<seg id="32"> Two men are talking on a football field. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing the saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> The man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A woman is scrubbing the sole of her foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> the person is doing the cooking </seg>
<seg id="37"> A man speaks into several microphones. </seg>
<seg id="38"> The man is talking on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> The man strummed on his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman beats two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A guy playing the kids bass tuto. </seg>
<seg id="42"> The man erased what the other man had on the board. </seg>
<seg id="43"> The animal ate some fruit in his paws. </seg>
<seg id="44"> The drill sargent is talking to his men. </seg>
<seg id="45"> Two dogs are lying in a bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> The man beat the other man with a stick. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Someone is holding sunflowers. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three men are practicing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person types on a stenotype machine. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man plays an entire song on the piano. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five kittens are eating from dishes. </seg>
<seg id="52"> The man rode his motorcycle dow the dirt road. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog retrieves a can of dog food and tries to open it. </seg>
<seg id="54"> The man did a funny dance for the girl. </seg>
<seg id="55"> The man gave a speech in front of some bookshelves. </seg>
<seg id="56"> The ball bumped into the potato. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A school boy is looking at the calender. </seg>
<seg id="58"> Two people talk to each other. </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two men compete in a tire rolling race. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The lady danced in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> The singer also played a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The drill sargent is talking to his men. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a telephone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> The man dove off the board into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> Someone is playing an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="66"> The lady sat and ate a drumstick. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is draining pasta. </seg>
<seg id="68"> The boy slapped the mud on himself. </seg>
<seg id="69"> The cat is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man strummed a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> there is a two people </seg>
<seg id="72"> The lady boiled two eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> Someone tried to give the hedgehog a bath. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A person rises out of the water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> Someone is drawing a picture. </seg>
<seg id="76"> the animal is playing </seg>
<seg id="77"> A SMALL GIRL WATERING PLANTS WITH A SPRAY </seg>
<seg id="78"> A man yells at a women. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is chopping onions and chillies. </seg>
<seg id="80"> The couple walked arm in arm down the path. </seg>
<seg id="81"> Using a plastic sword, a teenager whacks the bottom of a man standing hunched in front of him. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is slicing through a slab of tofu. </seg>
<seg id="83"> The baby rhino followed his mother. </seg>
<seg id="84"> The ball bumped into the potato. </seg>
<seg id="85"> the boy is a sing a song </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="87"> the boy is figthing the monkey </seg>
<seg id="88"> A man plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> The man strummed on his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> Someone sliced a loaf of bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> The baby pandas are playing. </seg>
<seg id="92"> The little boy played with his toy telephone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> The cat rubbed his head against the lady's hand and licked his medicine. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two dogs are lying in a bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A man smoothly slicing the papaya to make juice. </seg>
<seg id="96"> The man added tomatoe sauce to the sausages in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> The man is pouring oil into the pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman is cracking three eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="99"> The couple walked arm in arm down the path. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A man sets a matchbook on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A person moves a fallen tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="102"> The man held a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman puts some cooking oil in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> The man is removing eggs from the fly of his pants. </seg>
<seg id="105"> The lady sewed the fabric together. </seg>
<seg id="106"> The man is teaching the boy how to play cricket. </seg>
<seg id="107"> Someone is setting two cameras on fire with a spray. </seg>
<seg id="108"> A young man plays a cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A man is cleaning some fruit </seg>
<seg id="110"> A woman slices a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> the people are running </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a telephone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A woman glazes some meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> The man is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> Lionel Richie is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> The lady cracked an egg into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> The man split open the fish with a knife. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A person shoots a gun in slow motion. </seg>
<seg id="119"> The animal is biting the man's finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> The man rode the black horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A woman is scrubbing the sole of her foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> The man picked up the heavy barbells. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three men are practicing martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse gets back up on his feet. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five kittens are eating from dishes. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A young boy is running through an area filled with water when a dog runs past and knocks the boy down. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A person types on a stenotype machine. </seg>
<seg id="128"> The cat looked out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> Someone is boiling okra in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="130"> The lady is peeling a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A martial artist breaks a wooden table. </seg>
<seg id="132"> The man erased what the other man had on the board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> Someone is shown tearing off a rectangular piece of paper from a paper triangle. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man drills a hole in some wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man performs a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> Someone is playing an instrument. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A young girl is playing a flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> there is a preparing the item </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man standing in the woods fires a shot with his rifle at a far off target. </seg>
<seg id="140"> Someone fell off a horse. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Actors dancing and singing in the movie. </seg>
<seg id="142"> The lady broke raw eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> Some children are jumping on Trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> The man played the violin on the rooftop. </seg>
<seg id="145"> The man is cooking a crepe. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A train coming around a bend hits a stationary car on the track. </seg>
<seg id="147"> Two people are riding horses on a track. </seg>
<seg id="148"> The dog played on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> The woman is cutting cooked octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> a picking up a water vase </seg>
<seg id="151"> The man stirred the vegetables in the big bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man drills a hole in some wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A man drills a hole in some wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> The man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A woman drinks from a soda can. </seg>
<seg id="156"> A little girl rides her scooter up the driveway. </seg>
<seg id="157"> The chef wiped the edge of the soup bowl. </seg>
<seg id="158"> Someone dived off a cliff into water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> A skater skates on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="160"> The men performed on stage. </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing on the balcony. </seg>
<seg id="162"> Someone is cutting potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> A woman is slicing cauliflower. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman beats two eggs in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="165"> the person is cutting the capsicum </seg>
<seg id="166"> The man cried on the other man's shoulder. </seg>
<seg id="167"> The baby is laughing and crawling. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The cat opened a drawer and climbed inside. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is applying makeup to a mans face. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A finger rubs an animal. </seg>
<seg id="171"> A man plays the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> The man rode his motorcycle to the woman. </seg>
<seg id="173"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people jog in place. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl is eating a mini cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> A man rode a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> The cat rubbed his head against the lady's hand and licked his medicine. </seg>
<seg id="178"> A skater skates on a half pipe. </seg>
<seg id="179"> The turtle swam after the fish. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is waddling in water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat swings around on a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> the boys doing the dancing </seg>
<seg id="183"> A guy is cooking calzone recipe </seg>
<seg id="184"> Three men are jumping and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="185"> The badger dug a hole in the ground. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A guy is cooking prime rib recipe for his father. </seg>
<seg id="187"> The kitten is drinking milk. </seg>
<seg id="188"> The truck drove past a car on the road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> The cat is playing with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> The man lifted barbells. </seg>
<seg id="192"> The man lifted barbells in each of his hands. </seg>
<seg id="193"> The man dropped the fish he caught back into the water. </seg>
<seg id="194"> A person plays with a lemur. </seg>
<seg id="195"> The man did tricks with the soccer ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is draining pasta. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man drills a hole in some wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man is showing the smallest monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> The lady cut a pince of lemon rind. </seg>
<seg id="200"> a man is teaching on blackboard </seg>
<seg id="201"> The dog could not reach his ball in the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl is eating a mini cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man cuts a boot with a huge knife. </seg>
<seg id="204"> The man spread cheese on the pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> A young woman is playing a fiddle. </seg>
<seg id="206"> The lady stirred the noodles in the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="207"> The dog ran away and hid behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> The cat tried to get the hanging string. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman cuts up vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="210"> A girl brushed curls into her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> A girl is cutting flower </seg>
<seg id="212"> a cat is playing a guitar </seg>
<seg id="213"> A girl sits in a chair with her hand over a white piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="214"> The man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> A guy is praying in  middle of the road. </seg>
<seg id="216"> A woman slices pork meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> The players made a soccer goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> a men is cleaning  the kitten </seg>
<seg id="219"> Women begin a swim race. </seg>
<seg id="220"> The cat opened a drawer and climbed inside. </seg>
<seg id="221"> The man is singing and walking. </seg>
<seg id="222"> The woman is dropping the breaded pork chop into the hot oil. </seg>
<seg id="223"> The girl did sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> The lady stirred the noodles in the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women in uniform are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="226"> the women is cooking </seg>
<seg id="227"> An individual plays a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A boy is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> The baby is laughing and crawling. </seg>
<seg id="231"> she is doing the nail polish to the nailes </seg>
<seg id="232"> The drill sargent is talking to his men. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A man is holding up a small hedgehog in one hand. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A finger rubs an animal. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A boy plays the drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> A woman is singing and dancing. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man is playing a mega bass flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A woman plays the violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog retrieves a can of dog food and tries to open it. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man cut a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> young girl grooming her hair in front of bathroom mirror </seg>
<seg id="242"> The man is fishing. </seg>
<seg id="243"> The woman is dropping the breaded pork chop into the hot oil. </seg>
<seg id="244"> young girl grooming her hair in front of bathroom mirror </seg>
<seg id="245"> The lady added oil and seasoning to the vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="246"> The man is trying to feed the snake with a mouse. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref16">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> a girl id riding horse. </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is eating. </seg>
<seg id="3"> A MAN IS THINKING SOMETHING. </seg>
<seg id="4"> The man held his guitar and pet the two dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> The cat jumped into the box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> The man teased a snake with a live mouse. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A women is cleaning the fish </seg>
<seg id="8"> The men are in a table tennis match. </seg>
<seg id="9"> Two people dance together. </seg>
<seg id="10"> The man is folding paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is booting </seg>
<seg id="13"> A huge pencil sharpener is placed in the room. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman rides an elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A lady break a egg and put in the machine. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is riding in a horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> a lady is giving the thread to the other lady. </seg>
<seg id="19"> the dog chewed on the ball. </seg>
<seg id="20"> A dog tends a store checkout. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is doing skipping excercise. </seg>
<seg id="22"> A young boy sings and plays a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A woman climbs down a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> A young child is sitting on a sofa laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> a girl is laughing </seg>
<seg id="26"> A chef demonstrates cutting onions. </seg>
<seg id="27"> The lady played her violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> The man talked to the girl on his computer. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A guy is wearing the band around his wrist. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person folds over a soft taco. </seg>
<seg id="31"> The couple strolled down the path. </seg>
<seg id="32"> Two men talk on a football field. </seg>
<seg id="33"> the person is playing music </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man is climbing a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> A person brushes his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> An old woman is peeling potato. </seg>
<seg id="37"> The man gave his report to the reporters </seg>
<seg id="38"> A man talks on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A guy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman mixes a mixture. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A MAN IS PLAYING KEYBOARD. </seg>
<seg id="42"> The man is erasing the chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="43"> The animal with the big eyes is eating. </seg>
<seg id="44"> The military officer barked at the recruits. </seg>
<seg id="45"> Two dogs are lying on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> the person is fighting </seg>
<seg id="47"> The man exhibited a sunflower head. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Three men practice martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="49"> the man used a stenograph. </seg>
<seg id="50"> A man plays the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five kittens eat. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A guy is sitting in the road. </seg>
<seg id="53"> the dog chewed on the ball. </seg>
<seg id="54"> the boy and girl is dancing </seg>
<seg id="55"> A gentleman giving a lecture with background of books on shelf. </seg>
<seg id="56"> The green ball knocked down the potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="57"> A schoolboy is watching a calendar and counting the number of holidays for a particular month. </seg>
<seg id="58"> a clipping from the movie anbae shivam starring kamal hassan and madhavan </seg>
<seg id="59"> Two people flipped tractor tires in a race. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The woman is dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Two men are playing in a musical band. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The military officer barked at the recruits. </seg>
<seg id="63"> The man talked on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> swimming in the liver pool </seg>
<seg id="65"> The man is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="66"> The woman is eating. </seg>
<seg id="67"> The man shook the rest of the marinade into the sink! </seg>
<seg id="68"> a kid showing his anger in dirty muddy water </seg>
<seg id="69"> The cat is lapping milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="70"> The man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man climbs on a wall. </seg>
<seg id="72"> The lady is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> the person is doing the something </seg>
<seg id="74"> The man emerged from the muddy water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> Someone is drawing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A dog is trying to sleep on a log </seg>
<seg id="77"> A child is giving water to plant. </seg>
<seg id="78"> The man appealed to the woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is chopping onions. </seg>
<seg id="80"> The man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="81"> the boy is beating the another person </seg>
<seg id="82"> The lady sliced the cheese. </seg>
<seg id="83"> Baby Rhino playing </seg>
<seg id="84"> The green ball knocked down the potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A man is telling something </seg>
<seg id="86"> three teenage girls dancing on music in their home </seg>
<seg id="87"> a monkey is hitting the man. </seg>
<seg id="88"> A musician plays a drum kit. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A guy is playing a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A guy is cutting the bread. </seg>
<seg id="91"> Two pandas play. </seg>
<seg id="92"> a  kid playing with a toy phone </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is rubbing its face on someones hand. </seg>
<seg id="94"> Two dogs are lying on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> a woman is cutting a papaya </seg>
<seg id="96"> The man is pouring tomato sauce into the pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A man is pouring olive oil into a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="98"> A woman breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="99"> The man and woman are walking. </seg>
<seg id="100"> The man is staring at a burning matchbook. </seg>
<seg id="101"> The man moved a big tree branch away. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man holds a frog in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman pours a liquid into a skillet. </seg>
<seg id="104"> Steve Martin is performing a comedy routine. </seg>
<seg id="105"> A Woman is stitching a cloth. </seg>
<seg id="106"> A trainer is showing a cricket batter the correct batting stance. </seg>
<seg id="107"> there is a cameras </seg>
<seg id="108"> The boy swayed to the music as he played his cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> a lady is washing the cucumber. </seg>
<seg id="110"> Someone is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and a woman are running together towards the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="112"> The man talked on the phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> The lady floured the meat. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> Lionel Ritchie dances while standing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> A woman is cracking an egg. </seg>
<seg id="117"> the man is cutting fish </seg>
<seg id="118"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="119"> A slow lori plays with a person's hand. </seg>
<seg id="120"> A guy is riding on horse in the ground. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A person brushes his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> The weight lifter lifted a heavy weight. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Three men practice martial arts. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse gets up off the ground. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five kittens eat. </seg>
<seg id="126"> The dog is bumping to the boy. </seg>
<seg id="127"> the man used a stenograph. </seg>
<seg id="128"> The cat looked out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> The lady put the bean pods in the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> The lady peeled a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="131"> The man karate chopped through blocks of wood. </seg>
<seg id="132"> The man is erasing the chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> The man is tearing paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A man drills a hole into a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man picked a card in a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> The girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> A young woman is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> Someone is stirring a pot of chilli. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man took aim and fired at a target. </seg>
<seg id="140"> The horse and his rider fell down. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men are dancing in unison. </seg>
<seg id="142"> The lady cracked the eggs and stirred them. </seg>
<seg id="143"> The boys did tricks on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> The man is on the roof playing a violin. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A person folds over a soft taco. </seg>
<seg id="146"> A train crashes into a car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman cuts up some worms. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A women in the garden </seg>
<seg id="151"> the person is cutting the tamato </seg>
<seg id="152"> A man drills a hole into a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A man drills a hole into a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> The man sang into the microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> The lady popped open a can of soda and drank. </seg>
<seg id="156"> kids playing in they ground </seg>
<seg id="157"> there is preparing item </seg>
<seg id="158"> Someone dives into the water from a tall cliff. </seg>
<seg id="159"> The man is riding a skateboard and doing tricks. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Two men are singing and playing guitars. </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="162"> Someone is cutting potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="163"> Broccoli is being chopped. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman mixes a mixture. </seg>
<seg id="165"> Woman makes a chicken dish </seg>
<seg id="166"> Men are deeply breathing. </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby crawls on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The cat opened and climbed into the drawer. </seg>
<seg id="169"> The lady is putting on makeup on the man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A bunny struggles to get away. </seg>
<seg id="171"> The man is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> the boy and girl is going on the bike </seg>
<seg id="173"> A Man Playing Guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three people march in place. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A girl eats a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> The man is riding a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is rubbing its face on someones hand. </seg>
<seg id="178"> The man is riding a skateboard and doing tricks. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is walking in the ocean. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey is walking through the water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> The cat was swung around the room by the fan pull. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A man is saw the wood </seg>
<seg id="183"> A man is unrolling some rolled up dough. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Two people jump against a vending machine. </seg>
<seg id="185"> The badger dug a hole in the ground. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man is using a microwave oven. </seg>
<seg id="187"> A kitten drinks water. </seg>
<seg id="188"> the man is drive the car on the road and seeing the place </seg>
<seg id="189"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat tries to eat a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> the man is ding excirse </seg>
<seg id="192"> The man lifted small barbells in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man and woman are fishing. </seg>
<seg id="194"> The person scratched the monkey's arm pits! </seg>
<seg id="195"> the men is playing football </seg>
<seg id="196"> The man shook the rest of the marinade into the sink! </seg>
<seg id="197"> A man drills a hole into a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man shows off a small monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman, in a kitchen, peels a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> the computer screen correcting the lines straightly </seg>
<seg id="201"> The dog is trying to jump into the water. </seg>
<seg id="202"> A girl eats a cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> The man sliced through the toe of a boot with a big sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> The cook is spreading cheese on the pizza dough. </seg>
<seg id="205"> The girl played her violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> Learn to make Yakibuta Ramen a Japanese noodle </seg>
<seg id="207"> A dog runs away and peers out from behind a tree. </seg>
<seg id="208"> the dog is playing the box </seg>
<seg id="209"> The lady sliced the eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210">       </seg>
<seg id="211"> a girl is laughing </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat plays the keys on a piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> The woman is tapping her fingers on the table. </seg>
<seg id="214"> cutting a potatoe into first half and then again in second half </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man is bowing before the traffic. </seg>
<seg id="216"> The lady sliced a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> Two teams are playing football as a member of one team kicks a goal. </seg>
<seg id="218"> Someone is brushing their cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> The swimmers dove into the water for a race. </seg>
<seg id="220"> The cat opened and climbed into the drawer. </seg>
<seg id="221"> The man is walking. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman puts some meat in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="223"> The girl is using sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> Learn to make Yakibuta Ramen a Japanese noodle </seg>
<seg id="225"> Two women sing and dance. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A woman is mixing ingredients together in a small bowl. </seg>
<seg id="227"> Someone is playing a organ. </seg>
<seg id="228"> The boy laughed with his friend as he drove the car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> The man is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby crawls on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> a woman's are preparing with woolen </seg>
<seg id="232"> The military officer barked at the recruits. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A person is holding a hedgehog. </seg>
<seg id="234"> A bunny struggles to get away. </seg>
<seg id="235"> The man played his drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> The girl danced in front of the bonfire. </seg>
<seg id="237"> The man played a long wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> The lady played her violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> the dog chewed on the ball. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A little girl fixing her hair in front of the bathroom mirror. </seg>
<seg id="242"> The man was fishig with a pole. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman puts some meat in a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A little girl fixing her hair in front of the bathroom mirror. </seg>
<seg id="245"> The lady poured ingredients into the vegetable mixture. </seg>
<seg id="246"> The man teased a snake with a live mouse. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref17">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> a girl is riding horse </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is eating something </seg>
<seg id="3"> A man is making a funny face. </seg>
<seg id="4"> The man is petting the dogs. </seg>
<seg id="5"> The cat was curious about the box and jumped inside. </seg>
<seg id="6"> The man tried to feed a live mouse to a snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is pulling apart cooked fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two people play a ping-pong match. </seg>
<seg id="9"> Several people sing and dance </seg>
<seg id="10"> A guy is folding a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="11"> The lady is riding on the horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is doing boating </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine cutting iron </seg>
<seg id="14"> The girl waved on top of the elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A girl is riding in the horse. </seg>
<seg id="18"> A woman is measuring another woman's ankle. </seg>
<seg id="19"> The dog is opening a can so he can eat. </seg>
<seg id="20"> The dog is standing at the counter. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A man is standing in front of the house. </seg>
<seg id="22"> The boy is singing and playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> The lady came down from the tree on a vine. </seg>
<seg id="24"> The baby is laughing. </seg>
<seg id="25"> a woman cutting flowers outside </seg>
<seg id="26"> A chef showing how to cut an onion the proper way. </seg>
<seg id="27"> The woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> the man is talking with the girl and dancing </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man hiking in the woods and camping with others shows the Fitzen Wrist Armor Option. </seg>
<seg id="30"> the man folded the quesadilla over in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="31"> The man and woman strolled down the path. </seg>
<seg id="32"> Two men talk on a football field. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing some music instrument </seg>
<seg id="34"> A man climbs a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> The girl scrubbed the bottom of her feet with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is removing outer cover of a potato  with knife. </seg>
<seg id="37"> The man is talking to the media. </seg>
<seg id="38"> The man talked on the phone in the pizza kitchen. </seg>
<seg id="39"> A guy is playing his guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="40"> The lady scrambled the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A man is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A slow lori eats. </seg>
<seg id="44"> The seargeant inspected the recruits bunks. </seg>
<seg id="45"> The dog is lying down on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="47"> The man is brushing dry sunflowers. </seg>
<seg id="48"> Two boys are fighting one. </seg>
<seg id="49"> the person is tyiping </seg>
<seg id="50"> A person is playing a piano. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Five little kittens are eating from five little dishes. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> The dog is opening a can so he can eat. </seg>
<seg id="54"> This film is badri </seg>
<seg id="55"> He is speaking </seg>
<seg id="56"> The green ball knocked the standing potatoe over. </seg>
<seg id="57"> The boy is reading a calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man having scars in his face. </seg>
<seg id="59"> the man is lifting the weight. </seg>
<seg id="60"> one girl is dancing </seg>
<seg id="61"> A man is on a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="62"> The seargeant inspected the recruits bunks. </seg>
<seg id="63"> the men is speaking to phone </seg>
<seg id="64"> one person jumping into swimming pool </seg>
<seg id="65"> The man played a ukelele on stage. </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman is eating a chicken leg. </seg>
<seg id="67"> the person is cooking the something </seg>
<seg id="68"> A BOY AND GIRL ARE PLAYING DIRTY WATER. </seg>
<seg id="69"> The cat lapped milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="70"> The man picked at his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A person walking their </seg>
<seg id="72"> The layd put two eggs into the water to boil. </seg>
<seg id="73"> woman giving abath to mouse </seg>
<seg id="74"> the person is trying the out side </seg>
<seg id="75"> The man drew a picture. </seg>
<seg id="76"> the bear is enjoying itself and take rest </seg>
<seg id="77"> A cute little girl is watering the plants. </seg>
<seg id="78"> The man is talking to the woman. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is chopping up a white onion and another vegetable which is green. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A guy hits a man. </seg>
<seg id="82"> the person is cutting the something </seg>
<seg id="83"> Two rhino's are walking around. </seg>
<seg id="84"> The green ball knocked the standing potatoe over. </seg>
<seg id="85"> The man is singing. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Girls are Dancing. </seg>
<seg id="87"> THE MONKEY IS PRACTICE THE BOXING. </seg>
<seg id="88"> The drummer is playing his drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A guy is playing his guitar and singing. </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is cutting a bread using a knife. </seg>
<seg id="91"> The panda bears piled on top of each other. </seg>
<seg id="92"> a boy can be take this phone </seg>
<seg id="93"> the cat is playing </seg>
<seg id="94"> The dog is lying down on the bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> well a clip of peeling a papaya and making it smooth. </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man is pouring a can of tomato sauce into a saucepan. </seg>
<seg id="97"> A person pours cooking oil into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> The lady cracked the egs. </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and woman are walking in the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> The man lit the book of matches up. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A man is moving a fallen tree. </seg>
<seg id="102"> A man is holding a frog. </seg>
<seg id="103"> there is preparing the item </seg>
<seg id="104"> A Musician performing magic show. </seg>
<seg id="105"> there is a stiching the cloth </seg>
<seg id="106"> A man shows a cricket player how to grip the bat. </seg>
<seg id="107"> cameras are burning. </seg>
<seg id="108"> The man is playing the cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A MAN IS WASHING A CUCUMBER. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The lady sliced a tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="111"> a hero and the heroine are running. </seg>
<seg id="112"> the men is speaking to phone </seg>
<seg id="113"> A person covers a steak in flour. </seg>
<seg id="114"> A man breaks an egg. </seg>
<seg id="115"> The man danced upside down on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> she is cooking </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is cutting a fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> A man is firing with a gun </seg>
<seg id="119"> The mammal bit the person's finger. </seg>
<seg id="120"> a man is rading in a horse </seg>
<seg id="121"> The girl scrubbed the bottom of her feet with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is doing weight lifting. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Two boys are fighting one. </seg>
<seg id="124"> The black horse got up on its feet. </seg>
<seg id="125"> Five little kittens are eating from five little dishes. </seg>
<seg id="126"> The dog knocked the toddler into the water two times. </seg>
<seg id="127"> the person is tyiping </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is looking out of the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> there is a preparing curry </seg>
<seg id="130"> The woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is karate chopping bricks. </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man is erasing a chalk board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A guy tears off a piece of paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> The lady made a hole in a piece of wood with a drill. </seg>
<seg id="135"> the person is playing with cards </seg>
<seg id="136"> The girl played a flute while sitting in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="137"> The girl is playing the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> the person is cooking something </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man using a shotgun for target practice. </seg>
<seg id="140"> The horse and rider fell. </seg>
<seg id="141"> A group of men are dancing in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> The lady is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> The kids are playing on the trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man plays the violin on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> the man folded the quesadilla over in the pan. </seg>
<seg id="146"> The toy train hit the red car on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="147"> The lady is riding on the horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> the dog is playing </seg>
<seg id="149"> The lady cut up an octopus tentacle. </seg>
<seg id="150"> a girl is cutting the tree </seg>
<seg id="151"> A man is mixing ingredients in a large bowl. </seg>
<seg id="152"> The lady made a hole in a piece of wood with a drill. </seg>
<seg id="153"> The lady made a hole in a piece of wood with a drill. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A man is singing into a microphone. </seg>
<seg id="155"> a girl drinking something </seg>
<seg id="156"> kids playing with cycles. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A cooker is showing how to cook. </seg>
<seg id="158"> Someone dives off a cliff. </seg>
<seg id="159"> The skateboarder did a trick and fell off his board. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Two men playing guitars are singing into microphones. </seg>
<seg id="161"> They are dancing </seg>
<seg id="162"> someone is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The lady chopped onions and broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> The lady scrambled the eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person is slicing a green pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> prabudeva song with kajol in merupukalalu </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> The cat opened the drawer and got inside. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is putting makeup on a guy. </seg>
<seg id="170"> Someone petted a rabbit on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="171"> The man played his flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> a movie scene where two actors sitting together </seg>
<seg id="173"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Three persons are doing same exercise. </seg>
<seg id="175"> The girl ate a small cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="176"> The man rode a mechanical bull. </seg>
<seg id="177"> the cat is playing </seg>
<seg id="178"> The skateboarder did a trick and fell off his board. </seg>
<seg id="179"> Fish vs. Turtle in the water </seg>
<seg id="180"> The monkey waded in the water. </seg>
<seg id="181"> Cat catch the fan </seg>
<seg id="182"> Men are sawing a log together. </seg>
<seg id="183"> The chef is preparing to cook Calzone </seg>
<seg id="184"> The men jumped on the coke machine. </seg>
<seg id="185"> The mole is burrowing a hole. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man keep his cup in the microwave and setting the tempreture. </seg>
<seg id="187"> The kitten lapped up the milk from a saucer. </seg>
<seg id="188"> the car is coming </seg>
<seg id="189"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat is playing with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is working out. </seg>
<seg id="192"> A Man is Exercising. </seg>
<seg id="193"> a man caughting a fish </seg>
<seg id="194"> A person is playing with small animal </seg>
<seg id="195"> A kid is doing tricks with a soccer ball. </seg>
<seg id="196"> the person is cooking the something </seg>
<seg id="197"> The lady made a hole in a piece of wood with a drill. </seg>
<seg id="198"> A man shows us his baby monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> The woman is peeling a lemon. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man is drawing a shape on a whiteboard. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog beside the sea </seg>
<seg id="202"> The girl ate a small cupcake. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man slicing a boot. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A man puts some cheese on a pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> The girl played the violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> lady cooking ramen noodles </seg>
<seg id="207"> The dog ran to the tree and hid. </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an antennae. </seg>
<seg id="209"> She is cooking </seg>
<seg id="210"> a girl combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="211"> a woman cutting flowers outside </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat plays the piano. </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman is clicking her nails on a counter top. </seg>
<seg id="214"> preparing something </seg>
<seg id="215"> a man is crossing the road </seg>
<seg id="216"> The lady sliced up the meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> FOOT BALL GAME </seg>
<seg id="218"> A cat is being brushed. </seg>
<seg id="219"> swimmers are ready to jump in to the water. </seg>
<seg id="220"> The cat opened the drawer and got inside. </seg>
<seg id="221"> The man sang while walking down the street. </seg>
<seg id="222"> The lady fried the meat in not oil. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A little girl is speaking in sign language. </seg>
<seg id="224"> lady cooking ramen noodles </seg>
<seg id="225"> Women are dancing and singing on a stage. </seg>
<seg id="226"> Cooking the food. </seg>
<seg id="227"> The man is playing the keyboards. </seg>
<seg id="228"> A teenager is driving a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A GIRL IS SEARCHING IN HER CHAIN. </seg>
<seg id="232"> The seargeant inspected the recruits bunks. </seg>
<seg id="233"> a man is holding the small animal in his hands. </seg>
<seg id="234"> Someone petted a rabbit on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="235"> the person is playing drums </seg>
<seg id="236"> The woman is dancing. </seg>
<seg id="237"> The man is playing a wooden flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> The woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> The dog is opening a can so he can eat. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man is cutting the rope </seg>
<seg id="241"> the small girl is combing the hair by herself. </seg>
<seg id="242"> the man fishing in the river. </seg>
<seg id="243"> The lady fried the meat in not oil. </seg>
<seg id="244"> the small girl is combing the hair by herself. </seg>
<seg id="245"> The woman is seasoning the mixture. </seg>
<seg id="246"> The man tried to feed a live mouse to a snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref18">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A girl names Tammy goes for a horse ride with a friend. </seg>
<seg id="2"> the person is eating curry </seg>
<seg id="3"> featuring a person thinking </seg>
<seg id="4"> The man pet the two dogs while holding a guitar. </seg>
<seg id="5"> A black and white cat playing with a big cardboard box. </seg>
<seg id="6"> A man playing with rat and snake. </seg>
<seg id="7"> a lady is peeling the skin of the fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> The ladies played a ping pong game. </seg>
<seg id="9"> A ballroom of couples dancing. </seg>
<seg id="10"> A guy is making the paper butterfly. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is riding a boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine is sharpening a pencil. </seg>
<seg id="14"> A woman is riding and elephant. </seg>
<seg id="15"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="16"> A woman is holding egg in her hand. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A horse and rider are cantoring around a arena. </seg>
<seg id="18"> the girls are doing the something </seg>
<seg id="19"> The dog opened a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="20"> The dog sat at the counter and watched people. </seg>
<seg id="21"> A young man jumping rope outside his house. </seg>
<seg id="22"> The boy played a small guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> a lady is coming in a rope near the cage </seg>
<seg id="24"> The baby sat on the couch and laughed. </seg>
<seg id="25"> A woman is cutting flowers from a bush. </seg>
<seg id="26"> A cooker cuts onions for chinese cooking. </seg>
<seg id="27"> A Women Performing Violin. </seg>
<seg id="28"> A man is talking to a woman on a computer. </seg>
<seg id="29"> A man is hiking. </seg>
<seg id="30"> A person is cooking </seg>
<seg id="31"> South Indian film song clip </seg>
<seg id="32"> A Man showing a base ball to a women. </seg>
<seg id="33"> A man is playing a saxophone. </seg>
<seg id="34"> The man climbed up a rope. </seg>
<seg id="35"> the person is cleaning the foot </seg>
<seg id="36"> the person is cutting </seg>
<seg id="37"> The man talked to the reporters. </seg>
<seg id="38"> They are cooking </seg>
<seg id="39"> A guy is singing a song . </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is Beating eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A man playing keyboard </seg>
<seg id="42"> A man erases a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="43"> The mammal ate something in his paw. </seg>
<seg id="44"> A man is putting kneel down. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A small dog and a large dog are on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="46"> Men are fighting in a ranch. </seg>
<seg id="47"> Virginia Farm Bureau - In the Garden - Sunflowers </seg>
<seg id="48"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="49"> A man is typing . </seg>
<seg id="50"> A person plays the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> the cats are drinking milk </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is riding a motorcycle. </seg>
<seg id="53"> The dog opened a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A man dances in the street. </seg>
<seg id="55"> there is a one men </seg>
<seg id="56"> a big green ball hit something </seg>
<seg id="57"> The boy looked at the calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A man with scares in the face is standing. </seg>
<seg id="59"> men are flipping tires. </seg>
<seg id="60"> The girl is dancing and singing in the rain in a south indian movie. </seg>
<seg id="61"> Guitar is being played by artist. </seg>
<seg id="62"> A man is putting kneel down. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A boy is diving backwards from a diving board. </seg>
<seg id="65"> the man is playing the guitar </seg>
<seg id="66"> A woman eats a drumstick. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is shaking a container over a sink. </seg>
<seg id="68"> A little boy is playing in the mud. </seg>
<seg id="69"> A cat is drinking milk from the plate </seg>
<seg id="70"> the man is playing gitter. </seg>
<seg id="71"> Mannippaya orginal jaazay Tv Rip hq hd vinnai </seg>
<seg id="72"> The woman is boiling eggs. </seg>
<seg id="73"> A little animal is getting a bath. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man is emerging from water. </seg>
<seg id="75"> The man is drawing. </seg>
<seg id="76"> A panda is laying on some logs. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A little girl is on her back porch watering the plants and spraying them. </seg>
<seg id="78"> The man talked to the lady. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is chopping up an onion. </seg>
<seg id="80"> A man and a woman walk through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="81"> the boy beating  a man's backside  with a stick </seg>
<seg id="82"> a lady is cutting the butter. </seg>
<seg id="83"> a baby rhino </seg>
<seg id="84"> a big green ball hit something </seg>
<seg id="85"> i heard a great music </seg>
<seg id="86"> the three girls are dancing </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey is doing karate. </seg>
<seg id="88"> The man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> A guy is singing a song . </seg>
<seg id="90"> A man is cutting the breads. </seg>
<seg id="91"> The small animals are playing </seg>
<seg id="92"> a boy is playing </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cat is rubbing and smelling a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="94"> A small dog and a large dog are on a bed. </seg>
<seg id="95"> a lady is cutting papaya </seg>
<seg id="96"> A man pours tomato paste into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> The lady poured oil in the pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> the old lady tells something about her breakfast </seg>
<seg id="99"> A man and a woman walk through the woods. </seg>
<seg id="100"> The matches caught on fire. </seg>
<seg id="101"> A forest in north manitou island in 2008 </seg>
<seg id="102"> it looks like a really cute walking scrotum that chirps Yeh supposed to be millions of years old hahahahah.And extinct hahaha.Cant bring the big ones on the boat obviously. </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is pouring oil into the bowl </seg>
<seg id="104"> A man is doing magic tricks </seg>
<seg id="105"> A lady is sewing cloth by sewing machine </seg>
<seg id="106"> The coach helped the boy with his stroke. </seg>
<seg id="107"> A camera is on fire. </seg>
<seg id="108"> The man played the cello. </seg>
<seg id="109"> A woman is cleaning a vegetable. </seg>
<seg id="110"> The lady sliced the tomatoe. </seg>
<seg id="111"> A man and woman are running. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> A person is cooking </seg>
<seg id="114"> The man cracked eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="115"> The man is dancing on the ceiling. </seg>
<seg id="116"> The woman is breaking egg in the bowl. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A man is cutting the meat </seg>
<seg id="118"> someone is shooting with the gun </seg>
<seg id="119"> A man has his finger in a loris's mouth. </seg>
<seg id="120"> a man is riding a horse </seg>
<seg id="121"> the person is cleaning the foot </seg>
<seg id="122"> The man is lifting weights. </seg>
<seg id="123"> Two men are fighting. </seg>
<seg id="124"> A horse is standing up. </seg>
<seg id="125"> the cats are drinking milk </seg>
<seg id="126"> The dog knocked the toddler over into the water twice. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A man is typing . </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is seeing through the window </seg>
<seg id="129"> a lady is stirring  the lady finger which is in the boiling water. </seg>
<seg id="130"> The old woman is peeling potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="131"> the person is breaking bricks </seg>
<seg id="132"> A man erases a chalkboard. </seg>
<seg id="133"> A man is Makeing  a Paper Cup </seg>
<seg id="134"> the person is doing the something </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is performing a card trick. </seg>
<seg id="136"> The girl played her flute while sitting in a chair. </seg>
<seg id="137"> The girl played her flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A man is stirring the contents of a pan. </seg>
<seg id="139"> The man shot his gun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> The horse fell down with its rider. </seg>
<seg id="141"> Dasavatharam Song Copied from Vikram's Movie </seg>
<seg id="142"> The woman is cracking eggs into a bowl. </seg>
<seg id="143"> the two boys jumped on the tramplines. </seg>
<seg id="144"> The fiddler played the fiddle on the roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> A person is cooking </seg>
<seg id="146"> The toy train hit the toy car on the tracks. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> the dog is jumping </seg>
<seg id="149"> octopus dumpling. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A woman picks up a large watering can. </seg>
<seg id="151"> A person is making salad </seg>
<seg id="152"> the person is doing the something </seg>
<seg id="153"> the person is doing the something </seg>
<seg id="154"> a man singing. </seg>
<seg id="155"> A GIRL IS DRINKING SOMETHING. </seg>
<seg id="156"> Little kids playing outside on their tricycles and scooters. </seg>
<seg id="157"> the  arusuvai arangam the two persons  demo how to prepare the food tasty </seg>
<seg id="158"> Someone is jumping off a rock. </seg>
<seg id="159"> The skateboarder fell off his board while doing a trick. </seg>
<seg id="160"> Some persons are playing music </seg>
<seg id="161"> the women is get down the water </seg>
<seg id="162"> The man is slicing a potato. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The lady cut up broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is Beating eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> A person slices a pepper. </seg>
<seg id="166"> the person is dasncing </seg>
<seg id="167"> A baby is crawling along the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> the cat is playing with box </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman is applying clown-like makeup to a man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> A man is playing with his bunny. </seg>
<seg id="171"> The man played his flute. </seg>
<seg id="172"> A man is riding a scooter. </seg>
<seg id="173"> the person playing the music </seg>
<seg id="174"> Two women and a man are stamping their feet on the floor and swinging their hands in rhythmic fashion. </seg>
<seg id="175"> The teenagers is home coming </seg>
<seg id="176"> Do like to ride a bull then watch this </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cat is rubbing and smelling a bottle. </seg>
<seg id="178"> The skateboarder fell off his board while doing a trick. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A terrapin is swimming. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A big water stream is falling down from the mountain. </seg>
<seg id="181"> the cat is playing with fan </seg>
<seg id="182"> two men are cutting the wood. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A chef is preparing dough. </seg>
<seg id="184"> the boy and girl is making the dancing </seg>
<seg id="185"> A Batter open a mud. </seg>
<seg id="186"> A man showing how to prepare a prime rib dinner for Christmas on cookingfordads.com </seg>
<seg id="187"> Puppy is drinking milk </seg>
<seg id="188"> a man singing a song </seg>
<seg id="189"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="190"> A cat plays with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> he is do exercise. </seg>
<seg id="192"> He is doing execise </seg>
<seg id="193"> A man has caught the fish </seg>
<seg id="194"> the boy is playing the dog </seg>
<seg id="195"> A boys he night footaball sikllfoot path. </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is shaking a container over a sink. </seg>
<seg id="197"> the person is doing the something </seg>
<seg id="198"> The man held the monkey in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="199"> A woman cuts vegetables. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A man showing how a computer can understand what he is drawing and respond to it. </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is jumping into the pool. </seg>
<seg id="202"> The teenagers is home coming </seg>
<seg id="203"> the man is cut the shoes </seg>
<seg id="204"> The man sprinkled cheese on the pizza. </seg>
<seg id="205"> The woman is playing the violin. </seg>
<seg id="206"> the women is preparing noodles </seg>
<seg id="207"> the dog is frightened </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an electronic device antenna </seg>
<seg id="209"> she is cutting the something </seg>
<seg id="210"> A girl is making her hairs </seg>
<seg id="211"> A woman is cutting flowers from a bush. </seg>
<seg id="212"> A cat playing with peyano </seg>
<seg id="213"> A woman drums her fingers on a table. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is cutting a potato. </seg>
<seg id="215"> a man is praying in the middle of the street. </seg>
<seg id="216"> The woman is slicing meat. </seg>
<seg id="217"> The people's are playing the football </seg>
<seg id="218"> a cat is playing </seg>
<seg id="219"> Women dive into a lake. </seg>
<seg id="220"> the cat is playing with box </seg>
<seg id="221"> A Man Singing on a footpath. </seg>
<seg id="222"> the man is saying how to make  Katsudon </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl is signing or talking with her hands. </seg>
<seg id="224"> the women is preparing noodles </seg>
<seg id="225"> A lady policers are singing on stage. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A chef pouring oil and adding spices into a bowl </seg>
<seg id="227"> The man played an organ. </seg>
<seg id="228"> Two boys diving in a car. </seg>
<seg id="229"> The man played his guitar. </seg>
<seg id="230"> A baby is crawling along the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> A woman is putting string on a metal shaft. </seg>
<seg id="232"> A man is putting kneel down. </seg>
<seg id="233"> a bird is so small </seg>
<seg id="234"> A man is playing with his bunny. </seg>
<seg id="235"> A young man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="236"> Actres performing dance in the movie. </seg>
<seg id="237"> A man plays a huge flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> A Women Performing Violin. </seg>
<seg id="239"> The dog opened a can of dog food. </seg>
<seg id="240"> A man slices a rope with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A baby is standing in front of the mirror. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is fishing in the pond. </seg>
<seg id="243"> the man is saying how to make  Katsudon </seg>
<seg id="244"> A baby is standing in front of the mirror. </seg>
<seg id="245"> Woman making some Japanese food. </seg>
<seg id="246"> A man playing with rat and snake. </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
<refset setid="example_set" srclang="bar" trglang="baz" refid="ref19">
                          <doc docid="doc1" genre="nw">
                          <p>
<seg id="1"> A girl racing on horse </seg>
<seg id="2"> A man is telling something </seg>
<seg id="3"> cud u plz post the song where pawan kalyan dances with mumtaj in this movie..id really appreciate it </seg>
<seg id="4"> A man is play with pets </seg>
<seg id="5"> A cat  jump and goes under the box </seg>
<seg id="6"> the man is keeping food to snakes </seg>
<seg id="7"> A woman is cleaning a fish. </seg>
<seg id="8"> Two man are playing table tennis. </seg>
<seg id="9"> the tamil film song poove sem poove sang actor karthick </seg>
<seg id="10"> A guy making a paper butterfly. </seg>
<seg id="11"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="12"> A man is sailing the boat. </seg>
<seg id="13"> A machine is sharping a pencil </seg>
<seg id="14"> a woman riding a elephant </seg>
<seg id="15"> Man playing guitar </seg>
<seg id="16"> Laura in the kitchen explains and shows how to make banana bread from scratch. </seg>
<seg id="17"> A man ride on horse </seg>
<seg id="18"> A ladies anklets being measured </seg>
<seg id="19"> A dog open a box and eat. </seg>
<seg id="20"> the dog is setting the shop </seg>
<seg id="21"> skipping exercise is very good for his health </seg>
<seg id="22"> The little boy played a small guitar. </seg>
<seg id="23"> A women ropells to the ground on a tree branch. </seg>
<seg id="24"> The toddler giggled on the couch. </seg>
<seg id="25"> a women playing with flowers </seg>
<seg id="26"> A man is cutting a onion </seg>
<seg id="27"> She is playing music </seg>
<seg id="28"> one boy is talking with girl </seg>
<seg id="29"> a man walking around with sticks </seg>
<seg id="30"> the person is making omelet </seg>
<seg id="31"> A Couple Singing in the Movie </seg>
<seg id="32"> They are playing </seg>
<seg id="33"> actor prabhu play the instrument very nicely in the tamil movie </seg>
<seg id="34"> a man climbing a rope </seg>
<seg id="35"> A person is brushing the sole of his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="36"> A woman is peeling a potatoe. </seg>
<seg id="37"> a famous hero of india saying something to media </seg>
<seg id="38"> the boys are cooking the somethiung </seg>
<seg id="39"> a man playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="40"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="41"> A men playing gitar. </seg>
<seg id="42"> The man erased the work on the board. </seg>
<seg id="43"> A loris is eating fruit. </seg>
<seg id="44"> 10 Minutes of Boot Camp. </seg>
<seg id="45"> A dog is laying on a bed wagging his tail. </seg>
<seg id="46"> two men are fighting in the film sequence. </seg>
<seg id="47"> A guy is holding the sunflower in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="48"> the boys are doing the fighting </seg>
<seg id="49"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="50"> The man is playing the keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="51"> Cats are eating food. </seg>
<seg id="52"> A man is sitting on the road. </seg>
<seg id="53"> A dog open a box and eat. </seg>
<seg id="54"> A young man and a woman freaking out in the hills. </seg>
<seg id="55"> A man is speaking </seg>
<seg id="56"> A boy having a green ball in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="57"> The boy looked at the calendar. </seg>
<seg id="58"> A men with talking with a boy </seg>
<seg id="59"> two strongest man playing a game with tyre </seg>
<seg id="60"> the girl is happily dancing in the rain. </seg>
<seg id="61"> A person is singing and playing with the guitar </seg>
<seg id="62"> 10 Minutes of Boot Camp. </seg>
<seg id="63"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="64"> A guy is jumping into the swimming pool. </seg>
<seg id="65"> A man is playing benzo. </seg>
<seg id="66"> The lady ate chicken in her hands. </seg>
<seg id="67"> A man is straining some noodles. </seg>
<seg id="68"> a boy falling in the mud </seg>
<seg id="69"> Cat drinking milk </seg>
<seg id="70"> A man is playing the guitar. </seg>
<seg id="71"> A man jumps on a fence. </seg>
<seg id="72"> how to make some delicious Yakibuta Ramen </seg>
<seg id="73"> A hedgehog is being bathed in a sink. </seg>
<seg id="74"> A man emerges from mud. </seg>
<seg id="75"> A group of guys are painting on the wall. </seg>
<seg id="76"> a panda is lying on the wood. </seg>
<seg id="77"> A little girl is spraying plants with water. </seg>
<seg id="78"> A guy is teasing the  girl. </seg>
<seg id="79"> A woman is cooking vegetable pot pie. </seg>
<seg id="80"> The couple walked down the path together. </seg>
<seg id="81"> A boy hits a man in the back. </seg>
<seg id="82"> A woman is cutting tofu in half. </seg>
<seg id="83"> A baby rhino follows an adult rhino. </seg>
<seg id="84"> A boy having a green ball in his hand. </seg>
<seg id="85"> A MAN IS SINGING ON THE STAGE. </seg>
<seg id="86"> Three young women are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="87"> A monkey performing karate moves. </seg>
<seg id="88"> The man is playing the drums. </seg>
<seg id="89"> a man playing guitar. </seg>
<seg id="90"> a man is cutting the pices of bun </seg>
<seg id="91"> the baby is playing them </seg>
<seg id="92"> A boy is playing with a toy phone. </seg>
<seg id="93"> A cute cat </seg>
<seg id="94"> A dog is laying on a bed wagging his tail. </seg>
<seg id="95"> A lady is explaining how to make a Papaya smoothie </seg>
<seg id="96"> The lady added tomatoe sauce to the sausage and wine in a pot. </seg>
<seg id="97"> Someone is pouring oil into a pot. </seg>
<seg id="98"> the old lady is talking. </seg>
<seg id="99"> The couple walked down the path together. </seg>
<seg id="100"> A Man Playing with Fire sticks. </seg>
<seg id="101"> a man carrying a tree. </seg>
<seg id="102"> the man is in the forest </seg>
<seg id="103"> A woman is putting oil in a pan. </seg>
<seg id="104"> the person is doing the magic </seg>
<seg id="105"> a women is stitching the cloth </seg>
<seg id="106"> a man is coaching cricket </seg>
<seg id="107"> a person burning a camera </seg>
<seg id="108"> A guy play a violin. </seg>
<seg id="109"> a person perparing something </seg>
<seg id="110"> The woman is slicing a tomato. </seg>
<seg id="111"> The girl and boy were running towards the sea. </seg>
<seg id="112"> A man is talking on a phone. </seg>
<seg id="113"> the women is cooking something </seg>
<seg id="114"> one man is braking egg in a bowl </seg>
<seg id="115"> a dancer dancing in a very crazy style </seg>
<seg id="116"> A lady preparing food using eggs. </seg>
<seg id="117"> A chef cutting fish. </seg>
<seg id="118"> Shotgun in UltraSlo motion. </seg>
<seg id="119"> the cat is eating </seg>
<seg id="120"> A man is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="121"> A person is brushing the sole of his foot with a toothbrush. </seg>
<seg id="122"> A man is lifting a large weight. </seg>
<seg id="123"> the boys are doing the fighting </seg>
<seg id="124"> the group of horse are searching the food and eat and drink </seg>
<seg id="125"> Cats are eating food. </seg>
<seg id="126"> A kid playing with dog at rainy water. </seg>
<seg id="127"> A person is typing. </seg>
<seg id="128"> A cat is staring out the window. </seg>
<seg id="129"> Someone is boiling peppers. </seg>
<seg id="130"> A woman is peeling a potato. </seg>
<seg id="131"> A man is breaking the tiles </seg>
<seg id="132"> The man erased the work on the board. </seg>
<seg id="133"> a man showing how to cut a paper. </seg>
<seg id="134"> A person drilled a hold in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="135"> A man is showing some tricks with playing cards </seg>
<seg id="136"> A girl perform the Flute. </seg>
<seg id="137"> The girl played the flute. </seg>
<seg id="138"> A person is stirring a pot of soup on he stove. </seg>
<seg id="139"> A man is shooting a shotgun. </seg>
<seg id="140"> jockey falling from horse </seg>
<seg id="141"> Men are dancing in front of an airplane. </seg>
<seg id="142"> Learn to make Omurice </seg>
<seg id="143"> Two boy are playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="144"> A man is fiddling on a roof. </seg>
<seg id="145"> the person is making omelet </seg>
<seg id="146"> The toy train ran into the toy car. </seg>
<seg id="147"> A woman is riding a horse. </seg>
<seg id="148"> A dog is playing on a trampoline. </seg>
<seg id="149"> A woman is cutting up octopus. </seg>
<seg id="150"> A lady is pouring water </seg>
<seg id="151"> the person is preparing the food </seg>
<seg id="152"> A person drilled a hold in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="153"> A person drilled a hold in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="154"> A person singing a song </seg>
<seg id="155"> a man talking on some issue </seg>
<seg id="156"> the kids are playing outside. </seg>
<seg id="157"> A man is wiping a bowl of food. </seg>
<seg id="158"> The man jumped off the cliff into the water. </seg>
<seg id="159"> Tony Hawk is doing skateboard tricks. </seg>
<seg id="160"> boys are playing guttier </seg>
<seg id="161"> People are dancing outside. </seg>
<seg id="162"> The man is slicing potatoes. </seg>
<seg id="163"> The woman is cutting broccoli. </seg>
<seg id="164"> A woman is stirring eggs. </seg>
<seg id="165"> a man is cutting the capsicum. </seg>
<seg id="166"> A man is crying </seg>
<seg id="167"> The baby crawled on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="168"> the cat is inside the box. </seg>
<seg id="169"> A woman applies makeup on a man. </seg>
<seg id="170"> someone is playing with a rabbit </seg>
<seg id="171"> Un barbat canta la fluier melodia din super mario. </seg>
<seg id="172"> a man riding a scooter </seg>
<seg id="173"> the man is playing guiter. </seg>
<seg id="174"> Women are doing exercises. </seg>
<seg id="175"> A woman is eat cupcakes. </seg>
<seg id="176"> the person is playing </seg>
<seg id="177"> A cute cat </seg>
<seg id="178"> Tony Hawk is doing skateboard tricks. </seg>
<seg id="179"> A turtle is chasing a fish underwater. </seg>
<seg id="180"> A monkey in the water </seg>
<seg id="181"> A cat is playing with a ceiling fan. </seg>
<seg id="182"> A PEOPLE ARE SINGING AND WORKING. </seg>
<seg id="183"> A chef is rolling out dough. </seg>
<seg id="184"> Men are dancing. </seg>
<seg id="185"> A badger is digging. </seg>
<seg id="186"> Man is setting up the temperature of the oven. </seg>
<seg id="187"> the cat is drinking the milk </seg>
<seg id="188"> A truck is driving up the road. </seg>
<seg id="189"> Man playing guitar </seg>
<seg id="190"> The cat played with a watermelon. </seg>
<seg id="191"> A man is doing excercise </seg>
<seg id="192"> the person is doing exercise </seg>
<seg id="193"> a men and women is catching fish </seg>
<seg id="194"> masagining monky </seg>
<seg id="195"> A person playing football </seg>
<seg id="196"> A man is straining some noodles. </seg>
<seg id="197"> A person drilled a hold in a piece of wood. </seg>
<seg id="198"> The man is holding a baby monkey. </seg>
<seg id="199"> The lady cut some lemon rind. </seg>
<seg id="200"> A teacher teaches the computer programming </seg>
<seg id="201"> A dog is trying to jump in water </seg>
<seg id="202"> A woman is eat cupcakes. </seg>
<seg id="203"> A man cuts a boot with a sword. </seg>
<seg id="204"> A person is cooking </seg>
<seg id="205"> a girl is playing a guitar </seg>
<seg id="206"> A woman cooks noodles. </seg>
<seg id="207"> a dog playing a game of hide and seek </seg>
<seg id="208"> A cat is playing with an antenna. </seg>
<seg id="209"> A woman is chopping an eggplant. </seg>
<seg id="210"> a girl maintaining her hair </seg>
<seg id="211"> a women playing with flowers </seg>
<seg id="212"> you must do practice </seg>
<seg id="213"> A girl drummed her fingers. </seg>
<seg id="214"> A man is slicing a potato </seg>
<seg id="215"> A man is praying in the street. </seg>
<seg id="216"> How to make a good Japanese delicacy </seg>
<seg id="217"> Two groups are playing football </seg>
<seg id="218"> A man brushing hair of a cat. </seg>
<seg id="219"> girls are swimming </seg>
<seg id="220"> the cat is inside the box. </seg>
<seg id="221"> A man is walking an singing. </seg>
<seg id="222"> A woman is frying a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="223"> A girl uses sign languages to communicate. </seg>
<seg id="224"> A woman cooks noodles. </seg>
<seg id="225"> Pranks and comedy at policeman's ball. </seg>
<seg id="226"> A japenees woman putting some kind of oil or vinegar in a bowl and adding some ingredients to make temaki sushi. </seg>
<seg id="227"> Someone is playing on a keyboard. </seg>
<seg id="228"> the boys are doing the car driving </seg>
<seg id="229"> Man playing guitar </seg>
<seg id="230"> The baby crawled on the floor. </seg>
<seg id="231"> They are talking </seg>
<seg id="232"> 10 Minutes of Boot Camp. </seg>
<seg id="233"> A MAN IS SHOWING SOME ANIMALS. </seg>
<seg id="234"> someone is playing with a rabbit </seg>
<seg id="235"> A man is drumming. </seg>
<seg id="236"> the girl is dancing near fire </seg>
<seg id="237"> The man played a long flute. </seg>
<seg id="238"> She is playing music </seg>
<seg id="239"> A dog open a box and eat. </seg>
<seg id="240"> There is a white guy severing a rope using a Chinese sword. </seg>
<seg id="241"> A small girl is combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="242"> A man is realling in a fish. </seg>
<seg id="243"> A woman is frying a piece of meat. </seg>
<seg id="244"> A small girl is combing her hair. </seg>
<seg id="245"> the woman is cooking </seg>
<seg id="246"> the man is keeping food to snakes </seg>
</p>
</doc>
</refset>
</mteval>
